♪ Four letter words
just to get me alone ♪
♪ It's a difficulty
and I'm biting on my tongue ♪
♪ And I never say
anything at all ♪
♪ But with nothing to consider,
they forget my name. ♪
Oh, not bad...
for a girl.
A girl off the men's tee, Brad.
Ignore him, Lucy,
he's just jealous.
Whoa, was anyone complaining
when they set us up with a girl?
Actually, yes. Something about
her killing your mojo.
(laughing) Thanks.
What are you, like 17?
Only for another 11 hours or so.
This is an early birthday
present from my folks.
Want to give it a try?
(groans)
Looking a little whipped
today, Ry-boy.
(groans) Long night.
Barely got three
hours of sleep.
Not me.
Slept like a free man.
No kids, no headaches.
No ball and chain.
Yeah, no nothing that matters, right?
BRAD: Okay, guys.
Keep the Vanessa stuff
off the course, all right?
Fine by me.
Just hit the ball already.
Come on.
That's terrible.
(chuckling)
Just when you thought a bad shot
couldn't get any worse.
BRAD:
Oh, he's had worse.
In the water.
The water.
All right.
I should take the drop.
BRAD: What, are you kidding?
Dropping is for...
Girls?
Sissies.
I was gonna say sissies.
Mm-hmm.
Ooh...
that is nasty.
BRAD:
Just hit it.
BRAD: Staring at it's not going
to improve the line, Ryan.
(chuckling)
(cries out in pain)
Are you okay?
(yelling)
Ryan! Alligator!
Ryan! Grab my hand!
Ryan!
Grab my hand!
(grunts)
Elroy, hit him!
Grab my hand!
(Ryan yelling)
(yelling)
Ryan! Ryan!
Ryan!
Ryan?
Ryan?!
♪ ♪
♪ Here it comes ♪
♪ Here it comes, here it comes ♪
♪ Here it comes
♪ Here comes your nineteenth
nervous breakdown... ♪
Sync by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com
Am I reading this right?
"Alligator attack
at Palm Drive Country Club"?
Last I heard,
it was five minutes out.
What's this?
Tickets to The Black Eyed Peas?
Tonight?
Oh, my pneumo
from a couple weeks ago.
He wanted to thank me.
Oh, I love The Black Eyed Peas.
Where did you score those?
They're Eva's.
She was just about
to invite me along.
Huh.
And why would she
take you when she could take me?
Huh. PROCTOR: I saw The Black Eyed
Peas in Boston two years ago.
Got a call to go backstage
when Fergie got...
food poisoning.
(pagers beeping)
Will.i.am will have
to be put on hold.
Gator victim's on our doorstep.
I will pick up
your dry cleaning for a month.
No, no, no,
I will wash your car
and a neck massage.
(scoffs) Hmm.
(elevator bell dings)
GRACEFFA:
Ryan Whitten.
28-year-old male.
Right foot amputation
and lacerated femoral artery.
Abdominal trauma,
altered mental status
and respiratory distress.
GCS is 4-6-4,
tachy and hypotensive.
I was standing there
and then my foot was just gone.
We'll get you
stabilized first, Ryan,
then we'll deal with the foot.
Did they recover it?
WARREN:
The foot!
Haven't found it on scene.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, hey.
BRAD: Hey.
Uh, we're Ryan's friends.
Brad Dalton.
Elroy Hindley. We were-we were with him.
The gator--
had to weigh, like, 500 pounds.
Yeah, he dragged him in the pond
and held him under.
How long was he underwater?
Two, three minutes.
Wasn't breathing
when we pulled him out.
Why don't you tell everything
to one of our nurses.
Yeah, and then do not pass go,
do not collect $200,
you're gonna
go straight to the ER,
get these injuries checked.
What, this isn't the ER?
No, this is MT1.
It's trauma only.
ER's around the corner.
We're gonna stay with Ryan.
No, no, no, no, you're gonna
go through those doors,
around the corner
and to your right.
Just...
Do not make me continue
with the monopoly
references, Brad.
We'll be right back.
Great.
Lucy Reyes, multiple lacs
to head and arms
with blunt head trauma.
All right, Lucy, can you tell me
where you're feeling any pain?
My head.
Everything's spinning.
Let's finish a primary survey,
get her a head CT.
Oh, and, uh...
Next of kin?
Her parents.
Got a cell phone number
for her father.
Good work, Kleebus.
(Ryan groaning)
Ow, my leg!
It's throbbing.
(groans)
One milligram of Dilaudid.
We're gonna give you something
to take the pain away, Ryan.
You just drift off
to sleep, okay?
I'll take the femoral artery.
ZAMBRANO:
Check his lungs.
I need some help--
he's bleeding out.
Grab me a stack of four by fours
and two units
on the rapid infuser.
(monitor beeping rapidly,
Zambrano groans)
Pressure's still dropping.
Should I call up to O.R.?
He's not gonna make it
unless we stop the bleeding.
They found the foot; golf course
security's bringing it in.
PROCTOR:
Excellent!
We'll stop the hemorrhage.
Serena, go and get
that foot ice.
Where is it?
Here's your perp.
Complete with
the stolen goods inside.
You mean the foot...
is inside there?
Mm-hmm. Oh, we dredged the pond.
There was only one gator, so...
So you shot it?
You'd prefer him alive?
Okay...
Let's get the gator
on a gurney.
Ali Gator, age and sex unknown.
GSW to the right flank,
possible esophageal reflux
from ingesting a human foot.
Tell Eva to page us when Ryan,
our foot amputee, is stabilized.
Want me to...
And miss the
chance of a lifetime,
are you kidding?
There's quite a bit of
tough abdominal muscle
to get through here.
What's this...
Must've been midday snack.
Lucky for Ryan.
Force of their bite is
2,000 pounds per square inch.
Great.
This feels like bone.
(grunting)
I'll find Zambrano,
if you, uh...
Contact the on-call
vascular surgeon for a consult.
If it's viable, we're gonna
have to act fast.
Thank you.
Hey, there, Lucy.
Sweetheart?
Dad.
Mom's trying to get
a flight back from Chicago.
Okay.
I'm just gonna ask you a few
questions and then you can
get some more rest.
You still feeling dizzy?
Um, no, I'm just really tired.
That's normal with head trauma.
How about any nausea
or blurry vision?
No, not really.
Well, her head CT shows
no bleeding in her brain, so...
Thank God.
Yeah.
How soon can I practice again?
You take it easy-- let's...
let's get you checked out
before you start
setting tee times.
She has a golf scholarship.
A full ride to Stanford.
Really?
Yeah.
Pre-season training
starts in, like, a month, so...
Oh, yeah?
Have you tried opening up your grip?
Mmm.
If you just, uh, don't wrap
your right thumb over your left
so much, then...
Was, um,
was this redness here
before you got those cuts?
Um... I guess so.
I have pretty sensitive skin.
It could be that
new sunblock, Luce.
Let's get them checked out
just to be sure.
Uh, let's get a tissue sample,
send it up to the lab.
That's it.
I'll come back
once we get the results.
Great.
Thank you.
Uh, open up my grip?
Got it.
Pressure cf stopped the bleed
in Ryan's leg.
His femoral artery should hold
up until we get him to the O.R.
How is his breathing?
High-flow oxygen
seems to be helping.
Doesn't appear to have
aspirated water.
That's unusual,
considering he was underwater
for three minutes.
Ryan's wife just arrived.
And wee got an O.R. scheduled
for an hour from now.
Vascular consult's on the way.
All right,
let's Ryan a chest CT
to check for any delayed
lung swelling.
Run another set of blood work
and prep him
for the foot replant.
WARREN:
I'll take the Fe.
Not if you want to see
The Black Eyed Peas.
How about I do all the blood
work, oversee O.R. prep,
and buy all the food, drinks and
souvenirs your heart desires?
Better.
I'll take the wife.
Are you Ryan's wife?
Yes, Vanessa Whitten.
Hi, I'm-I'm Dr. Zambrano.
I'm afraid your husband's
in critical condition.
He was having
difficulty breathing.
But it seems to be
resolving now.
I can't believe
this is happening.
The good news is that
we were able to stem
the bleeding
in his femoral artery.
And how about his foot?
They recovered it.
We're just checking
to see if it's viable
for reattachment surgery.
ELROY: So that's good, right?
It's better than
the alternative, yes.
Aren't you supposed
to be in the ER?
Oh, dude, I told you the hot
doctor was gonna be pissed
if we hung around.
I'm fine.
He won't go, Doc--
he doesn't think I could
handle this.
I'm sting, Vanessa.
Hey, who wants to get a coffee?
Maybe a latte?
You and your stupid golf game.
What does this have to do with golf?
He even took an earlier
flight for you, Elroy.
Yeah, he got bit by an alligator
because he took an earlier flight.
That makes a lot of sense.
You know what, not everyone
can live like they're
still in college, Elroy!
Do you think I wanted him to end up here?!
BRAD: Hey!
I'm his best friend!
Yeah, you know what,
I'm his wife! Elroy!
Okay, okay!
Tensions are high.
I need you two to calm down.
For Ryan.
He has complicated surgeries
ahead of him.
Elroy and I are absolutely
gonna go get that drink now.
Okay. (whispers):
It's gonna be decaf.
I'll come find you
if I have any updates, okay?
Alligator made a clean cut
through the major vessels.
The foot looks remarkably good.
Especially considering
they pack about
2,000 pounds of bite force.
You're a closet herpetologist?
I got it from Proctor.
Mmm.
Quite a mind on that one.
Is Vascular here yet?
Dr. Sable.
You're not Vascular.
You're Cardio.
Actual, I'm both.
No one's both, not anymore.
Cal Berkeley and U Penn
may disagree.
Is the foot viable?
I'd say we have a good shot
at replantation.
How's the patient?
I tied off his femoral artery.
Though not perhaps
with the elegance
of someone of your expertise...
Oh, I'm sure you make up
for it in other ways.
Should I go do... something?
Get the foot prepped
and take Ito the O.R.
Dinner, Nobu, one hour
after your shift ends.
What if it's 8:00
in the morning?
Breakfast at the Brick House.
And if it turns
into lunch, Tony's
on Palmdale Drive.
You think of everything.
Yes, I do.
(pager beeping) Doctor Deleo.
See you in the O.R.
Looking forward to it.
What's up?
(sighing) My golfer,
Lucy Reyes, she has a redness
spreading up her arm.
Thought it was
cellulitis but...
PROCTOR: Doesn't appear
to be simple cellulitis.
Looks more like a
vibrio infection.
And it looks like it's
spreading to her deep tissue.
That's necrotizing fascinitis.
Flesh-eating bacteria.
If she got this in the pond,
that means the other patients
are at risk, too.
(siren wailing)
Okay, turn over.
What's that for?
To help us track
the rate of bacterial growth.
LUCY:
So, it's getting worse?
It's developed into
something called,
uh, necrotizing fasciitis.
I saw that on the news.
That's flesh-eating bacteria?
Oh, my God, flesh-eating?
It's not-it's not
literally eating, Lucy,
but it is causing
the destruction
of the underlying
tissues in your arm.
Do the others have it?
Not so far.
Not everybody who's exposed
to it gets infected.
What do we do?
First we try debriding.
Cutting away
the infected tissue.
But the chance of that actually
stopping the spreading of it
are about 20 percent.
And if it keeps spreading?
If it gets into her blood,
then it could cause
something known as sepsis.
Um, now, once that happens,
it will shut down
your vital organs.
The only sure way
to completely eliminate
the bacteria...
is amputation of the limb.
What? No, no.
And that's only
as a last resort, Lucy.
You're not cutting off my arm.
Let the doctor
speak, sweetie.
No, I don't care
what you have to do.
If there's a 20 percent
chance to save it, just...
We're gonna do
whatever we need to do
to get you through this.
That's not your call!
Let's just listen.
No, I'm an adult now, okay,
or I will be in, like,
six hours, and this is my body.
You can't tell me
what to do with that.
Lucy, Mr. Reyes, I understand.
It's a lot to absorb,
but at the moment,
hard as it may sound,
I just need you to be
patient until the biopsy results
come in.
Then we decide how to proceed.
Together.
Okay?
ZAMBRANO:
Good news, Ryan.
Your chest CT looks no
so we're gonna prep you
for the O.R.
My wife, Vanessa?
Here.
She's in the waiting area
with your friends.
Not to worry. I've been
updating her on your condition.
Can you, uh,
take him up to the ICU
and page me
when the O.R.'s ready?
Great.
I'll see you soon.
Clam chowder
or chicken with stars?
Oh, first, I have a rule about
taking soup from strangers.
Really?
Mm-hmm.
And second, why aren't
you still the ER?
Well, yeah, I had to use my
ninja moves to get Elroy there.
But then I claimed
I had to go to the bathroom
so I could go check on Vanessa.
Mmm. Those two-- it's
like fire and ice.
Yeah, I noticed.
Must be hard
running interference.
We've en tight since college.
Elroy took it
kind of personally
when Vanessa AR.
Started calling her Yoko.
She broke up the Fab Three?
Whoa, you mean Fab One.
Those two, they're...
well, they're all right.
Are you flirting with me?
The soup offering
might've been flirting.
But the, uh, the banter,
it's just keeping
the communication open.
In hopes that if something does
happen, you'll come to me first.
That way I can manage
fire and ice.
Sounds like a solid plan.
I'll see you in bit.
What about our soup date?
I have lives to save.
Get back to the ER.
Consider it a rain check.
I'm going to talk to him, okay?
Hey, Dr. Deleo?
If-if there's
any chance...
that you have to amputate
to save her life,
you gotta promise me
that you'll do it.
I'm going to do what's best
for your daughter, Mr. Reyes.
Yeah, but after midnight,
she's an adult.
Which means the decision
becomes hers.
Now, I can already see...
Mr. Reyes...
No, it's all gonna be
about her golf.
It's-it's the great
love of her life.
Legally, things may change
because of the birthday
but emotionally,
she's still just a kid.
She is too young...
realize...
that she's mortal.
If this were your daughter...
Lynn...
Lucy Reyes-- do you have
the biopsy results yet?
Just got off the
phone th the lab--
they're running behind.
Ok, I need to book
an O.R. before midnight
in case I need to do
an arm amputation.
I'll see what I can do.
No, no, see-see-e isn't gonna work.
Must be fore midnight,
and ll the lab
I needed those results yesterday.
Got it.
(beeping)
I got six hours to save her arm.
Lunch?
Uh, for the gator.
Ryan Whitten's foot--
If the foot's out of the gator,
why am I still looking at that.
Fish and Wildlife
have to come get it.
Make sure it's not tagged
or protected or something.
Well, they better hurry
before Chatty Kathy
makes herself a belt
and a new pair of pumps.
(giggling)
Where you headed?
Uh...
Well, Ry's CT was clear,
so I'm gonna update his wife.
(sighs)
're so not making it
to that concert, are we?
At this pot, not likely.
Best show you ever saw?
Hmm, Chili Peppers.
Drove all day to see
them in Tallahassee.
Daft Punk Lollapaoza.
Grant Park when I was
at the University of Chicago.
Head bouncing, hands in t air
all sweaty
fr the humidity. What?
Oh, yeah.
Hi, Kathy.
PROCTOR:
I got your page.
I have a problem.
You have my bike.
Oh, I figured if
repetitive motion
works for you,
I'm willing to give it a try.
This about the golfer girl?
I have exactly five hours
and 44 minutes
to decide whether or not
to amputate Lucy Reyes' arm.
You started debriding?
I don't want to cut
too much tissue
without knowing how deep
the infection's spread
That's all you can do.
Yeah, but Lucy
turns at midnight.
So, up until that point,
the medical decisions
rest with her dad.
But once that clock
strikes 12:00...
It's up to Lucy.
Yeah, and her dad's afraid
she's gonna wait too long
to make the call.
So, in the meantime,
I have to figure out
what I can do
to save her life, her arm,
and a relationship
with her father.
Give me the bike.
Really?
You want my help,
give me the bi.
I assume you've got her started
on broad-spectrum antibiotics.
Yeah, from the moment
she was diagnosed.
But it doesn't seem
to be slowing the infection.
Any sign of lactic acid
Came back normal.
Good.
That points away from sepsis.
You should get hold of a
near-infrared spectroscope.
Would that work?
I've only heard of them being
used to check brain function
through the skull.
Can also measure O2 levels
in deep tissue.
You'll be able to see where
and how much of Lucy's arm
is still getting oxygen,
and how much more tissue
to debride.
That's right.
That's the bike.
(pager beeping)
And that's my O.R.
ready for OT reattachment.
Hey, thanks.
"Hope for the best,
prepare for the worst."
Smart lady.
She also used to say,
"Put things back
where you found them."
Nice work on his femoral artery.
I managed to stop the bleeding.
Looks like our dinner's
become breakfast.
Foot's ready for replant.
Keep it on ice.
Ryan's artery isn't
supplying blood
to his lower leg.
Leaving us nothing
to attach the foot to.
(pager beeping)
It'll merely delay things
until we do a bypass procedure.
Which, unfortunately,
will have to wait.
I have an emergency aortic
transection to attend to.
Torn aorta trumps
severed foot every time.
Only for an hour or so.
Now what?
What if the leg's not viable
in an hour or so?
Ever read Frankenstein?
I saw Young Frankenstein.
Close enough.
We're gonna need surgical
tubing and vascular loops.
I'm not sure I follow you.
We're gonna run blood through
the tube to his lower leg
until Dr. Sable can
do a formal repair.
External bypass.
That's like "Franken-leg."
Franken-sort-of.
Vanessa?
How's Ryan?
He's doing well.
Uh, his chest CT came back clear
and now he's up in the O.R.,
ready for his
foot reattachment surgery.
(sighing):
Thank God.
Uh, listen,
I wanted to say sorry
for the little fight
Elroy and I had.
We've um, never really
seen eye-to-eye.
Yeah, I-I got that.
Brad's been such a saint,
keeping Elroy
from driving me nuts.
Brad?
Mr. Dalton?
Wake up.
What?
Can you stand up?
Wait, what's wrong with him?
What is this?
You got a bump back here.
Did he hit his head?
VANESSA: I don't know.
He didn't mention anything.
I need a gurney out here!
If I'd have known
there was a bed involved,
I would've brought my own
blankie and stuffed animal.
I'm gonna take...
I'm gonna take a little nap.
No. No, no.
You stay with me, Brad.
Okay.
Okay?
How did you end up
with that bump on your head?
(machine whirring)
Gator wrestling.
Huh.
I showed that thing who's boss.
ZAMBRANO:
Do you remember blacking out?
(over intercom):
Now that you mention it,
I do remember
having a little headache.
But it... it was no big deal.
ZAMBRANO:
Tough guy, huh?
I am tough.
I'm sweet though.
Hey, Doc?
Yeah.
Anybody ever propose to you
in this thing?
Uh, happens at least
once a week.
He's starting to herniate
his brain.
Call Dr. Chung
in Neurosurge.
I bet we could make it work.
I prob...
I probably should
get you a little cup of soup.
(monitor beeping rapidly)
Brad?!
Brad? Brad!
Stay with me. Brad!
He's posturing.
Get me a crash cart
and burr hole kit.
Hurry!
CHUNG:
I managed to evacuate the clog,
but there's massive
brain injury.
ZAMBRANO:
Come on, Brad, don't give up.
Keep fighting.
CHUNG: I'm sorry to say,
you're asking a lot.
♪ All in one day ♪
(sighs)
♪ I learned your name
and fell in love ♪
♪ And never saw you again ♪
(flatline beeping)
♪ All in one day ♪
(sighing)
CHUNG:
I'm sorry.
There was too much damage.
(flatline beeping)
♪ All in one day ♪
♪ I drove you home ♪
♪ Sat out in the car all alone ♪
♪ And thought about things
we'd talk about ♪
♪ Later on the phone ♪
♪ Then I went back to my house ♪
♪ Packed up my things ♪
♪ And moved away ♪
Your friend Brad suffered what
we call an epidural hematoma.
What, uh...
That's a delayed bleed
in the skull
caused by hitting his head.
We tried to relieve
the pressure, but...
he didn't make it.
He didn't make it?
He died?
We got to him too late.
I'm sorry.
What?
He-he-he was just
totally fine.
I mean, he didn't complain
of a headache or nothing.
VANESSA:
I can't believe this.
I mean, he was-he was
just standing right here.
I'll be back
to check on you both
when I have some news on Ryan.
♪ I know who you are ♪
♪ All in one day ♪
♪ All in one day... ♪
♪ I hold your name
and live in love ♪
♪ While I never
see you again. ♪
What's that?
All right,
we're gonna need a scalpel
and, uh, Lidocaine with epi.
LUCY:
Wh-what are you doing?
I'm cutting away
some of the infected tissue,
try and stop the infection
from spreading.
Hopefully this will
buy us some time
until we can get into an O.R.
Wait, an O.R.?
I can do a full
debridement there
and, uh, and I can cut deeper.
You're gonna feel some pressure.
I want you to let me know
if you feel any pain.
My dad-- has he been
telling you to amputate?
Just trying to make sure
we don't let this thing
get into your blood.
Yeah, but he's not the one
that has to live with
the decision, I am.
I've wanted to be
on the Stanford golf team for...
since I was, like,
ten years old.
I just don't understand it.
I should be able
to make my own decision, okay?
Lucy...
I mean, one hour from now,
on one side of a second,
my dad is in charge
and on the other, I am.
I mean, what changes
in that one second?
You know, I-I don't know.
But we're gonna keep fighting so
we don't ever have to get there.
All right?
Yeah.
(sighing)
How are we doing
on Ryan's popliteal artery?
Tying off the last
suture right now.
Good.
This should restore
circulation to his foot.
Let's give it a try.
Blood seems to be flowing.
Yeah.
And the leg is pinking up.
This is amazing.
Like nothing they teach
you in med school.
Doesn't seem to be any leakage.
That's a nice job.
(bad Austrian accent):
Zame to you, Herr Fronkenshteen.
(chuckles)
Teri Garr, Young Frankenstein.
I prefer the classics.
Boris Karloff?
The Munsters.
(chuckles)
You can take Ryan to ICU.
I'll see if I can
track down Dr. Sable.
You did your own bypass.
PROCTOR:
The only asset more valuable
in the army than
speed is creativity.
Hmm, I like a man
with imagination.
It's not bad.
The shunt is crude
but clearly effective.
Are we good for reattachment?
I'm all yours.
Excellent.
Of course, I'll
need you to assist.
I'd hate to mess with
your shunt without you.
My crude shunt.
No slight.
I was just hoping you
wouldn't proceed without me.
I've been proceeding
without you for my entire life.
In fact, if I'd
waited any longer,
the chance
of reattaching the foot
would've been made much worse.
Hmm.
You know, I don't think...
I don't think
we're gonna make breakfast.
We won't make it out in time?
No, it's not that.
It's, um...
You're more me than I am,
if that makes sense.
And, uh, as much as
I quite like the idea
of dating myself,
it's a little weird.
So, where does that leave us?
You're just gonna have to
wait for me to ask you out.
Dr. Deleo, it's
getting late.
I'm aware of that,
Mr. Reyes.
My O.R. time got pushed.
What does that mean?
You promised me.
No, no, no, what I promised you, sir,
is that I would do
everything I could
to save your daughter's life.
He's not taking my arm, Dad.
Lucy, I'm sorry
but this is not about
golf or Stanford anymore.
This is your life.
I know that.
Now, you have always
pushed yourself
to be the best at everything,
you are so strong, but
you're not invincible.
What are you gonna do?
Yeah, what?
I'm taking her to surgery.
Let get her arm on an arm board
and prepped with Betadine.
Hang another bag
of antibiotics.
The room's ready for you,
Doctor.
Dr. Deleo?
Everyone just stop.
You're running out of time.
(alarm beeping)
What is that?
Happy Birthday, Lucy.
(sighs)
I knew you were on my side.
Hey, of course I'm on your side.
Which is why I have to tell you
that we need
to amputate your arm.
I thought you'd try to save
my arm no matter what.
I did.
But if we amputate,
you can have a long
and rewarding life.
But if we don't,
there's a chance that
that infection will
spread, and once it does,
you will die.
Why can't you try
the debriding thing first?
I don't care
how much you cut out.
Listen, Lucy...
No, I don't get it.
If you thought I should
amputate, why did you wait?
Because I wanted this
to be your decision.
Not one you can blame on your
dad for the rest of your life.
So it's all up to me now.
So,
what'll it be?
Heard about your patient, Brad.
I'm sorry.
He offered me soup.
You know why getting
The Black Eyed Peas
tickets made me so happy?
I just want one night where
the weight of life and death
isn't hanging in the balance,
and I'm...
Singing out loud?
Yeah.
Under e stars,
not a care in the world.
(door opens)
Let's go, Doctors.
I'm ready.
Let's reattach the foot.
I need some singing.
♪ ♪
Is she okay?
Lucy did well.
Oh, my God,
you didn't do it, did you?
You let her decide
even after I begged you...
Mr. Reyes.
Luce, Luce, sweetie,
I'm right here.
You did it?
She did it.
It was her call.
My baby girl.
She's a fighter.
Yeah, she is.
She never...
she never ever gives up.
Okay.
Luckily, we were able
to save her shoulder
to make it easier
for fitting a prosthetic arm.
(gentle melody begins playing)
ELROY:
Soup from, uh,
from the health food place.
♪ My tired brown eyes ♪
Thanks.
♪ And these bad jokes,
that's all I've go♪
♪ Ah, ah, ah. ♪
Have you ever heard
of the luminescent
jellyfish off Key Largo?
No.
It's migration season.
The surf just glows.
If we left now,
we could be on the beach
while it was still dark
and get breakfast
on the way back.
Are you asking me out?
I am, yes.
How unexpected.
I'm going to have to think about it.
Really?
Well, it's just so sudden.
I'm worried you might
be moving a little fast.
(elevator bell dings)
(elevator doors opening)
I'll drive.
No, you won't.
You won't buy
breakfast, either.
(elevator bell dings)
(siren wails,
indistinct chatter)
DELEO:
Right. Work it. Own it.
WARREN: Work it!
DELEO: Own it!
(both humming along to "I Gotta
Feeling" playing on radio)
(Zambrano laughing) ♪ That
tonight's gonna be a good night ♪
Oh, my God.
What are you guys doing?
We know you didn't
get too to the Peas, so...
♪ A good, good night ♪
...we brought the Peas to you.
(laughs):
What?
♪ That tonight's gonna be ♪
♪ Ah, you guys.
♪ A good night ♪
♪ That night's gonna be ♪
It's warm.
Well, give me a break.
It's 3:00 a.m.
It's all I could
get my hands on.
Well, I guess warm beer
is better than no beer, right?
I raided the vending machine.
HM Ding Dongs?
Gummi worms?
Sure.
♪ That tonight's gonna be a
good night ♪ (chuckling)
And then, there was singing.
♪ Tonight's gonna be
a good, good night ♪
(volume increases)
♪ I gotta feeling ♪
♪ Whoo-hoo ♪
Come on!
(all singing along):
That tonight's gonna be ♪
♪ A Gd night ♪
♪ That tonight's
gonna be a good night ♪
♪ That tonight's gonna be
a good, good night ♪
♪ Tonight the night ♪ Oh.
♪ Let's live it up ♪
Here it is.
♪ I got my money ♪
♪ Let's spend it up ♪
♪ Go out and smash it ♪
♪ Like, oh, my God ♪
♪ Jump off that sofa ♪
♪ Let's get, get off ♪
♪ I know that we'll have
a ball if we ♪
♪ Get down and go out
and just Le it all ♪
What is this?
♪ I feel stressed out,
I wanna let it go ♪
♪ Let's go way out, spaced out
and losing all control ♪
Whoo!
♪ Ooh-hoo ♪
♪ That tonight's
gonna be a good night ♪
♪ That tonight's gonna be
a good, good night... ♪
Sync by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com