Subtitled by tsunami7
Quality checked by champloofan, Ebert, lookupinthesky, RacerX & whirlybird
Teacher, come here! / What is it? / They're fighting.
Move, move. Please stop this!
Calm down. What's wrong? Why are you acting like this?
What is this going to accomplish?
What are you gonna do?
Can you tell us?! / Please stop it!
Teacher, you're not in this. Get outta here!
Please stop!
Am I in this now?
Teacher...
I want your tongue. / You want my tongue? / Um.
Tell me where I'm licking you.
I can't. You're so good.
This is getting your dick all hard. / Because you make it feel so good.
Get naked. / [inaudible] / You get naked as well.
You've gotten all hard...
Teacher, this is so fucking hot.
I'll suck you too! / Ah, teacher, that feels good.
Me too. Me too. / You want me to suck your dick? / Um.
It tastes good! / Really? / Um.
Say, your teacher would like to be pleasured too but... / Is that so?
Well?
Wanna see something? / Yes. / How about my tits? / Yes.
So hot...
Feel them...
Okay. / I want them felt. / So big...
Don't you wanna feel and lick them? / Yes. / Can we? / You sure can.
Your face is so pretty...
Well? Does sucking your teacher's tits feel good?
It feels good to me.
Suck them. Suck on my tits.
Feel them.
Do you wanna get more intimate? / Yes.
Go for it.
This is so hot!
Does it feel good here teacher?
Yes, rub my clit-chan.
I want you to touch it directly. / Directly? / Um.
Inside my panties...
Take them off of me.
Teacher, it's very beautiful.
Lick your teacher's clit-chan.
Can I? / Yes, lick it.
Watch me.
I'm licking the entrance.
Can I finger you?
I'm gonna cum! I'm gonna cum!
What's wrong?
You want me to touch you?
Can I put your dick in me? / I would like that.
Watch it go in, okay?
I'm cumming! I'm cumming! I'm cum-mi-i-i-ing~!
I can't go on! / You can't? / Um.
You can cum! Give me a big load! / Where? / On my face.
Really? / Cum for me!
Asami [inaudible]
Oh yeah! / Here? / It feels really good!