THIS BELONG TO JAVRAPESUB.COM
Wait a second..wait, wait ..
Let's come together..
Are you leaving? | Yes..
Because i already finished my training, from today i'll work by myself...
Huh? That a big responsibility..
Yes.. but Keiko good at cooking too..
I think you would've become a good mother..
Thanks, I'll tell your insurance on my office..
oh..Im thankful..
Ok then ,lets go..
Yes..
Please be careful because its still hot..
Are you okay?
Im sorry..
Im sorry, here..
Is it good?
My father love fishing..
I forced to eat the fish that he catch..
He said..
Swallow it. that only tiny fish bone
Oi dad...
It just a tiny fish bone, swallow it..
Let me replace this..
This is a beatiful vase..
Do you like hydrangea?
Before i came here..
Someone loves to planting hydrangea..
May i borrow this?
I'll take it back tomorrow..
Ahh...
I'm sorry..
Ahhh..
This vase belong to my mother, this is priceless..
Oi dad ..
The vase is broken..
Your mother?
What must i do?
I'm really sorry..
No, this vase is very expensive..
This was made by famous artist in Shouki Era..
I see..
It seems the company won't cover such a situations..
What happened?
No..
Its nothing..
I'm just thinking, if i break something..
What will happen?
I see..
I'll ask this problem to boss..
Yes...
Hmm..
Its time to get back to work..
I understand..
Yes, see you..
Where is my father ?
What?
Because I can't find him, after i go to bathroom..
Where does he go again?
I was asking the neighbour, someone saw him at the bus stop..
Ehh....
Oi dad..
Please don't go anywhere without tell anybody..
I'm looking for your mother..
See,you understand, right?
What?
Thats why please tell him this is the right thing..
Yes..
How's your day?
Work to help people..
Yes. not bad..
What about the talks on the phone?
You better talk to your head company about the insurance..
You're right..
Breaking things, that happen sometimes..
Sometimes that things are to expensive, over million ..
It can be done, the insurance cover such a situations..
Insurance holders can work quiet and comfortable..
You're right
Good morning..
When i wake up..
He was gone again...
I'll find him,,
Its okay..
He will find his way home..
Don't do that..
What are you doing?
Why you wont listen to my instruction?
Its not like that..
After you broke that vase, dad's act so weird..
If you not listen to my instruction..
You must replace the vase..
What?
The price over a million..
Careless with people's stuff..
Now I can call the police if i want..
Its not like that..
That's a big problem,right?
Thats why..
Now listen to me..
Stop it !!
You are clean. aren't you?
As a replace..
Pay with your body !
Think about it...
Wait..No..
Why? Just once..
No..Never !!
Then bring me one million..
Thats..
Just a while..
No way !!
No.. No !!
Uhhh !!
No...
Don't !
No..
Why? Stick out your tongue !
Besides, you dont have that much money,right?
Then..Pay with your body..
No..
Stop it !
Move your hands..
No way !
You have a sexy body..
Ahhh !!
You like to be dirty like this, right?
Then..
You like it ,right?
I'll put this out..
No.. Noo !!
Spread your legs..
Show me your pussy !
Move your hand
Smell's good..
So lewd..
No way !!
I'll take this off, right?
Then..
You will enjoy it immediately..
I enjoyed it too..
No..
Move your hands..
Come on..
Let me see..
Show it to me !
What a sexy pussy !
Move your hands 1
How's my licking, feels good right?
No..
Ahhhh !!
Stop it !
Stop it !!
I wanna know what's inside..
What's wrong with that hand?
How its feel?
You like it,right?
Come on..
Look..
Good,right?
You like this, right?
It's wet inside..
I know it, when i see your face..
I know this feels good..
You can feel it,right?
Cause I know about your body..
Come on !
No..
Thats..
Take this off!
Strip off !!
Take this skirt off!
Like this..
No..
Open it up !
I really want to see your pussy..
No way !!
Come on show me more !!
Come on ..Bend over..
Can you suck my dick?
Come on..
No..
No way..
Just like this..
Come on !!
You have no money, so pay with your body..
Come on..
Come on, do it..
Come on, enjoy it..
You want it,right
You like this, right?
Come on !
Come on !!
Come on, come on !
Suck it !
Come on !
No..
Let me do it !
You better give up !!
Hey..
My dick already inside..
Its good, right?
No..
My dick..
How's that feel?
Come on !!
Enjoy it..
Come on !
My dick are so wet inside your pussy ..
No..
Don't pretending you don't like it ..
Its feels so good !!
You feels so great, right?
Your pussy feels so amazing !!
No way !
No..
Come on..
You often to have sex, don't you?
Ahh..Your pussy,,
Come on !
Come on..
Bend over, please..
No..
Aaahhh~
Feels so good inside ..
Dont !
Look at here..
I wanna taste everything you have ..
Why?
Show me your face..
Your face seem enjoyed it, dont you?
Dont !
Come on..
Your pussy so amazing tight..
Ahh..Im gonna cum !
Ahh.. I almost cumming !!
This body feels so great..
Im gonna cum..
I'm cumming !
You should come tomorrow..
Because from now, you must follow my instructions..
You're married, right?
If you're not coming..
I'll tell your husband about what we are doing now..
I'm home..
Nurse..
Today i got so many fish..
The price is over a million..
After you broke that vase, dad's act so weird..
As a replace..
Pay with your body..
No.. No way !!
Just a while..
Let me do it..
You should come tomorrow..
If you not coming..
I'll tell your husband about what we are doing now..
Nurse..
Come on..
Put that together..
Nurse..
My underwear..
Yes..Right now..
Wait a sec..
Follow me..
What is this?
You don't know?
Put it inside ere..
No..
Nurse...
My underwear..
Come on..
oyaji no pantsu kaete koi yo
Go change my dad's underwear..
Don't get caught by dad, don't be noisy..
Then..Let me clean you
Nurse..
What's wrong?
No,its nothing..
Are you okay?
Are you tired?
Come here, lie down please..
Nurse..
I bought you this perfume..
Why you don't use it?
No..
I knew it nurse..
You smells like bath soap..
Make me satisfy,please ..
Nurse..
Nurse...
Let me lick you,please
What?
Yes..
Get above me..
Come here..
Nurse..
Turn your back..
Vib..vibrator...
You wearing this thing..
You must be lonely..
Harder..
More hard..
Nurse..
You must put on that vibrator until tomorrow..
Always put on..
Stop it, please !!
Wait..
Wait !!
Are you wet enough?
My husband sleep upstairs..
If you don't make any noise, we will be okay, right?
I found it on the internet..
This stuff..
The price is 2000 yen..
You already know it..
How could you?
But you..
You can't lives without this dick, right?
Its true, right?
What do you think ?
You are a helper..
This hard dick..
Is that you must taking care ..
Come on..
Be ready to suck it..
Open up your mouth !
Until more deep..
Lick that balls !
Come on..
Stick out your tongue more !
Lick it more !
My dick getting hard..
Like that, all way down..
Come on..
Use your hand..
Too sensitive..
Come on work it out..
Right there..
Lick all of it..
What's wrong ?
Look at here..
Ahh..I'm cumming ..
Open your mouth..
Because you won't back here tomorrow..
I take this back..
Yes..
Let me feel it more..
Right here?
Your boobs..
Are you embrassing?
Don't be ashame of your self..
Because I want to see you more..
You feels it more?
Take it off..
Show me..
Your nipples getting hard..
Hard like this..
Does that feels good?
You wanted more,right?
Come on..I want to see everything..
Women smells so good..
Bend over, show me your ass..
Come on.. This sexy ass, big and curvy..
Come on, makes me horny...
Bend over, show me more..
Feels good?
Move your hips..
Move it more..
If you wanted it more, shake your ass more..
You wanted more pleasure,right?
You want me to touch you,right?
From here?
Right here?
Like that..
Come on, make some dirty voice..
You are such a pervert girl..
Let it go..
You want me to help you cum, right?
Thats right ,you like it..
I will see deep inside..
Come on..
Let me see until deep inside your pink pussy..
Come on !
I wanna see deep inside..
You like to be seen, do you?
Cmon..You getting wet..
Come on !
Like this..
Hey..
Looks clearly..
Yes?
Your pussy looks clearly..
You see it,right?
Im fingering your pussy..
Feels good?
Then why yours become messy like this?
So amazing !!
Spread your legs more..
Spread your legs...
Spread your legs..
Come on..
Lick it..
You like it to suck it?
More a dirty sound..
Licks it pervertly..
Come on !
Licks it..
You want suck it, right?
Cmon..
You like it?
Come on..
This big dick,,
Cmon..Try to enjoy it more..
Suck like you want it more..
Ahh..Like that
Suck that deeper..
Alright..
Let me licks you..
Suck it more..
You suck it more....
Deeper..
Come on..Suck all way down
Your pussy so wet..
You want my dick,right?
You want to be treated like this, right?
Thats right, bend your ass over..
You really want it, don't you?
Come on.. How's that feel?
You like your ass being used ,right?
Come on !
Feels good? Let out your voice more..
Come on..
Move yourself..
So sexy, move yourself !
You're a bitch..
Feels good?
Feels good when you in control?
Shake your ass..
Show me that you enjoying it..
Show me more..
I want it deeper..
I wanna see..
Deep inside, Come on !
How's that feel?
Deep inside!
Feels good,right?
You sit on me..
Sit down..
Move your legs...
Ah..Like that..
So good..
Ahh.. so good !
You're so pervert..
Turn over..
Turns back, and move your body..
Come..Hold this..
Feels good, right?
My dick feels good, right?
How's that feel?
Say "Its feels good", Say it !
Feels good~
Thats right..
My dick is good, right?
Come on..Look at me..
Move it by yourself..
You wanted this dick, right?
How's that feel?
You are so lewd..
Its feels good?
Feels good?
Stick out your tongue..
Stick out your tongue !
Ahh..I'm cumming !!
Its time to go..
Hey darling..I left my stuff behind, you go ahead, i'll catch you later
oke..Then, I'm going ..
Bye..
THIS BELONG TO JAVRAPESUB.COM