Well done. Thanks. Good job!
Do your best in the next match!
Kirara, my life is on the line.
I'm cheering for you! I will not loose.
Hello.
It's me. In the next title match, won't you loose for us?
Ah.
Well, you see. The next match is... I'm sorry.
Kirara, Kojima... is dead.
It happened all of a sudden.
The day before the important match.
My very important boyfriend.
Was killed in the gym by someone.
He's got no enemies... WHY!?
Why, would this happen!?
The sadness of the gyms lost future fighting master,
Coupled with the promise of staying with him.
Crying over him. I was at a loss.
Uh, You're Kirara right?
Who are you?
What happened here,
I'm at a loss.
This is who I am.
Fighting Association Chairman Joe Oshima
Are you someone important from the tournament?
I'm so sorry that this has happened to Kojima.
No, no. Kirara...
No, this guy is in the worst predicament.
Thank you so much for caring.
Why would such a thing happen? I'm mortified.
But he's got no enemies.
Even thought the facts are right before our eyes,
The situation is quite intense now.
Please cheer up Kirara.
Without fail, without fail, the partner who killed Kojima. I will...
The, partner, who killed... You know who killed him?!
Please calm down. Don't tell me to calm down!
If you know who killed him then you know why he was killed!
It doesn't matter why he was killed it's unacceptable!
Positively, with all my might.
Understood.
Please calm down Kirara, I'll tell you everything.
Now, I finally learned the truth about Kojima's death.
Oshima said that,
The promoter told Kojima to take the fall in the title match.
Kojima was too serious so, ???
And the promoter hired someone to kill him.
If that's the reason that someone would be killed.
I didn't believe that lousy reason from the start.
However the stupid match fixing fighting association...
Planed to throw the title match.
As I listened puzzled to Oshima calmly tell me the story I didn't think he was lying.
As I listed further, the hatred for who killed him welled up.
The person who killed my darling will not be forgiven!
It's allowable to accept that reason.
It's very sad, but it's reality Kirara.
I was also involved with the underground.
However, we got our own rules.
Certainly, we will return the favor.
What should I do...
What do you mean Mr.Oshima? I want to do something! Let me help!
Tell me what to do!
Please calm down Kirara.
If we do something... because we're professionals.
There's nothing more you need to do.
Mr.Oshima, don't turn away from me. There's nothing to do now, I get it.
But after that, tell me!
Alright Kirara.
From one professional to another you see, listen up.
Are you prepared?
Ready? Yea, I'm more than ready! Hurry up and tell me!
No police, no lawyers.
We've got project specialists to resolve the matter.
See, I'm here so, I've got lots of connections.
So, please leave it to me. I won't so anything strange.
A secret organization.
What do you mean? If that's true please introduce them to me. I want to do something!
Is that so? All by yourself?
I see.
What are you saying!? I'm serious!
I want use any power that I can.
Tell me, hey! Mr Oshima!
understood, I... have another business card.
Crackdown Enforcement Officer Joe Oshima
Mr.Oshima is a member of the secret organization.
I don't know... it's incomprehensible!
Tell me, What are you?
That business card says it all.
I have confidence in the secret organization.
It would please me to get help from you.
Well, I have an idea of who did this.
They know that I know.
I'm in a between a rock and a hard place.
Mr.Oshima Please tell me!
Give me the knowledge I need.
You know it's a secret organization.
What are you doing!? Stop that.
My lover should be my partner right?
Of course if you don't, the info you need...
Perhaps is a gun!?
Which I can use freely.
You just told me that you want to join.
Because I can't act yet, I'll have you do it.
Let's talk to each other.
You see, You've got a secret that you can't tell anyone!
Shall we die with him!?
Alright get up, Stand!
no...
Don't move.
Very nice.
You should take them off. Everything.
Got it. NOW, take it all off!
Respond.
Alright.
Go.
Don't try anything.
If you try anything... Bang!
Nice panties.
Got it!?
Hurry.
I'm hard already!
Turn around.
NO, no.
Let's make it better.
I don't even need a gun to kill you, I could use my hands. Got it?
OK, Open your mouth.
Open.
No, Open! From now on you're my lover. Let's start acting like it!
Suck!
Work with me! Come on Suck!
Alright... next take your bra off.
Come on. Take it off!
Remove it!
Wonderful.
Your boyfriend should have been very happy!
What a hot body.
Don't touch me!
That's right.
You'll give it up. NO! What!?
Hey, look here. Ready for more?
No way! No!
Shut up! Don't tell me no!
Come on.
Open up.
More.
Give it to me!
Don't be humiliated.
It's for you, and for him.
Gimme more.
Look a me, Look!
Come on, come on, come on!
Do it!
Come on.
Do more, now.
More.
I said more!
Are you enjoying it?
On your knees.
Open up.
Come on, open it.
Hows that? Huh? You want more don't you?
Suck it more!
Do it!
Stick your tongue out, out now!
That's it.
Come on.
Remember what I said, let's go.
I want you to use what you got ok.
Squeeze it, now!
Good.
Get up now, quickly!
More, yea. More!
I'm gonna do it, yea.
Put your shoulder down.
You're ready.
Look interested.
Do it.
Wonderful, this hot body.
Now I want you to lye down, lye down.
Yea, come here.
Open your legs, look here.
Just right.
So nasty.
Open up for me.
After Mr.Oshima raped me at gunpoint.
I Joined and got myself a gun!
Now I can do anything.
Having learned well, nothing scares me now!
A memorable place, He trained so much here.
He was a great guy. Very proud of himself.
I came ere looking for the enemy.
Look what we have here. Stupid bitch. Oh yea.
What!? What the hell?!
Let go! Let me go!
You, you don't know anything.
You heard me! Let me go!
It's your fault that bastard was killed.
It's your fault we have no matches.
It's your fault we got no money.
Hey, wait, what are you saying!? I don't get it!?
What, matches, money, what do you mean?!
Tell me now!
What do you mean!?
mumble, mumble, mumble.
Keep quiet.
no, no, NO!
no, no, STOP!
NO!
Don't touch ME!
No, no, Stop it!
Look at that. No, NO!
Hold on.
It's all your fault.
You know it feels good. NO!
Enjoying it yet?
Enjoy it, it's all your fault.
Have fun.
Looks like fun.
mumble, mumble.
What is it?
Feels good right?
Real good.
Want more?
Seems you love it. NO!
NO!
Don't!
Let's turn it up.
No! Stop it!
Feels good huh?
Spread em.
That's the spot.
No, What are... No!
What, NO!
No, no, no, NO!
Open up!
No, no, NO!
Hey, you like it! NO!
Ah, it feels so good.
No, NO!
NO! We're not done with you.
mumble, mumble.
Ah, that's it! It's your fault.
Hey, stop resisting.
No! NO!
Stop!
Don't you tell us.
Hey, come on!
Suck it!
No, NO!
Stick your tiongue out! NO!
Now! NO!
Do it! Now!
Come on! NO!
no, no, no, NO!
Yea, that was good. I wanna try.
Ah, that's it! Great!
You happy? You're the bad one!
It's your fault.
But, I didn't.... Do anything... no.
mumble, mumble.
What is it? Thank you...
What's the matter?
Kirara! Are you alright?
What happened!? Was it him?
So why did Kirara...?
Just feeling nostalgic.
Nostalgic?
Where your boyfriend died?
Anyway... today...
You should go home... your bag?
Oh! My bag. I got it!
Why the hell do you have a gun!?
So you know who as here today!?
Mr.Kuro this is where Kojima was shot right?
But if that's the case...
You, have a gun!?
Who do you think?
Where'd you get it!? What are you talking about?
So you know...
If you know...
We have to kill you. Yea.
Tells us, now! No!
What the hell are you saying!? I...
I only wanted to...
You wanna die?
Stop it, Stop it!
You were here with Kojima!?
No way!? Well...
Dis she...?
Shoot him...?
With this gun...?
This is the one... NO!
We know now!
Let's begin! NO!
Come on don't resist. NO!
Do it!
Let's have fun.
No, NO!
You wanted it.
Don't resist.
Listen close.
Do it!
Got it?
What's wrong, carry on!
Look at that dirty pussy!
Open up!
What is it? You know... Come on!
Tell us everything!
I don' know!
You don't know huh?
Looks like you're having fun. NO!
No, NO!
Do it or else.
no, NO!
Don't make it difficult.
When shall we kill you?
Really, how far shall we go?
Ah, let's have a looky here. NO!
What is it?
You like it?
Say something! NO!
Say it!
Your ours.
Such a pretty face, huh?
No I don't.
Stop, stop, stop, STOP IT!
No, no, NO!
Get down.
Come, work with us. This way!
No, no. Huh!?
You know what we want.
Rather than kill you we'll just please ourselves. Feeling good!
Do it! Come on, don't make it hard on us.
How's that feel huh?
Do it right!
You want it.
Yea, all of it!
I'll teach your pussy a thing or two.
This way.
Do it!
Come on!
It's all your fault.
You do it too well.
Ah, that feels good.
You can take it.
Hey, get up now.
Come here.
Do it!
You can do it.
You could fool anyone.
She's such a slut.
Do it right!
More!
Take it!
Jerk it!
Come on, do it.
Take mine too.
Yea. Yea, that's it.
Hey, stick your tongue out!
Don't stop, do it!
Scared?
Don't be afraid.
Could be worse.
Hey, calm down.
Eat the DICK!
Gimme that pussy! NO!
No, no, no, NO!
NO!
No! Open up!
No, NO! Don't stop now.
Yea, that's it.
We won't kill you. Just please you...
I'm gonna cum.
You'll get it.
Look.
No, no..
We'll just enjoy you.
Say something, say it! NO!
See!
Still won't say it?
Look here.
Have something to say? What are you hiding?
Let's have fun.
Hey.
mumble, mumble. Hey!
You can do more.
You can do it.
Hurry!
yea.
You can do more! Do it!
Do it. Come on!
Come on do it!
Say it. Say it!
You want us to kill you? Do it!
We'll give you more.
Hold the dick, come on grab it.
If you don't wanna die let us have fun!
What is it?
Come on, what's the matter? Hey.
There's another dick.
Hey, come on. What?
Look at it.
Lemme ask ya something...
Hey, yea.
Come on.
Come on. Hey! Come on.
I'm in!
Come on, huh?!
Here, come here.
Ass, now!
NO!
Hey.
Together now.
Move yourself!
Moar!
Hey, come on! Yea!
You feel good? Hey, look here. Come on.
Hey.
Open up.
Open more!
Hey!
Hey, Move it!
Yea!
Not done yet.
What's is it?
Nice and slow.
We might have to kill you.
Feels great.
She's got it. This is the last. Yea!
Squeeze it tight.
Very nice.
Feels great.
Hey
The last time you'll ever have sex. Hey!
No!
Say it! It feels good! It... is good... NO!
Don't say no! You know it's good. Come on!
Feels good.
You're the best. NO!
I'm gonna cum.
Oh! That's good.
Hows that?
Yea, the last time... you'll ever have sex...
Let's end it.
Hey, Tamaki.
I'll kill here alone.
You can leave. NO, I'll help ya!
It's alright, you can go!
Yea, but... Tamaki, go home! Got it, later.
So, what the hell do you know?
What... You know.
Mr.Oshima told me all about you.
I heard about you & that organization.
Are you joking, what the hell are you saying!?
So, someone here killed him!
I know that he didn't want to participate in the final fight.
That's why I'm here.
I see, but let's be honest.
It's just me and you so let's not worry about Mr.Oshima,
But he was right about you, very thoughtful.
Huh!? Why?!
I'm on your side!
I don't what's what now.
Quickly, I gotta get them now!
Oh, what the hell!?
You're the one!
I lost a ton of money! I lost more than that!
That bastard didn't give us the correct info!
Oh, huh?
Ouch.
Where the...
You know well.
Hey you! You're the one! Who shot them!?
Why the hell are you really here?
Say something. Tell us!
Shut up! Bring the boss out!
WTF!? We'll fucking kill you!
Don't get too excited.
Yea I guess.
Sorry fellas, I was just...
I do anything.
What's she saying? Do anything?
Don't believe you! Probably lying anyway...
At least you can undo the handcuffs.
I can't do anything if I can 't move.
So you, will do anything?
What will you do?
Careful!
Be careful, there's no need.
Besides, I've got an idea.
It might save your life.
Let's open it! Feels good.
Looks great!
Open up! Come here!
You try anything and your dead!
Hurry up and get them off!
That feels great!
Don't forget about me. Yea, him too!
Feels too good.
Let's get them out.
Me, first. No, Me.
Yea, that's great!
You really had a great idea!
She's really good. I want some too.
Oh, feels great!
That's it!
I'll get it out too.
She does it well.
Feels... so good!
Suck me off too!
Ah, feels good.
Feels good right?
From the young lady.
I'm waiting.
Good, oh! So good!
So good.
Suck me too!
Tasty dick? Mines the best!
Hey, wait... don't forget about me.
Feels good.
Why so skilled. I'm sure she gets around.
Should be happy with all these dicks!
Look at me!
She looks happy.
It's be nice if she gave it all up.
But feels so good!
You can do them both.
Such great tits!
Come here, gimme.
Feels good.
Oh, I'm gonna cum. Already!?
I'm gonna cum!
I'm gonna come on your tits!
Such a wonderful rack!
Hey... mumble, mumble.
Oh, I'm gonna cum!
That's a lotta cum! There's more!
Suck it.
Oh, I'm... gonna cum!
I'm gonna cum!
Here cums!
Gonna cum... here it cums!
She's great! Yea, that was awesome! Hey, WTF!?
Get in!
Hey, What are you doing!? Stop it. Don't shoot!
It was unexpected that Kuroda was killed.
Well we got her, Mr. Agawa, from now...
We'll let our geeky Tamaki do it. Nah, not yet.
Our star is without a girlfriend.
He's a bit too serious so he can't promote.
Tamaki go study! OK!
We'll have you take care of a few things Tamaki.
Compared to now, there's much more on the other side.
Just like gambling!
Hey what are you doing!?
YOU!?
How the hell did you get here!?
That's... Kirara isn't it?
She's look wonderful. Shit! Oshima!
You're the one...
Not so loud.
Mr.Oshima...
It's alright if I fuck her before we kill her right?
That's why your here after all, isn't it?
Hey, BITCH! Why try thing's you're not supposed to!?
Don't make us!
What ever you like... Hey, Tamaki you too!
She looks delicious doesn't she Tamaki?
She likes it doesn't you Kirara?
She's looks cute.
Let's be cautious.
Work with us now.
Hey, let's get you out of this.
You can't escape.
Tamaki, watch this.
Open up.
So wet! What a beautiful pussy!
It's alright Kirara.
So cute.
I'll touch it a bit.
Look at them, watch them please you.
What's the matter? Huh!?
What is it?
What's up!?
Have a look at that! Well done Kirara.
You're pussy must feel great!
Stick it out! Come on, OUT!
Look at that asshole!
Looks good!
Wiggle, yea.
How about that? Do it!
What shall we do?
Get up! Where you goin?
That's the look.
She's great!
You're dripping wet.
It's not enough. Not enough for you huh!?
No, no!
Look closely.
Hows that? You like a lad to eat you out!?
The lads good huh? We hoped you'd like him.
Watch more!
NO!
No, no, no!
It's good you know it! Open up!
OPEN! OPEN!
Up! Gimme the ass now!
Some dick... you know you want hthe dick!
Open your mouth, hurry up!
Hey, come here.
Come on, do it!
Do it, do be lazy. Come on!
Eat this dick. Jerk it too! That's it.
Hey, that's it!
Come on, lets go.
Eat it, just like that.
EAT THE DICK!
Mr.Oshima, she's awesome!
Use your tongue!
Hows that? Speak up!
What's wrong, cat got your tongue?
On all fours!
Hows that? Smell the dick, smell it!
You know you want it. Open up, OPEN!
In order, do them both.
Look here, with those sad eyes!
Heartbreaking I know.
Use your hands too, use em.
I'm next, hey!
You can do more. Do it!
Don't act like you haven't done this before.
This, like this!
Like this... huh!?
Show me your face.
Look up. Yea that's it.
What a beauty!
You stinky of dick now.
Stick your tongue out. Hey, out now!
Give it a taste.
Havin' fun!? Feelin' good!?
Don't stop, not now.
You can do more!
Hey, you want the dick! open up!
Take it all!
Open more!
More, yea. Here comes more.
Yea, that's it.
Like this, yea that's it.
Can't get enough.
Can I get dibs?
He's gonna give it to you!
Show your face.
Take the dick, huh?
Hey, hey.
Sure feels good.
How regretful.
Yea, more of it. Come on!
Ah, that's the spirit!
Looking so good.
Whtcha doing, gimme that ass!
Never enough!
Sounds like your having fun! Really enjoying yourself!
Move it! Come on, MOVE!
Eat this dick.
Work that ass.
Not enough for you!?
Yea, come on.
You know it tastes good.
Deeper!
Lookin' cute, so cute!
Lift your ass, lift the ass!
Won't stand on your own?
Here, come here.
Mr. Oshimas turn.
Yea, that's it. SO GOOD! Feels great!
That's it. I'm so hard!
Mr.Oshima, this is AWESOME!
Looks good. Feels good? Yea, feels great!
Sorry, I'm next!
Hold on.
Put your back into it.
Suck it.
Yea, that's it.
This is fun. Yeas sure is.
You like the 2 of us watching!?
She takes the dick so well.
Look here, yea, like that.
Feels so good!
I'm gonna cum!
Open your mouth, open up.
You want more cum?
Gonna cum!
It's unfortunate but... you gotta die.
Yea... well, with this gun it'll look like natural. Ah.
I did it. Mr. Kojima & Mr.Kuroda...
It was allowable; to me & for you.
I must die! NO!
I... I...
Must parish.