AVC Sub-Thai, translated by The Forbidden
Published at AVCollectors.com only
- Is it really okay?
- trust me
- Have at least 2 hours
- Don't wake up halfway.
- I've never used it with sick people.
- Are you a demon?
Let's get started
Very much
- finally saw
- Yes - not just the chest
All of this is ours.
Listen, this is the secret between us.
Don't get caught.
Really cute
Ai Sayama
AVC Sub-Thai, translated by The Forbidden
Published at AVCollectors.com only
"Conspiracy to conquer the widowed mother"
One month before
This is 4 years.
Time passed very fast
- Thank you to the president for visiting.
- No, we are friendly.
I've been dating Akira's parents for a long time.
I saw him grow up since childhood.
But never thought that it would be so sensitive
Still young
Better then because the doctor
My husband has always recommended this place.
Akira is not strong.
Like his parents
What about the president's interest in buying a house?
Even though it's hard to decide.
But must refuse
I have a duty to protect my father's house.
It is also the husband's hometown.
Welcome
Akira is really lucky.
Who still has a wife who still loves him forever
Even though he left premature
What do you say? I shouldn't go on to say anything.
Thank you, Master.
Everyone always treats me gently.
He must definitely like
It's a really good woman.
It's hard to meet people like this.
I don't think I can live alone.
And what about your house?
I used to talk about this
But still, she didn't.
Show that you are not able to offer enough prices.
Wrong. .. It is impossible to buy with money.
4 years, she's all alone
Yes, there are no other houses in that area.
- look at this
- What
- Ya?
- I've been there for a long time.
- It's a good sleeping pill.
- and why take it
She has known me since her marriage.
So trust me
Sometimes she still falls asleep during treatment.
What are you going to do?
It's getting tired.
I will go back to you
I was jealous of you who had massage her frequently.
Okay, listen. We all want to try good things.
Everyone is getting older.
Why not find happiness for yourself?
Really speaking?
And this is also for Kotosan
If you can find happiness
How good is it
Wouldn't it be okay?
If you don't
I will do it alone
Old age, never waiting for anyone.
So i also
She will come here twice a month.
That will be our opportunity
And would you agree to take this strange medicine?
If i say good
She definitely eats
A month later
Kotasan
After this, is there enough time?
Want to try a firmer body massage
It's okay
Thank you for your suggestion.
So try drinking this.
it's good for you
It may cause a little sleepiness but there are no side effects.
got it
Kotasan
- Is it really okay?
- trust me
- Have at least 2 hours
- Don't wake up halfway.
- I used to use it with others and it's okay.
- Are you a demon?
Let's get started
Never mind
Very much
- It's very big
- better than I thought
- Breastfeeding
- I like it
- Yes
- Not just the chest
All of this is ours.
Listen, this is the secret between us.
Don't get caught.
- really cute
- Is this really true?
It's great
very pretty
It's so beautiful
- Great
- here is good
- So beautiful
- Very good.
Can't, then have to taste it.
I would like to taste some, not too much.
The ultimate hard nipple
- Feeling too?
- like sleeping deep
Hard nipples
Probably feel it
It's already wet
So greasy
- Great. - See here.
- Clitoris
Can't be patient
this is clearly crazy
Want to break out
Where do you look?
It's really beautiful
So cute
This nipple is pretty good.
This looks delicious too.
Must taste a little
Very good. Very good.
Where do you look
Where do you want to see?
- Great
- like never used at all
Koto-san has no new ones.
It was not used for 4 years.
- Thank you for the fact that Kotosan still looks smooth.
- Yes.
Can't wait
It's delicious
What is the ultimate size?
- It's beautiful
- Ng.
Thank you for the birth of Makoto-san.
so cute
Excellent
- that is cool
- If we try to stimulate it
Don't worry about it.
Oh, soft, squeezed, very playable.
Look ... really wonderful
Have you ever helped yourself?
Fall asleep
Come see this
- Go ahead
- here it is
you see
- It's very fit
- Very fit?
So tight
- very tight
- poke into
- gradually
- very tight, must be gradually
The best thing is to get started.
This hole is great.
Can't stand it.
- What's inside?
- Still fit?
- Inside is still fit
- also wet
Ultimate ... It's good like this.
Inside that ...
Must be done gradually
Put just one finger?
- Be patient... So try two fingers.
- Go ahead
Put two fingers away.
How is it.
It seems to be easier
At this hole it is wet.
- Did you wake up?
- Anyway, the medicine is definitely taken.
Then tell me
I think Yana should be taken.
Here is how Koto-san
- Great
- Look, you breathe up.
Doubt will like
With moan
-How is it? -It seems to respond.
- Start accelerating.
- Sure.
- Great
Jerky
This is
I do not want to believe that it is true.
Like still not feeling
Is it finished?
- Oh, your body should be ready.
- Let's start first
- How are you the first person?
- What is this?
All right.
Koto-san ... Can't resist it.
Please be anointed first.
Will be plugged in?
Cute little Goto-san
Already put
It went into the hole of Kotasan.
I'm in .. inside of this.
Very fit
Never met like this before
- Really
- I want to try some
This
It's really a masterpiece.
Is a woman of dreams
In the past, she was still lonely.
Next ... I wish
Try it. I will not forget your merit at this time.
The voice of Kotosan is very tempting.
Like so much ... well to hear her moan
- that is cool
- Want to rock
Top
- She is so cute
- hold it
Like this
It's super awesome.
This is
Can't wait to wait
I love it .. love like this
This is a very good thing.
Try with the mouth better.
How is my cock smelling
What is the taste?
What is the taste of this cock?
Too good
Felt like she was helping
- reacted
- Have symptoms?
- Great. I love it.
- Yes
No, I can't.
If you break in, what is it?
- Wait a moment
- Can you?
Come
How are you
- It looks very obscene.
- Now my eyes
My eyes .. what kind?
I like the back side. Please help.
Okay ... Okay.
Good
Catch up like this
Already put
Super
It's very fit
The way you said
- Dream come true
- Good.
Siao Chan
Super
Push up a bit
Move this way
Open your mouth more than this .. Let's try.
I hope you want
This is for women who keep refusing others.
Endured for many years
What is this size?
Love it
Sweating all over, so it looks really sexy.
Very good ... very good
First removed from the mouth
You can't make it before.
Siao .. Siew Wee
Very awesome
Very good ... very good
When he didn't do it for a long time like he couldn't
Will finish that soon
- I can't.
- Hurry up and finish.
- I will hurry to continue
- No
Very good
I'm happy
Neat
Got broken?
How are you
To die
Come on
Let her sit down
Come here ...
So drenched in this, definitely comfortable.
Entering Koto-san
- so
- Good stuff
Very good
Koto-san works very well.
If not bad
Very good .. What a great visit.
It looks like she is moving along too.
Do it without knowing it. Really good.
Slowly
It's very nasty
Super fit
- She has emotions in common.
- quite good
Really nice
Fit pussy
Can't wait to stop ...
See you willingly
Great
Must be like this
Koto-san, you have a dream.
Yes definitely
A lot easier to bet
Don't feel ... I will break
Cracked
Shivering
Try it out
- Overflowing
- sloppy
It's great
- so much
- Not yet awake
Really good
Really porn
It still runs out.
A lot
The water is set for 3 people
Is about to run out of time
5 minutes each, enough
Must be kept as a secret that we cooperate
Don't get caught.
Will do this forever
- Every 3 of us will meet
- to swarm her
- Okay ... to my eyes
- will break and wait a little
What about the medicine
Because in the past we used it all the time
Like this, it is hopeless
I still want to do it for a long time.
Really sad but without hope?
If you can find it again, I'm happy to pay.
My friend said it was hard to find.
But don't know when to find it
- Another glass
- can quit
I can't forget things
Can do with Kotosan
Don't want to give up like this
What would it be if we used general sleep medicine?
There is no guarantee that you will not wake up.
And how to take it?
If so, I went to Diasna.
I'll try myself
Will you try it yourself?
If that's okay, tell us too.
This is Akira Sang?
Fit, store and then meet
Thank you, President
Slowly look
- I will go to drink tea.
- No, I ...
- See it.
- Thank you very much
Koto-san also forgives.
I can't really help .. I can't really help.
This smell
Beautiful breasts
It is mine
Can't wait
Yeah right
Very beautiful .. very good
Can't stand it
Okay
How to be patient
Can't wait ... Koto-san
Can't do it at all
This body
This skin ... is mine
Can't do it at all
Koto Sang Dee?
Slowly .. gradually before
Great. I love it.
Would like to do this continuously
can not stop
I can not afford it anymore
Yeah
This is so soft.
Then the drug is gone
I don't have any excuses if you're really awake.
If she gets upset
Probably I sideways first
Who
How is it
Koto-san, I myself, Akira
Akira?
This is the past 4 years.
- How can Akira
- Unexpectedly
I come because I want to see you
Love you, Koto-san
- I love you
- Love
Akira, I miss you
Koto-san, I can't wait.
Lonely, no time without me
Want to meet all the time
I've always been lonely.
Akira
- is it good
- Akira
Great Akira
So good, Akira
Will be finished ... I finished
Kotasan
Akira ... the most sensitive
I love you
beloved
Take off again
good
Now, come here.
beloved
Kotasan
How about
beloved
The smell of love is not touched for a long time.
enjoy it
very like
Show her to see
My
Akira looks good.
The most beautiful, Koto
It happened unexpectedly, but he was able to survive.
Do not think she will believe that it is Akira
Even though it is unlikely
Whichever is, then follow the water.
Anyway, I think Akira is
Go in
I definitely don't stop.
It's because of the craziness
Kotasan water flowed so I couldn't believe it.
Show the real base out
Right here, right?
There ... continue to love you
I love it so much.
- Take it again, right?
-Akira take it again. I like it.
Super
That!
- darling .. the best
- Will you finish?
- will be finished
Arrange
A ... finished
Very tasty
This is very good.
- Really
- Yeah
It's great
It's good to be expected.
So great.
Akira
Kotasan
Can't, then ... will be broken already.
Can't get Akira
Put in me first
Go ahead
Will be crazy dead
Come here ... plug it in
Akira ... already entered
Aa Koto-san
I love the most.
Like me?
Like Akira san most
I also like Kotansan too.
Kotasan
It's great
Ultimate bet
- beloved
- no
good
beloved
Rocking perfectly
- so much
- I was so sick
- excelent
- Akira .. I will finish it.
- How?
- Akira, I can't.
Finished
beloved
Do you like it
good
beloved
I love it
ShoWo
Excellent .. It's so good.
That is very good.
- Is this?
- Yes.
- I like this posture?
- So good.
beloved
Another force ... strong.
Super .... dear
Aha .. will finish
Come here .. come to me
beloved
Super
delicious
Beautiful breasts
Super
Kotasan
Akira
no
Now back
Already put
Again
Nice
is it good
Koto-san during my absence
- Do not go back to anyone.
- It will not happen.
- Are you sure
- can swear
I have never done with anyone else.
Then how horny are you doing?
- do that
- Tell me how
I help myself with my finger
And then imagine that taking with you
Is this better? ... Is this better?
excellent
I always miss me
I'm so lonely
I am very happy
Baby, why do you leave me
- I'm sorry
- Do not leave me alone
Stay with me in this dream forever.
I will come every day
- Darling - will be broken
- will finish the same
Crack
Widow
beloved
Do you really do it?
Is the drug effective?
Sure?
Calmly speaking
Do you think you are Akira?
Yes i just try smooth
She truly believes that Akira is
Just a little
Listen here
Can you hear that is proof
She would have thought that she was dreaming.
beloved
Would think that Akira was a ghost
Beloved
Dreams ... to Akira
Really romantic
4 years ago, still dreaming of him
No ... I think it's strange.
How strange?
Is ... I mean
First of all ... drink a glass
But I'm not good at drinking.
Never mind .. drink a glass to relax
This is a dream. Koto-san
You are dreaming
Akira comes to her as promised.
I miss until I have come to find you in my dreams.
Akira
Yes .. Akira himself
Koto
- This set is it
- looks good
Okay, right?
Looks good
I can only talk to Akira in a dream.
That is what you understand.
See who is watching.
- No, I'm embarrassed
- Let him see.
No, Akira ... don't.
Akira
Never mind even though it's not a dream.
do not
When I said that it wasn't a dream?
Is that what you say? The filthy Kotans will die.
All of this has been done for me.
Why is the master silent?
Actually, I think you know
Drugs that use it will die.
Even though she was aware, but still dazed
Even though it's like a dream
But she has emotions
Why is Koto-san reaching out like that?
After losing her husband, no one else.
The body is not used to anyone.
When it was time to stop
At this time we have freed her.
We know more because changing drugs.
She wants anyway
But we use the name Akira to spoof only
Koto-san isn't that kind of person.
So I will test it.
Let's see if you were right about this.
Must try again
Isn't this good health during this time?
I feel tired and weird.
And still not sleeping well
Must come to sleep for the day instead
I can't sleep for a while.
Plus another strange dream
There are medications that cure the symptoms like that.
Interfere with it
Drink now
For the past
She was often hit.
It's so tired, unaware
I will treat her own.
Enjoy it
Akira
Yes
How am i
Not happy?
not like that
We are not separated
Glad to see you
- every day
- It is good
Sorry for missing 4 years
Probably starving
I know that you will use this kind of stuff.
Can't bear time
No matter how neat the woman is
There is a desire too.
Akira
no
Super
Forcefully
Akira is not serious.
Akira ... I'm finished.
no
- Do you bet deep well?
- Nice
- good
- so much
Another force is stronger ...
Very good .. very good
Akira .. No
Darling ... d finished
Is it deep?
Super
- Is it good?
- very sensitive
Finally
like it so much
Have fun
Akira
Harder
So shy
See, this is the nature of women.
- What to do?
- We don't have to worry.
No need to rely on drugs.
Worry for a long time
Now you can be confident.
How to visit the hot spring?
What if going to the hot spring together?
We heard that this time she had a nightmare.
So I want to invite to soak in the water to relax.
- Worried about being a husband?
- No, I am afraid to be more burdensome
- What did you say? We have known each other for a long time.
- If you don't go, Akira may get angry.
If so then I have to reply.
Akira 4 years ago, you left
I didn't go out to find happiness anywhere.
But don't worry
I definitely don't have new ones.
But still good
Even though it's embarrassing
Akira still met me in my dream instead.
We will be a husband and wife forever.
The sound of the door opened ... Who came in?
Kotasan
May I soak with people
Yes
so
So warm
Here is a sink.
Probably like that .. but it's really weird
I can be comforted because it is the president.
Well, this type of soaking is good.
I think it's better than a separate tub.
So?
It's time to move forward.
Akira would like to do that.
Will be worried
How can I forget Akira?
but
Do you want happiness as a woman?
Not so?
What will the president do?
You know ... what we do
- Why
- When you sleep
We do
Wait, the president can't.
What do you do
Do not do it.
Really soft cheeks
Koto-san... Can't be done.
- How is it?
- President, don't do this.
Well
Don't do this ... stop.
Thank you
- How did you like it?
- Don't ... don't
Do not
Big boobs
stop
Don't do this
enough
Kotasan
Always aware
But pretended not to know
Don't force it.
Let's have fun
You haven't done it for 4 years.
Very soft
- Okay, get up.
- Do not
Why did the president do this?
Everything is for you
We know she wants
Show it out
- Let me look here.
- What to do .. Stop.
All to make you happy
Thought that I was her husband
Be honest with yourself
Show me
Look
Here .. Why is this?
Do not
This is already wet.
Soaked inside
- A little more
- Do not
Take it
Don't stop ... The President.
What do you do
Very sensitive
That's it
How does this feel?
Kotasan
Can't stand it right?
no
Finished
I'll lick it anyway
Enough ... Enough
Great
So wet
Enough ... The President
- Are you finished?
- Widow
Come here, let's look inside clearly.
So greasy
So wet, Kotasan
Stop you ...
No ... I'm afraid.
Looks very good
Can't do it.
stop
Widow
President, do not do this.
I do it for you
Actually, she herself
Is a woman who is not light at all
- Koto-san, I can't.
- I can't do it.
- Do not
- Kotosan
- Can't wait
stop
Very good
- It's tight
- Aya
No, please. Please take it out.
- Kotosan
- Do not
Akiko would like to help like this too.
- no
- I will help myself
- will be broken - don't do it
- Can't, then
Superb ... Can't, then.
Yes
Her loneliness
I will comfort myself.
Can trust
I can't believe it.
That the chairman
Will do this
Because of trust
I'm not careful
Why
Why is Kotosan here?
Doctor
Chairman
Yes
What does this doctor think?
But he said strange
As if he had done it before
Don't tell him that he has broken in too.
That's it
True?
Okay, listen. We have to deal.
- but
- I have to do something
I'm shy
I will manage for myself, but I have to do it gradually.
but
I have to remove all the semen from Ruthie.
Doctor
This kind of doctor is embarrassing.
Nevermind
I have to clean the hole
All semen
I took it out
Can you doctor before
Before
Do not
Don't break it. Don't look like that.
Don't look
It's not all.
Here
Must be completely removed
Doctor, don't do this.
First
Do not .. not
stop
Widow
Can you get it first
Please stop.
stop
Doctor
Nevermind
It's really soft
Do not
Doctor, okay.
really
So can
For sterilization
I have to try a little more.
Try something
Wait
- Open your mouth .. soon
- Wait, you do too.
- Open your mouth
- Don't do that
Go out in fluency
I'm doing with women, pornography, right?
- if so
- What will you do
stop
Removed
Stop.
Excellent
- add another one for the sensitivity
- Widow ... Stop.
Do not
Shy, right?
stop
Try to increase the strength.
no
stop
Complete it.
We 3 people will take care of her own.
We will help make your dreams come true.
Inescapable ... this nightmare
This nightmare
Stop it
Where will you go?
Still 3 days left
Let me do it with people
do not
Already know that you will find this
- No ... don't
- Think of it as Akira
Do not
Below
It was restless.
Do not
We will make ourselves happy.
Stop now ...
It's not bad, right?
The three of us will replace Akira himself.
How are you
Good?
- stop
- Kotosan
- Please stop.
- Very good
Why is that
I do not understand
I can't remember anything.
What did these people have done with us?
Stop.
- Siao
- Stay still
- It's so good
- Yes
After that, they had to do each other continuously.
Still living together in the room all night
Until I did not eat
He's done with me like this.
It is still heavy.
Without appearing to rest
Crying, pleading is useless.
There is only an endless desire.
I have no choice
All the way to escape
So great, this moaning sound
Very good
Big jerky
The third day
Why don't you do a finger?
Must continue to do
But it's a lot easier to obey.
Really a woman of Akira
Wouldn't it be?
Take another finger
Prod
See if it's deep enough?
Is a really pleasant image
- already wet
- Nice
Good?
- Is it good?
- so much
- keep doing
- loud moan
See, this big pussy is fully ready.
- A lot of rude words
- really possible
Doctor .. see again
- See what else - see me again
- Viewing
Super
Very warm inside
Where did you come from?
Super sensitive
- Top
- excellent
- You see me like this. The more emotional
- Good.
Now, be honest with yourself.
Siao Chan
- no
- take it
- What's the matter
- released now
Look good
Finished .. finished
I can't.
Kotosan finally accepted
Now you know, right?
That she herself is horny
- Will you accept it?
- I accept it
really
more
Let's have fun
Choose now ... choose it as you like.
- Top
- Selectable
And what would you take first?
Choose well
Oh president
See it as a popsicle.
President's Cock
Both big and hard
Kotasan
Lick well
Find the true self
Release it
Very good
- my taste too
- me too
- There are up to 3 cocks at the same time.
- Great to go
- Great
- I love it
Yes
Use the tongue to drag too.
Kotosan is very good.
good
Really like it
- so delicious
- delicious?
This is good.
No need to choose.
Simultaneously
Lick away ... very good
Unlike before
That's very good.
- There are 3 cocks to set.
- Can't help
- I am very happy.
- great
This kind of honesty forever
- suck it
- Slowly
Awesome
- I will throw my pussy to sit well.
- Suck it too
excellent
Doctor's finger
Almost unbearable
- Is it good?
- Siao
Will be very strong
Aha Siao
Will finish ... finished
I'll do it from behind.
- what
- hurriedly changed the posture
Want to be right?
To the master too
- go in
- good
- Really sensual
- Her butt is terribly cool.
Very soft bottom
Very smooth skin as well.
Is really lucky for us
So good?
I'm so sick
Keep this honesty.
- deep
- Like, isn't it?
- will finish - will be finished again?
- Already finished
Please see.
So exceedingly
- Do you like the whole tongue?
- Which one is so good
Answer well
Let me lick some
- Sitting in a wide leg
- Master, Mongolian line came
Will lick to float
Doubt will like
- lick a lot
- Open your mouth
excellent
- He used the tongue very easily.
- She's almost crazy.
- It's really wet.
- Look inside this hole
Not
- let's see
- Top
- I like to prod.
More stimulating than this
- You want everyone to see this, right?
- Great
So full
Look so vividly
Good
- I will help myself
- widow
No ... will be finished
Then will finish again
- I will give this
- Go ahead.
Please disturb
President
The president, please put it in.
Go in
Is this enough? ... What?
A little deeper
OK
- Fit until almost unbearable.
- What?
Don't stop again
I want a lot
Is really the best pussy
Can not tolerate and lick eggs
No .... Done.
So tired
President for me to do
- great
- suck it
This pussy is really fun.
Too much, never got a lot of cocks like this, right?
Wonderful, right?
Great, right?
Lift up your legs
Not better than standing at all
Will thrust deep
Good?
Siao-chan stabbed for deep
Here
I'll lick A
Sit down
- I will lick
- Okay
Sitting
So much
The expression is clear.
No, Cretileis, it will
Will be finished
Lick
Finished ... finished
Suck each other
Suck for me
That is very good.
Is this delicious?
- very delicious
- put it better
Take it and grab it yourself
Here below
- how
- So good
- Deep stabbing cock
- fucking a little milk
Squeeze it
See you like it
Ah ...
Continue
excellent
Very good
Good force
Strong force will finish again.
Finished
- Mr. Okay?
- Playing tired
Okay, I'm against myself.
Until floating
Come here .. let's see
So wet ... can't stand it
Okay
Will wear it
Yeah ... the best
Shy ... Is it good?
Very nasty pussy
Easily broken like this
- super sensitive
- Push in. .. Looks very good.
Banged the cock back
Move around
Good?
Lick the nipples
- My nipples are hard.
- Which try?
Make me too
Awesome
Very good
- So sluts
- Siao
So good
So much to do
Will be finished again
Let's change
I continued
- She's not using light tongue at all
- is an unusual tongue
Look silly solid.
- very sensitive
- Use a good tongue
Very well done.
Finished .. finished
Catch it, plug it in.
Go ahead and show it.
Very good
Super
- Ah Siao
- Same
Excellent
Like this position?
- Okay, bump deeply.
- looks very good
Yes
Accelerate yourself
Ah, you're done.
- really sluts
- She is obsessed with it.
Lay down
Put it in
Don't wear it?
- What are you doing?
- I took it to stimulate Kitis.
Oh, so ... then do it.
- What will you do?
- I want to rub anyway
Sia .. Aao Siew Wee
Go ahead!
- will be finished
- Finished .. finished
I like it very much.
Kotasan, her pussy. This is really fucking.
Wow
Catch milk
Speed up
will be...
Will be finished
- No moaning at all
- will stab it to the middle
Aaa Siao
Can't do it at all
Miss
How are you?
Fucking a little
- Koto-san...
- Top
Can't finish it
To die
Can't
Reached the limit
Take it too hard.
Come out
Why can't another person?
Semen overflows.
The top is warm.
To my eyes
Turn aside
Want to put cock into the hole?
Please add semen again.
visit
How is it
Until almost crazy
Good to do well
Good to die, right?
excellent
Nice
completed
Very good, right?
Cool, right?
Like to be broken
Still.
Kotasan
- will not be able to
- Doctor
So comfortable
- Keep it in her pussy
- warm
I'm connected
Overflowing from the pussy
Lie down
Wide break
The president put the cock in
Very good
The inside is warm as well.
Super
Accelerate
more
Again?
I think i will finish
- Do you like it?
- very happy
Finally
Can't wait
Koto-san took it.
Warm semen
- Great
- Not bad at all. Koto-san
- Satisfy
- get full water
- She deserves it
- Of course.
- Take it again?
- more
Do it again?
Want to do more
Can Akira forgive me?
Now
Can't stop myself
Everything happens very quickly.
Before I realized
The body and mind have changed.
Don't want to be the same
Because it .... must be lonely alone
- How is the body Koto-san?
- Do not overdo it.
Can tell
I'm fine. I'm fine.
Is a boy, right?
What's the name?
- Akira
- is a good name
AVC Sub-Thai, translated by The Forbidden
Published at AVCollectors.com only