THIS BELONG TO JAVSUBBED.COM
I married an older man and had a son with him.
Since then, I've been
highly enjoying this life as a mother and wife.
Good morning..
Ahh, good morning..
Have you been working all night, Honey?
Yeah, the deadline's almost near..
Also, the kids were too loud so I couldn't sleep.
They knew you were working so they
should've at least been considerate.
Geez, those kids !
Even our son Shou grew up fast,
and now, has become too spoiled.
- I'll just go up and scold them, okay?
- Yes, I'll leave that to you.
- What about your meal...?
- Ah, I can fix it myself.
Ah, really? I'm sorry.
No prob, since I'm already up anyway.
I'll be going then.
Masegaki classmate aiming at tits Mom2 ~
My mom is taken down and begs for pregnancy ..!!
~ Eri Hosaka
This is Gagrus.
I've acquired the devil's hand.
Let's prepare for battle.
Roger, Captain. I'm ready to fire at will.
Ready, aim...
Stop it...
- Stop it...
- Hey! What are you doing?
He's all wet!
Are you okay, Yuuta?
We just wanted to play some war games.
You guys... Stop this foolishness.
You shouldn't play around like this.
Are you okay?
This hurts, right?
I'll help you get this off.
Like this...
What is this...?
Wait a minute...
Hey, where did you get this?
I'm asking where did you get this!
Answer me!
Yuuta brought that thing in by accident.
Huh?
Why would this young kid...
have this kind of thing?
A-Anyway,
this is definitely not "by accident."
Then, what is that?
This is an important thing adults use.
This isn't something kids should be keeping.
Then it's Yuuta's fault.
Yuuta has nothing to do with this.
Ah, anyway,
those water guns are confiscated.
Understood?
Answer me!
Yes.
Shall we go and get you changed?
Come on, let's get you out of those clothes.
Those guns and that thing... they're all banned.
Water guns are banned, got it?
Come here, Yuuta.
Go sit over there.
We'll get you changed, okay?
Just a minute.
Okay...
You'll catch a cold so, let's change your clothes, okay?
Are you cold? You okay?
This bruise...
Shou hit me.
Those kids...
I'm...
...already at my limit.
At this rate...
Teacher, Mom and even Auntie...
I’ll speak to Sho sternly.
That's why...
- Hey...
- But at this rate I'll go mad...
Then, your Auntie shall do...
anything you want so, can you let this pass?
- I'm sorry...
- But...
In the meantime, let's get you changed.
Yes, shall we take off these pants too...?
Ah, sorry about this...
This...
Yuta, why are you carrying this thing around?
It was in the house.
But you know, this is...
It's too early for you to know.
This is something...
when you don't want to make babies, so...
Kids having this kind of thing is bad, okay?
How do you make a baby?
Well, that's...
It's when men and women...
- love each other.
- How?
Huh? How?
Hmmm... For example,
kissing and such,
and embracing like this gently...
Something like that I guess.
Hey!
Ah... I'm sorry... Does it hurt?
Are you gonna bully me too, Auntie?!
Ah, no, that's not it...
I'm sorry, that must have hurt...
Say sorry.
Sorry?
When you say sorry...
What do you mean?
Show me your tits!
Huh?
Show me.
Because...
They look soft...
So I thought I wanted to see them.
If you don't show me,
I'll tell my mother.
That... will be a problem.
Hurry up.
Then... just look at them, okay?
If that will make you accept my apology,
then I'll do it.
Hurry up, hurry up!
This is my way of saying sorry, okay?
I wonder why I'm this nervous...
It's just a child's curiosity and yet...
Here.
Ah... What pretty tits...
So this is what boobs look like...
You've seen them, right?
Hey, I said you can only look...
So soft...
Ah... Hey...
What is the purpose of having boobs?
Well, that's for a mother to provide milk for her baby.
So Shou has already sucked this part.
Yes, in order for him to get bigger.
Here too...
What's the matter?
Your legs are shaking...
That's not it.
- Then...?
- What?
Somehow, it's getting hard.
Hey... Why is that?
That's not true...
You were just gonna look right? So it's fine already.
So milk comes out from here...
Ah, but since I don't have a baby, milk won't come out now.
- It won't?
- No, it won't.
What a waste...
Milk... milk...
It's gonna rot if you don't drink it...
If I do this, will it come out?
- Hey, what are you doing?
It won't.
This too...
This part is getting hard too...
Wow...
How about this...
I'm gonna suck it.
How is this?
- I can't take it anymore.
- Huh? Wait...
What's the matter?
Nothing.
Ah, geez...
You're gonna get cold... Come on, stand up.
Shall we remove your underwear too?
No way... He's just a child...
but he got this hard...?
And he looks... turned on too.
Yes, lift your feet.
Let's get you changed.
Yes, yes, here...
Ah, careful...
This is already wet,
so I'm gonna wash them, okay?
- Here, wear this.
- Okay.
Come on... You say something too.
Ah, but... Shou's already regretting what he did so...
Right, Shou?
You promise not to bully Yuuta anymore, right?
- I promise.
- Good.
Well then, it's late so go to sleep.
But before that, make a promise with me.
Okay?
I understand.
Then, good night.
- Good night.
Well, that's how kids are.
You don't have to worry about it that much.
I wonder how long has it been,
since my body has been touched like that...?
W-Wait a minute... What am I thinking about?
Yuuta is just a child.
Hey...
Recently,
we haven't been... doing it, huh?
What do you mean?
Sex...
What are you saying all of a sudden?
Let's... not talk about it anymore.
I have work to do.
So depressing.
I...
My husband... doesn't see me at all as a woman.
The batter is scared!
Hey, can't you kids be more quiet?
What the hell...
And then, the next day...
Yuuta came over to play.
Hey you,
make sure you hit it straight, since you're the batter.
Then, I'll make it a fast ball.
I wonder why...
Just by looking at Yuuta...
My down-there won't stop tingling...
Come on, Yuuta! Make sure you hit it this time.
Where on earth are you looking?
- Ah, no...
- What a klutz!
You can't even do something so simple.
- Look, you hit it like this. Like this!
- Hey you guys, stop it already!
What on earth are you doing? Geez.
Shou, didn't you promise yesterday?
What are you doing?
That's not it... It just happened to hit him.
Right, Yuuta?
Auntie.
You said I wouldn't get bullied anymore!
- I'm sorry... Yesterday, we' even strictly reprimanded Shou not to do it anymore.
- Auntie, I can't trust you anymore.
Don't say that...
I'm really sorry...
Hey...
Can you apologize like you did yesterday?
Then... I'll just let you touch me for a bit so,
let's go downstairs...?
I want it here, now.
We can't do it at this place... I mean, look,
the children are here too.
Hurry up!
Even if you say that...
- Then, I'll tell my mom about this.
- Please don't do that... I'm really sorry.
Hurry up, hurry up!
W-What do you want me to do?
Spread your legs.
- Spread my legs... Wait, I can't do that in here...
- Spread it!
How much...?
Your skirt's in the way.
Ah, but...
- You can't...
- Come on.
Spread your legs.
Don't move.
You can't do this kind of thing here...
Let's stop this now, okay?
They're just outside...
What are you doing, Yuuta?
Stop it...
Spread your legs wider!
Don't touch that part...
W-Wait... Let's stop this...
What are you gonna do if we're seen like this?
- Don't care.
- N-No...
Here...
- What's the matter? You're shaking.
- Ah no, it's nothing...
Shall I take a look?
Wow...
Auntie... you act demure but...
You have a beautiful pussy.
Wait, Yuuta. Where did you hear that word?
Stop using those kind of words.
Hey look, you're wet...
Auntie...
- Stop it...
- There are juices coming out...
That's not it... so...
- Here it is. Look.
- N-No...
- No... That's not it.
- Look.
Stop it...
- It's fine now, right?
- No way.
- N-No!
What's wrong, Auntie?
You're making a weird noise.
This sound...
Lift your leg more.
Hm... let's spread it wider...
What's the matter?
Hey, what's wrong?
Just say it if it feels good.
- I won't say anything anymore.
- You're so dishonest.
Auntie, we're not done yet.
Not yet.
- Huh? No...
- More...
Stop it...
So...
What's wrong?
Auntie.
What's the matter?
He's just a child... He really is just a child but...
How lewd...
Auntie... are you feeling frustrated?
Do you want to... mate with me?
Mate... you say?
This was still in my bag so...
I'll give it to you Auntie.
You said kids shouldn't carry this around, right?
I'm going home.
W-Wait, Yuuta...
What's the matter, Auntie?
Auntie... you've been out of breath for a while now.
That's... not it.
Well, what is it then?
Is this what... I really am?
A frustrated woman, sexually harassing
my son's friend...
No good! I...
I am the mother of this kid's classmate.
What happened to you, Auntie?
You know, I...
Well...
I was thinking of
showing you how adults use this thing.
Huh? Now?
But, but...
Shou and the others are playing at the veranda...
And in the next room, Uncle is doing his work...
Are you really gonna teach me how
to use that right here?
What's the matter?
If you're gonna teach me then just teach me!
Or else I'm going home!
That's... I don't want that.
Then... I want Yuuta to touch me.
Okay.
Not like that...
Adults do it a little more gently...
Gently, like this...
Is this fine?
Yes but, just a bit harder.
But you're still wearing bra.
Then, I'll take it off.
Why are your nipples like this, Auntie...?
They're hard... What's wrong with them?
They are swollen.
Hey...
What's the matter? Hey...
Are you turned on...
- Because of me...?
- Ah, don't say it like that...
I'm just here to show you how adults use condoms.
You're making lewd noises...
If you get too loud, we'll be found out.
What's the matter?
This part is just a bit... itchy.
Hey, hey...
Take everything off.
All?
- Everything.
This too?
- Yeah. Faster!
Hey, remove your bra too.
And the bottom part too.
Hurry up!
You have a beautiful body.
I’ve already lost my figure.
What's the matter?
Do you want to take it off?
What is it?
What do you want?
Hey, hey...
- I want it.
- What do you want?
Yuuta's... hard cock.
- This thing?
- Yes.
You can't.
You can't have it.
- Huh?
Hey, lay down on the bed.
Does it feel good?
No.
Then, make me feel good using your tits.
Like this...?
So soft...
Do you feel good?
It doesn't feel good?
It feels good...
No..
Don't dirty it.
Don’t grab it.
Let me lick it...
You wanna lick it?
Here...
I want you to lick the tip of my dick.
No.
I just told you earlier.
Clean it up well.
You wanna suck it more?
You have to say it.
Please let me... suck your hard dick.
Is licking enough for you?
You want to take it whole in your mouth, right?
Hey... Come here...
Is it okay?
You can't use your hands.
Up to the base.
Suck it.
I want to hear more lewd sounds...
Loud enough to be heard by Shou and the others.
Do it harder.
So lewd...
What's that?
Auntie will put this on you, because...
I want you to put your cock inside me.
What is that thing?
- But we have to use this...
- I don't need it.
But, if you don't put this on...
- We might make a baby... Come on, all adults use this.
- But I'm just a child.
I'm going home.
Ah, it's fine if we don't use it so...
Just put it in me.
Please... Hey, come on, please...
Then, stand over there.
Here?
Yes. Lift your butt.
More.
Bend over.
Stop stalling and just put it in already...
Ah... Please...
Beg me... Beg me to do it... Come on.
Put your dick in Auntie's pussy...
I can't hear you.
Please... just put it in me...
Give me your cock...
- So you want cock that much, huh...
- Please...
Well, then...
Open the curtain.
Curtain...?
- Hey...
- What?
I have... betrayed my husband and Shou.
I've opened the curtain so please put it in me...
- You want me to put it in...?
- Ah... Please...
Hey... Look...
Put it in on your own.
Is it okay...?
Hey...
Ah... Feels good...
- It's so good...
- Does it feel good?
It feels so good...
You're a failure as a mother.
So good...
Please... do it harder...
-You want me to fuck you harder?
-Yes, please...
Please, more...
It feels so good...
Since I gave birth to Shou...
I haven't had much sex...
It really has been a long time...
Ah, I can't hold it in anymore...
It's not sex. This is mating.
- Yes... it's mating...
Ah! So good...!
- It's because you're a pervert, Auntie.
- No... don't say that...
... What are you doing?
Your cock inside my pussy...
I want to feel more of it...
- So you really want my dick in your pussy, huh?
- Please... give it to me...
Here's the cock you love so much...
Ah... so good...
Ah... Yuuta's cock feels so good...
Does it feel good?
I'm feeling really good too...
- Auntie is really happy...
- Auntie's pussy...
- That's right... Hey, Auntie.
- What is it?
Can you become my semen tank...?
That's impossible...
You mean you want to cum inside me, right?
I'll get pregnant so you can't...
I'm not allowed...?
I'll just stop this then.
No...
You can cum inside my pussy...
you can cum inside me...
Please, put your cock in me...
- Really?
- Yes... please...
- So you're willing to become my semen tank...
- Please... put it in me...
- Feels good...!
- Ah... feels full...
- I'm gonna cum hard inside your pussy...
- Please...
Ah...! Feels good...
Ah! So good...
It feels too good...
Yuuta's cock feels so warm inside me...
So hot...
Ah... cumming...!
Auntie, what are you saying?
Cumming all by yourself.
Hey Auntie.
This time, you go on top.
Hey.
Can I move now?
Just move already.
Ah... feels good...
Touch my tits too...
Feels good...
I can feel you deep inside me...
I want to see Auntie's cum face...
Can't wait to see it...
It's fine... you can keep fucking me...
- Then make sure you cum a lot...
- Let's cum together...
It feels so good...
Ah, I can feel my dick hitting your womb...
Auntie...
Your womb is descending.
- Is your cock hitting my womb...
- It is...
Ah... so good...
My womb...
It's craving for Yuuta's cum...
It feels too good...
- You want my cum that badly?
- I want it... please...
It feels too good... ah!
- Auntie...
- Ah... your cock is so hot...
- Ah.... I'm cumming...
- Auntie...
- I'm gonna cum hard...
- Please...
I don't wanna cum yet.
Here you go...
Hey, sit up.
Inside my pussy...
Yuuta's cum has gotten all messy and sticky...
It feels good...
- Is it good?
- It's really good.
Auntie...
...wants your cum to fill up her pussy...
Aaaah.... it feels so...
Ah... cum a lot inside me...
- Oh no... ah!
- I'm cumming...
I'm cumming...!
Feels good...
Cumming...!
I'm cumming.... ah!
Aaah...
Ah... so much cum...
Hey, your pussy's squeezing my dick.
It's so tight.
Yuuta...
You came hard... My womb is full of cum now...
I can feel your cum going deep inside me...
Ahhh... the juice is coming out.
Hey, clean it up.
Here, clean this..
Hey, Yuuta, will you have sex with me again...?
I'm your master, right?
And it's not sex, it's mating, right?
You semen tank.
Yes, yes.
I wonder... if I'm just one of Yuuta's many bitches...?
I... for Yuuta...
No, for Master Yuuta...
I was then willing to do anything.
After that,
I kept it a secret from my family,
and became Master Yuuta's sex slave.
I could no longer live
without Master Yuuta.
I...
Ah... Master Yuuta...
your dick is in my swine pussy.
It feels so good...
Master... please...
Hey! What's wrong? Is everything ok?
I just... feel a little sick. I'm sorry.
Ah, is that so...
Oh, Shou!
What the hell, Shou! You’re strong.
I lost.
Hey, Shou. Why are you being overly
friendly to Yuuta lately?
What's the point if we don't bully him!
Well, it's 'cause Mom keeps bugging
me when I bully him.
Because of that,
Yuuta's gotten smugger.
- It really sucks.
- Seriously?
Hey, you're taking too long in the toilet!
Hey Yuuta, buy some snacks! Your treat.
I don't have any money.
- What did you say, you bastard?!
- Hey, stop it Teppei.
- Stop it. Just do that when I'm not around.
- Tsk.
Hey! Honey!
Huh? Where on earth did she go?
Mom...?
She's not here... I wonder where she went...
Ah, Uncle, sorry for intruding.
- Ah, it's already late so take care on your way.
- Yes.
Mom!
Hey, Yuuta, I know Shou's not bullying you lately
but don't let that get to your head.
- Teppei, when Shou is not around, you can do anything, right?
- What did you say?!
I'll show you something good.
Is it really okay to go in without permission?
Is this for real?!
Have you been a good girl?
It's gotten all sticky.
It's cause I've been craving for Yuuta's cum all day...
- If you listen carefully to what I say,
I'll give you as much cum as you want.
- Okay...
I'll listen to whatever you say,
so please just put it in me...
I was thinking of...
teaching Teppei some things.
Hey, come here.
Ah, why Master Yuuta?
Auntie...
Master Yuuta... why is Teppei here?
This is a little... embarrassing...
Well, Teppei doesn't know anything so...
Hey, Teppei...
Besides your mom's, you know nothing
about a woman's body, right?
I'll show you.
This is my semen tank.
Semen... What is that?
Well, hmm... She’s a swine.
Also...
She's getting wet.
It feels so good...
Hey, push your hips forward.
- You want my dick, right?
- I want Master Yuuta's cock no matter what...
Aaaah.... amazing...
Ah... it's so good...
Ah... my pussy feels so good...
No good... I'm...
Aren't you completely soaked?
- Hey, keep it up.
- Yes, Master Yuuta.
It’s sticky.
Sit up.
Hey, Teppei...
You haven't seen tits before, right?
You haven't, right?
I'll show you.
Here, look.
Teppei.
You wanna touch them, right?
Try touching them.
I want to touch Auntie's boobs more...
Let me touch them...
Hey, Auntie, show him properly.
Like, how to properly look at them and stuff.
Um, you do this...
Feels good...
It feels so good...
Hey, Master Yuuta... Please touch me too...
Hey Teppei, why are you getting
all quiet for?
Hey, do it properly... Like this...
This is the part that feels good the most...
Can I have some cock...?
Ah... it's so good...
Ah... she's drooling...
- Come on, lick her tits.
- Huh?
- Ah, lick it...?
- Ah... so good...
- Auntie, you ask him too.
- Teppei... please lick them...
What's the purpose of these boobs again?
These boobs...?
This is... for rubbing dicks in between them...
Like Master Yuuta's cock...
Hey, Teppei...
Look this way.
Have you heard about this before?
Then look closely.
Auntie, spread it on your own.
Can you tell him what that is?
You mean this?
This is Master Yuuta's...
dirty semen tank...
for storing his cum.
- That's why...?
- That's why, please look at it carefully.
What's wrong? Don't you wanna try touching it?
Ah... feels good...
You don't have to be scared of it...
You can try eating it, you know...
Hey, do you get that, Teppei?
There's a hole right here.
In this part,
you insert your cock
then release your cum inside.
If you do, you can make a baby.
Did you know that?
You don't know what cum means too, huh?
I...
My dick's been this hard for a while...
That's right. You insert that in there.
Do you wanna cum?
Then, cum inside
Auntie's pussy mouth.
Come on.
Come here.
Hey.
Take off his pants.
Come on, put it in your mouth.
What is this... Ah!
What...?!
What is this... Amazing...
Teppei's cock tastes so good...
What's the matter, Teppei?
Somehow... it feels weird...
Are you gonna cum?
W-Wait...
Aaaah... I'm gonna...
Did you cum?
Show it to him.
What is that?
So much came out.
This white stuff...
is called semen.
Next, I'll show you how to mate.
Yuuta's cock...
Because I want to serve...
Make sure you let me know the day you're ovulating.
Yes, I'll let you know for sure.
Master Yuuta's cock... it's hitting my womb repeatedly...
Ah! Feels good...
I can’t have my husband’s dick anymore.
My pussy is Master's Yuuta's personal plaything...
Teppei...
if you stop bullying me,
I'll let you use Auntie and teach you everything
you want to know.
- Ah, it's good.
- Hmm, delicious!
- Ah, I tried changing the menu.
- Yeah, it's better than usual.
- It's good, huh?
- It's good.
- It's great.
- It’s a bit spicy today.
This is nice.
But somehow,
It's been a while since we ate together.
Ah, sorry... I've been so busy lately.
Yes, you've been.
- Really sorry.
- This is good from time to time.
I'll make something like this for you.
Okay, understood.
Ah, by the way Shou... that shy kid, you're
not bullying him anymore, right?
Right now, we're in good terms.
- And we're always playing together too.
- Ah, that's good.
Then, as a reward...
Next time when I'm free, shall we go watch baseball or something?
Ah, really?
- I wanted to watch live baseball...
- Yeah, I knew you do.
I'll definitely get a home-run ball.
I see... Well you've always loved boasting about stuff like that...
Right now, Master Yuuta's cum...
...is being totally wasted.
Oh, we can watch it from infield side.
What's the difference between infield side and outfield side?
Huh? Well, infield side is...
close to players.
Shou...
Do you want any siblings...?
W-What are you talking about all of a sudden...?
- Well...
- Siblings...?
Well, if it's a little brother, I'd like that.
I guess we can go watch baseball and stuff.
You too, what are you saying?
I'm already infertile.
- What's infertile?
- Ah, nothing, it's nothing.
It's adult talk.
- Tomorrow, Teppei and the others are coming, right?
- Yes, they are.
Geez, tomorrow too? I'll be busy with work as well.
Shou, don't get too loud.
Yes.
Yes... tomorrow will be an important day for Master Yuuta and I...
Hey, do you guys have a girl you like?
- Of course we do.
- Oh, really? Who are they?
- Well...
- No way...
- Your towels are here.
Okay.
- Well since you asked, she's really cute.
- Ah, really?
Shall I wipe your body?
- I can show you now.
- Really? Then show me some pictures.
Erika?
- Why?
- Good job, Shou!
- Isn't that just a one-sided crush?
- This feels good, right?
Well next time, I'm thinking of giving her a present.
Ah, really? You're really gonna give her one?
I'll definitely do it!
Is it her birthday or something?
Well, not really.
How should I say it... Just a normal present I guess.
You don’t have good sense, do you?
I was thinking if I should give her a necklace or something.
- Whoa... that's really mature.
- Yeah, really mature.
- Do you have any money?
- Hmm, well, I only have 300 yen.
- I can give you some.
- Really? Then give me at least 500 yen.
Ah, of course.
- Do you want to change your gift idea then?
- Ah, but I still think a necklace is good...
But I wonder how much would that be...
It's expensive you know!
Yeah, around 2,000 yen at least.
- That's too expensive!
- Ah, but when you become an adult, expensive gifts
go from 100,000 to 200,000 yen.
100,000! That's too expensive!
That... no matter what you say, it's too much...
Then that's around, 51 necklaces...
What are you talking about? Then that'll be 102,000 yen already right?
Because you multiply 2,000 to get 100,000, so it should be 50.
- If you double that then it's 100 pieces.
- What would I do with 100 pieces?
- Are you bad with math?
- I'm not that good with it.
Ah, so you hate math.
But Shou probably hates it more.
The grade I got for Math...
- I think it was around 3 points...
- What? 3 points is hardly a score! You should at least get 100.
- No way...
- You're really bad at it, huh...
- Me, I got 10 points.
- Oh, Teppei got 10 points, huh.
Ah, that's a big gap. That's 3 times more than Shou's.
- 3 times?
- Yeah.
- I didn't know.
- Haha, that's awful.
That's bad you know, not knowing how to calculate.
Then, try this. If 10 points is 3 times higher than 3 points,
how many points is 10 times higher than 3 points?
- Well...
- Come on, just try.
Teppei, you know the answer, right?
- 300 points is 10 times higher than 3 points you know!
- Teppei didn't know it either!
- But it's because I don't know much about the economics.
- That's not economics at all.
Huh, then if it's not economics, what is it?
Well, you guys...
Since you're feeling good right,
let's just forget about that.
Well, there's a lot going on in society when you become adults.
- But, what is society?
- Huh? Well, society is a group of people living, working
and coexisting together.
- Then, I'm also part of society?
- Yes, you are, in some way.
Well, there are people in society that are earning income,
and there are also those who are useless.
- I want to earn money too.
- Haha, it's fine, you're still young anyway.
When you get a bit older, you can get a part-time job.
- How old should I be to get one?
- I guess around high school.
Hmph, then I still have a long way to go.
Yes, you do.
Speaking of part-time jobs, what kind of
work do you wanna do?
- I guess a job where I can eat delicious food...?
- Like a family restaurant, maybe.
"Welcome! What would you like?"
Something like that I guess.
- That's a little different from what I imagined.
- Ah, different, huh?
- Hmm... then... how about a cake shop?
- Ah, that...
- But you can't eat your own goods, right? Ah but...
If it's near the expiration date, and you think it won't sell anymore,
I guess they'll give it to you or something.
- Then wouldn't that make your stomach hurt?
- Ah, no, it's just barely safe then.
- Would it be ok to eat it?
- It's fine.
There's no way they'd make something you wouldn't be able to eat.
That's right... then I'll just get a part-time job at a cake shop.
- And maybe, you get to work alongside a cute girl too...
- Ah... I'm feeling excited already.
- Right?
- Shou should work hard and become a pastry chef instead.
- Ah, that would be great too.
- Hey, Dad...
- I want to buy a pet...
- That talk again...
Hey Eri, Yuuta came out of the bath earlier, right?
We're talking about getting a pet right now...
You know, Shou's bugging me about getting a cute, little pet again...
It's so irritating!
I-Isn't that fine...?
- Is that really okay?
- Look, even Mom says it's okay.
Even if you say it's fine,
raising a pet is difficult, you know.
You know, I also used to have pet back then.
I used to like, walk it every morning or night.
And if it's a dog, you have to clean regularly.
And if it's not trained, then it'll be even
more difficult, you know.
Forget about it already.
But... I'll take care of it properly.
That's not the point.
And even if we get one now, at some point
you'll get tired of it, that happens right?
- There's no way I will.
- Really?
Even Yuuta has a pet... so it's just weird that
I'm not allowed to have one...
It doesn't mean that because one person has something,
you should have it as well.
Well, sometimes I'm fickle-minded too...
They're usually nice at first but then don't.
And when that happens, it's the dog that suffers, right?
Let's stop talking about this, okay?
Well, you know, Grandma...
Your Grandma, I mean...
When she told me to take care of it,
I was a little annoyed.
- I guess, I do get it.
- Ah, by the way, Yuuta.
What type of pet do you have?
- Me...?
- Yeah.
- Pig.
- Huh?
- Pig?
- A wild pig.
You have a pig?
Is that even allowed?
Isn't that considered livestock? Right?
It's fine.
I sometimes play with it too, the wild pig.
Why didn't you let me play too?
It's not like you have to anyway.
But why, geez...
you didn't let me play too?
- Why? You should have told him stuff like that.
- Huh?
Why didn't you tell him about it, huh?
Well, it's not like Shou and I are going out or anything, right?
It's not about liking or what, you're friends right?
There should be no secret between friends.
- I guess so...
- Well, well, it's fine, just don't fight you guys.
- Let's all get along, okay?
- Ah... I feel refreshed.
- Then, I'm going ahead too.
- Okay.
Auntie, please dry me off too.
By the way, Yuuta.
Are pigs easy to handle? It must be tough
especially cleaning up after them, right?
Yes.
But... it obediently listens to what I say.
When it's time for breeding,
it's not very good and it's a bit troublesome,
but when that happens, I play with it.
- So you play with it...
- Yes.
- So you can play with it.
- So you want a dog that badly?
- I want it.
You don't want a cat?
Hmm... I guess I like cats too.
How about something simple, like a goldfish.
Goldfish... I'm not interested in that...
- But isn't it easier to handle? A goldfish I mean.
- Rather than easy, I want something I really want.
- That's why I want a dog.
- Why?
- Because everyone in class has a dog.
- Does Teppei have one too?
Hey, wash your body properly.
- But you don't really know what pet Teppei has, right?
- Hmm...
Ryohei and...
- Kenta, I guess.
- How about the girls?
- Um, I forgot.
- Then not everyone has a pet.
- Masumi has one.
- What breed?
- Breed...?
- Breed...
- Of dogs.
I'm talking about dog breed.
Well... I don't know anything about that...
- Big or small, which do you prefer?
- Hmm... I guess the smaller ones.
Well, I guess smaller ones are easier to handle.
You know, I used to have a small dog.
- You did?
- Yes before. Your grandmother made me take care of it.
How was it?
It was really cute. It was a shepherd breed.
- Shepherd?
- Yes, a dog's breed.
- I want a Chihuahua.
- Chihuahua?
Feels good...
- You want a Chihuahua?
- Yes.
- Chihuahua's are really small, you know.
Like the one on the commercials.
We have to keep it inside the house.
- I think it's good.
- Right?
- And you can sleep with it too.
- Yes, yes... I'll sleep with it.
- With the dog?
But don't hurt it because you toss around in your sleep.
Auntie...
I'm gonna cum... I'm cumming...
I have no idea...
- I've never noticed what I do when I'm sleeping.
- Should I record you?
Like in a peeping movie.
No, you do it yourself. A peeping movie is done by others.
- By myself...
- It's because you want to know on your own.
It's fine right.
Then, I'm going ahead now.
You know what? Surrounded by a lot of kids like this,
somehow it feels like we have a big family, huh?
I guess having a lot of kids is fine too...
- I think it's good.
I can imagine us moving to the country,
making lots of kids,
doing things like we are right now, but the only
difference is...
we're doing stuff we like, like writing a novel or something...
What do you think?
Ah... that sounds really good.
- I think that's good...
- Right? It's good right?
Ah, that's right...
But if we do move to the country, I wonder if
I can quit writing novels too?
I mean, we can be self-sufficient,
have our own little farm and raise lots of kids, right?
And also... having a ranch is good too.
I guess if we have a ranch,
that's it... we can have livestock too, right?
- We can even get a dog... or better yet, we can have tons of dogs.
- Really?
- It's fine if it's like that.
- Then, let's move right now.
- That's it, let's move now!
- Ah, my bad, that's just your father's delusion.
It's just a delusion so...
But you know, Shou...
Your mom can't really have kids now,
at her age anyway.
Right? It's not that kind of body anymore, right?
Ah... But... I really want a baby.
No matter how many... I want a lot of babies.
Even if I do it repeatedly, I want lots and lots of it.
She says she wants it.
A baby she says... So it's either a sister or brother for you.
So, what do you think of that?
That's right, I want a baby!
Mom, what are you saying?
I'll go ahead.
- Hey, hurry up and finish up here too.
- Okay.
Honey...
- Oh, sorry. I didn't notice you.
- Ah sorry, you were in the middle of work.
Ah, the kids are already asleep so, I was wondering
if I should go to bed as well.
I see. Okay, good night then.
Just thinking of Master Yuuta's cock... makes my body tingle...
and my womb burn with desire...
My eggs long for their sperm...
They want to be fertilized with Master Yuuta's excellent genes...
My womb is screaming with anticipation.
Today is a dangerous day for me... a dangerous
day for me and Master Yuuta.
Hey, Auntie...
Yes...
Auntie is my what again?
I am... Master Yuuta's dirty bitch, semen tank.
Auntie.
Today is a dangerous day, right?
Yes, it's very dangerous.
Before that,  you said will be my semen tank. Am I right?
Yes.
From today, I pledge to get rid of my husband and son,
I pledge to become Master Yuuta's semen tank,
and pledge to carry Master Yuuta's children.
Master Yuuta's...
breeding preference,
and even his commands,
I'll receive them all without contraceptives, as promised.
To have Master Yuuta's cum so deep in my womb,
I promise to let him fertilize me.
Teppei.
Bring that thing out.
That thing... is where Teppei gathered all the boys' cum in class.
And we're aiming to put this all in your pussy.
Everyone in your class?
- Even Shou...?
- Shou's not included there.
I don't want any other cum other than yours, Master Yuuta.
I want a semen tank that'll accept any kind of semen.
Y-Yes... Master Yuuta.
Teppei, here.
Cum is coming...
It's warm...
Ah... no...
It's so wet...
Aaah... My pussy's drowning...
Then... so that you get pregnant,
I'll pour them down to your womb.
This semen has reached my womb.
Your cock...
Ah... I'm cumming... cumming ah!
You’re full of semen.
So much cum...
Amazing... My pussy feels full...
Teppei and I...
- Now, let's plant seeds directly in you.
- Ah... yes, please.
However...
in order to do that,
we've prepared something first.
- Right?
- Yeah.
- How long are you gonna keep standing out there.
- N-No, stop it...
- I said come here.
- No... no...
Ah, Shou!
Mom... why...
Master Yuuta... why is Shou here...?
We can't do this in front of Shou...
Then, that promise you said earlier is a lie?
Then, do you wanna go back to Shou?
Or do you still want to be my semen tank?
Please...
Mom... please go back to being my mom...
M-Mom...
Mom... please stop...
It's just as you see.
Auntie...
will forever be...
my personal semen tank.
- Right?
- Yes, Master Yuuta.
From this point on, we, Teppei and I...
will be planting seeds and mating with Auntie,
so just stay there and watch, Shou.
What do you mean by planting seeds and mating?
Well, you can just wait and see.
What's with that pitiful face?
Feels good...
Look Shou...
I don't want to...
This is from where you were born.
- Shou's mom's tits taste's good.
- It is...?
My pussy feels so painfully horny...
It feels good Master Yuuta...
On the bed...
I'm sorry... I'm gonna cum soon...
Whoa... it's all messy...
Ah... if you lick it like that I'll...
Licking my pussy that was full of dirty semen...
You can't do that...
I want to lick Master Yuuta's raw cock...
- You wanna lick it?
- Please let me lick it.
Do it more slowly.
I've been thinking about nothing but cocks lately...
I...
Master Yuuta, does this feel good?
Feels good...
I'll make you feel even more good...
I guess it's about time to put it in...
You go on top first.
Well then...
Now, let me receive Master Yuuta's
special type of breeding technique.
Aaaah... It feels so good...
Here, lick my dick too...
Keep moving.
Take it all the way in.
It's hitting your womb, right?
It feels so amazing...
- Feels good?
- Amazingly good...
It's so good... I think this kind of breeding is good...
Aaaah... it's so good...
Mating like a dirty pig...
Ah! I'm gonna cum again...
Let's cum together...
Please keep pounding my pussy with your cock...
- Your pussy?
- Aaaah... it's so...
Your cock feels so good... to the point where I don't
know which is my pussy or your cock anymore...
I don’t care as long as you give me semen.
Come here...
I can really hit it from this position...
Ah... It feels so good...
Ah... Amazing...
Ah... Master Yuuta...
Cocks other than Master Yuuta's should enter my pussy but...
please feel free to watch as much as you like.
Please, scold me later again.
Ah... So good...
- Hey, show me your face while you cum.
- Ah... ah... Fuck me harder...
Ah... I'm cumming...
Rub it.
It feels good...
So good...
Cock feels so good... Amazingly good...
Ah, I think I'm gonna cum...
Please...
Teppei, did you cum?
You released a lot of cum in me, right?
- Did you cum?
- Ah... Amazing...
It's all over... my womb...
Show me.
You allowed other cocks inside you apart from mine, huh?
I'm sorry, Master Yuuta.
I'm sorry for being a bad, dirty pig.
But this dirty pig doesn't surrender to any other cocks
other than Master Yuuta's.
Hey, stand up.
Master Yuuta's cock is thrusting in me...
Aaaah... That feels really good...
Please keep using my pussy for your cock's pleasure...
I want to get pregnant with Master Yuuta's sperm forever and ever...
I want a boy.
Hey, look at Shou!
Are you jerking off at the sight of your mom mating?
Enjoy it.
Master Yuuta, please, I beg you.
Please give your cum to this pussy... to this dirty pig's pussy.
Please give me your cum...
Then I'll give it to you.
- This dirty pig's pussy...
- Ah... Please give my pussy all your cum...
You want me to cum inside you, right?
Spread your legs wider.
Aaah... Please...
I'm cumming... cumming!
Ah... Amazing... Master Yuuta's cum...
I want more...
Please give me more of your sperm...
I'm begging you...
Y-Yuuta...
I won't bully you anymore so,
me too... please let me...
mate with Mom, I mean, Yuuta's dirty pig.
No way, no way!
Shou's the only one who can't.
This is your punishment for bullying me.
Auntie, you don't what that kind of guy too, right?
Yes, if it's not Master Yuuta's cock, it's no good.
If it's Master Yuuta's cock... my pussy goes all crazy.
Here you go...
I’ll get pregnant and I enjoy it.
Please pour semen on me.
Please keep using me...
as your semen tank.
I beg you..
I... I want a baby...
My pussy... my pussy's going crazy...
Feels good...
Ah... It's so good...
My womb's getting bigger and bigger...
Bigger...
Master Yuuta's cum...
Please fill it up with a lot of your cum...
Master Yuuta's cum... My pussy feels full...
I'm so happy... I'm gonna have a baby...
Ah... I'm so happy...
- Since you're already close, you shouldn't go out
much, just until here is okay.
- Ah, really?
How's Shou by the way?
Shou and Yuuta are very supportive of me everyday.
So I'm feeling a lot better.
I see, well he's a big brother now after all.
I just hope he sees to it until the end.
But surprisingly,
making a new baby is a happy thing after all.
Ah, I guess we'll have to work hard.
- I guess he's sleeping.
- Ah, probably.
- Ah, Yuuta, welcome.
- Uncle, good afternoon.
Welcome. Thank you, as always.
- Then, I'm off.
- Okay, off you go.
- Take care on your way.
- Yes.
You're prepared already right, semen tank?
Yes...
Master Yuuta...
My... pregnant pussy,
is already soaking wet...
You're sopping wet...
Ah... Today too...
please release your cum all over my womb...
Deep inside me...
Please release all of your cum deep inside my pussy...
Inside me, there's a small, living thing.
I became Master Yuuta's semen storage,
and in addition to my husband, meaning, all my son's classmates,
I continued having dirty sex with them...
This is my life now.
THIS BELONG TO JAVSUBBED.COM