[AIKA] Oh, Kanako, weren't you planning to go to the amusement park with your boyfriend tomorrow?
[AIKA] But isn't it going to rain?
[KANAKO] Aww, really? That's the worst.
[AIKA] Ah! You should bring your boyfriend home instead!
[KANAKO] But big sis, you'll be home.
[AIKA] Yeah, but it's fine.
[AIKA] After all, I really want to see your boyfriend.
[KANAKO] Really?
[KANAKO] Then I'll bring him home.
[AIKA] Yeah, do it.
[KANAKO] All right!
[JIRO] Is this...?
[KANAKO] Yep.
[JIRO] So this is your house.
[JIRO] Ah, your older sister lives here too, right?
[JIRO] I'm nervous.
[KANAKO] It's fine. She's nice.
[KANAKO] She just likes to tease people.
[JIRO] Eh, is that so?
[KANAKO] Don't worry. It's fine.
[KANAKO] Come on in.
[JIRO] Pardon the intrusion.
[KANAKO] Here.
[JIRO] Thanks.
[AIKA] Hello there. Kanako's boyfriend?
[JIRO] Nice to meet you. Thanks for everything.
[AIKA] What's wrong?
[JIRO] Uh, no. N-nothing.
[AIKA] Then, come on in.
[JIRO] Right, pardon the intrusion.
[AIKA] Yes.
[AIKA] But there's no need for such politeness.
[JIRO] Ah, I'm sorry.
[AIKA] Come on.
[JIRO] So this is what your room feels like.
[KANAKO] Hey, stop staring. It's embarrassing.
[JIRO] Kanako! I love you!
[KANAKO] Don't be that loud. My sister's here.
[JIRO] Sorry.
[JIRO] Come on, take it off.
[JIRO] Wow, your bra's so cute!
[KANAKO] You can't be this loud. My sister's still here.
[JIRO] My bad.
[JIRO] Still taking it off though.
[JIRO] This is fine too.
[JIRO] Wow, the underwear's cute too.
[KANAKO] They are panties.
[JIRO] That so?
[JIRO] Hey, I can't stand it anymore. Can you lick it?
[KANAKO] Fine.
[JIRO] Really?
[JIRO] What is it?
[KANAKO] The way you're rushing is cute?
[JIRO] That so?
[JIRO] Hurry up.
[KANAKO] It got so big.
[JIRO] Well, I got really excited after seeing you naked.
[KANAKO] I'm embarrassed.
[JIRO] Ah, that feels good.
[KANAKO] My sister's here so lower your voice.
[JIRO] My bad, my bad.
[KANAKO] It's okay.
[KANAKO] Does it feel good?
[JIRO] Really good.
[KANAKO] Even quieter.
[JIRO] Sorry.
[KANAKO] My sister will hear you.
[JIRO] Yeah, sorry.
[JIRO] Hey, I can't hold it anymore. Let's have sex.
[JIRO] Can I?
[KANAKO] Yeah.
[JIRO] Really?
[JIRO] All right.
[KANAKO] You can't.
[JIRO] What's wrong?
[KANAKO] Make sure to put on a condom.
[JIRO] It's fine. Let's just do it like this.
[KANAKO] No can do.
[KANAKO] Condom please.
[JIRO] Fine, I got it.
[JIRO] There we go.
[JIRO] I'm putting it in.
[KANAKO] This feels good.
[JIRO] Kanako, this feels so good.
[KANAKO] This feels really good.
[JIRO] Really?
[KANAKO] What is it all of a sudden?
[JIRO] No, nothing at all.
[KANAKO] I'll be on top this time.
[KANAKO] I'm moving, okay?
[KANAKO] Hey, where are you looking?
[JIRO] Ah, sorry.
[KANAKO] Don't be distracted.
[KANAKO] Look at me more.
[JIRO] Ah, um, you're too rough!
[JIRO] I'm gonna cum!
[JIRO] Don't be too rough.
[JIRO] Ah, I'm cumming!
[JIRO] I came.
[KANAKO] So you came.
[KANAKO] I feel like sleeping.
[JIRO] H-hey... what are you doing?
[AIKA] Well fucking done.
[JIRO] Uh, no. Wait, what are you doing?
[AIKA] It's fine.
[JIRO] You'll wake her up.
[AIKA] She's asleep already. It's fine.
[AIKA] You're young so you can go again, right?
[JIRO] No, I can't.
[AIKA] Shall we find out?
[JIRO] Umm.
[JIRO] What will we do if she finds out?
[AIKA] It's fine.
[AIKA] Come now, weren't you staring at me before?
[AIKA] Compared to Kanako's, my breasts are beautiful, right?
[AIKA] Beautiful, right? You wanna touch them? You can.
[JIRO] I can't.
[AIKA] You WERE staring, weren't you?
[AIKA] Are they soft?
[JIRO] Uhh, yeah.
[AIKA] More. Touch them properly.
[AIKA] Yeah, like that.
[AIKA] Harder.
[JIRO] Ah, no. I'm sorry. This is bad.
[AIKA] Why?
[AIKA] It's really fine.
[JIRO] Wait...
[AIKA] It's absolutely fine.
[AIKA] Touch them properly.
[AIKA] You eyes were super concentrated on them earlier, no?
[JIRO] N-no.
[AIKA] Touch them to your heart's content.
[AIKA] How about it? Ready for another round?
[JIRO] No. N-no. I can't...
[AIKA] Don't worry about it.
[AIKA] It got this big already. You can't deny it anymore.
[AIKA] You want it, no?
[AIKA] Still can go for it again, right?
[JIRO] No, that's...
[AIKA] What is it?
[AIKA] You can do me without a condom.
[JIRO] Wha..?
[AIKA] You want to, right?
[AIKA] There's no way you'll say no... when you're this hard, right?
[AIKA] Don't you want to feel good?
[AIKA] It's super hard.
[AIKA] This must feel pretty good, huh.
[AIKA] Don't you want to put it in?
[JIRO] No... I...
[AIKA] How about it?
[AIKA] Your face looks painful.
[JIRO] S-stop...
[AIKA] Gonna cum?
[AIKA] Go ahead.
[JIRO] W-wait... wait!
[AIKA] Why should I stop?
[JIRO] Nonono, stop, wait-
[AIKA] You're kidding...
[AIKA] It's your second shot... why did you cum?
[AIKA] Did you really cum again?
[AIKA] It's still really thick though.
[AIKA] You came again.
[AIKA] Couldn't you hold it in?
[AIKA] We didn't get found out.
[AIKA] You still want more, right?
[AIKA] You got your clothes dirty.
[AIKA] She won't find out.
[AIKA] Huh, so that's how it is. You and Kanako met back in high school.
[JIRO] Uh, yes.
[JIRO] Aika-San, you don't have a boyfriend?
[AIKA] Haha, just Aika is fine, and no, I don't have one at all.
[AIKA] Why can't I get a boyfriend?
[KANAKO] Big sis is pretty, smells nice, has a good personality... and a pair of big boobs.
[AIKA] Wait, what do you mean by "smells good?"
[AIKA] And my boobs have nothing to do with this.
[AIKA] Wouldn't a sleepover be interesting? It's fun if you think about it.
[AIKA] You'll stay for the night, right?
[KANAKO] It's fine, Jiro-kun. Big sis already says it's okay. So stay here.
[JIRO] Ah, okay.
[AIKA] Wake up.
[AIKA] You don't have to that surprised... shhhh
[AIKA] Or else Kanako will wake up.
[JIRO] Ah, I'm sorry. But what are you doing?
[JIRO] It'll be bad if Kanako wakes up.
[AIKA] That's why we have to be quiet.
[JIRO] This is bad...
[AIKA] It's going to be fine so be quiet.
[AIKA] Oh?
[AIKA] Still refusing?
[JIRO] No, I...
[KANAKO] Jiro-kun... I love you...
[JIRO] Is she awake?
[AIKA] No, she's having a good dream.
[AIKA] Do you like my boobs?
[JIRO] No, but...
[AIKA] I'll let you lick them a lot.
[JIRO] But Kanako is...
[AIKA] What? What about Kanako? Hmm?
[AIKA] No escaping.
[AIKA] Your loud voice will wake her up.
[JIRO] Yes.
[AIKA] Here.
[JIRO] They're really beautiful.
[AIKA] Suck it more.
[AIKA] Even more.
[AIKA] Suck it a lot.
[AIKA] This feels good.
[AIKA] Keep going. Come on.
[AIKA] That felt really good.
[AIKA] Next will be my turn to make you feel good.
[AIKA] Put your hands on the table.
[JIRO] Yes.
[AIKA] That's right.
[AIKA] Come over here.
[AIKA] I can see it all.
[AIKA] It's twitching.
[AIKA] Has Kanako seen any of this?
[JIRO] No...
[JIRO] What are you doing?
[AIKA] I'll make you feel even better this time... with the breasts you love so much.
[AIKA] Lie down here.
[AIKA] Come up here.
[AIKA] How is it? Does it feel good?
[JIRO] This is bad...
[AIKA] How about it? It feels good, right?
[AIKA] Kanako can't do this, can she?
[AIKA] I wonder if she heard us.
[JIRO] That'd be bad.
[AIKA] If you show me such a face... I'll be turned on too.
[AIKA] Now, let's do it.
[AIKA] Here, look.
[AIKA] Come on. Do it.
[AIKA] Oh, you want to lick it?
[AIKA] This feels good.
[AIKA] Touch it.
[AIKA] Feels good.
[KANAKO] Jiro-kun.
[AIKA] Come on, keep going.
[AIKA] She won't wake up.
[AIKA] This feels good.
[AIKA] Feels good.
[AIKA] Feels really good.
[AIKA] You feel great.
[AIKA] This is bad. It feels too good.
[AIKA] I feel like cumming.
[AIKA] I'm cumming.
[AIKA] It feels good.
[AIKA] So cute. You can do it after all.
[AIKA] This feels good.
[AIKA] Oh no.
[AIKA] I'm cumming.
[AIKA] That felt really good.
[AIKA] I want it so bad now.
[AIKA] It's fine, right?
[AIKA] It's fine.
[AIKA] May I?
[JIRO] Right here?
[AIKA] Why not?
[JIRO] Plus, I don't have a condom.
[AIKA] Then just do it raw.
[JIRO] Huh? R-raw?
[AIKA] Happy?
[JIRO] Yes.
[AIKA] Kanako wouldn't let you do her raw, right?
[AIKA] See? Nothing's between us.
[AIKA] It's okay to put it in, right?
[JIRO] Wait, it's going...
[AIKA] I'm putting it in.
[AIKA] Okay?
[JIRO] It's going in.
[AIKA] It went in. You were too late.
[AIKA] Does it feel good?
[JIRO] Y-yes.
[AIKA] Feels good? Then how about this?
[JIRO] My voice will come out.
[JIRO] Be quiet.
[AIKA] I did it.
[AIKA] Don't worry. She's deep asleep.
[AIKA] Come on, keep going.
[AIKA] This is bad. Feels too good.
[AIKA] As expected, my voice will come out.
[AIKA] All because of your dick.
[AIKA] Feels good.
[AIKA] I feel like cumming.
[AIKA] I'm cumming.
[AIKA] It's okay, we'll be fine.
[JIRO] No, you can't...
[AIKA] Oh man, let's change the angle for a bit.
[AIKA] This feels good too.
[AIKA] I love how this feels.
[AIKA] Feels really good.
[AIKA] Oh dear, my voice might come out.
[AIKA] I can't stop.
[JIRO] Wait...
[AIKA] Oh dear... getting close...
[JIRO] We'll be discovered at this rate...
[AIKA] Man, this feels great.
[AIKA] Gonna cum...
[AIKA] Cumming...
[AIKA] Feels so good.
[AIKA]  Hey, get up.
[JIRO] Yes.
[AIKA] And do me from behind.
[AIKA] It's okay. Just don't make a sound.
[JIRO] Ah, yes.
[AIKA] This is the best.
[AIKA] Right there. Try hitting there.
[AIKA] This feels great.
[AIKA] Can't hold it...
[AIKA] Feels good...!
[AIKA] That's the spot. Keep going.
[AIKA] Gonna cum...
[AIKA] Cumming. I'm cumming.
[AIKA] Doggy style's incredible. Let's do it again.
[AIKA] Stand up.
[AIKA] Oh man...
[AIKA] This feels great.
[AIKA] Does this feel good?
[JIRO] Yes.
[AIKA] You didn't want to but here you are shaking your hips.
[JIRO] But that’s...
[AIKA] We're in such a bad situation...
[AIKA] Amazing.
[AIKA] Oh dear, this feels good.
[AIKA] What are you regretting for?
[AIKA] Don't make too much noise.
[AIKA] Oh dear... I'm gonna cum...
[AIKA] Oh man...
[AIKA] Gonna cum...
[AIKA] I'm cumming...
[AIKA] Wasn't that the best? Huh?
[AIKA] How was it?
[AIKA] Addicted to doing it raw now?
[AIKA]
[JIRO] I can't help it. I'm sorry.
[AIKA] It's fine.
[AIKA] You really like boobs, huh?
[AIKA] Why did you stop?
[KANAKO] Jiro-kun... I love you...
[AIKA] She said she loves you.
[JIRO] I'm sorry.
[AIKA] But the one you're making love to is me.
[AIKA] What an amazing dick...
[AIKA] We've been doing it for awhile. You can cum, too, you know?
[AIKA] But isn't it bad to cum inside you?
[AIKA] Why not? Don't you want to cum inside me?
[AIKA] I'm fine with you cumming inside me.
[AIKA] So cute. It's okay to cum.
[AIKA] Come on. Do it.
[AIKA] It's your choice.
[JIRO] I'll do it.
[JIRO] I can't... hold it!!!
[AIKA] He came inside me with you here.
[AIKA] Eat.
[JIRO] Sorry that you have to make breakfast for me.
[AIKA] Oh, it's fine. Unlike my appearance, I'm actually quite good at this kind of stuff.
[JIRO] Uh, yes.
[KANAKO] Big sis, I'm sorry you had to prepare breakfast.
[AIKA] Oh, it's no big deal.
[KANAKO] I drank too much last night. I'm sorry.
[KANAKO] I'm sorry to you too, Jiro-kun.
[AIKA] Then let's eat!
[EVERYONE] Thanks for the food!
[AIKA] Oh, clumsy me...
[KANAKO] Jiro-kun, what's wrong?
[JIRO] No, nothing. It's delicious.
[KANAKO] Yes, it's great.
[KANAKO] Big sis, you okay?
[AIKA] Yeah, I'm okay.
[AIKA] I wonder where it went?
[KANAKO] Need any help?
[AIKA] No, it's fine. I can look for it myself. You go ahead and eat.
[KANAKO] Hmm, got it.
[KANAKO] Who is it?
[KANAKO] Coming!
[JIRO] You can't! Stop!
[JIRO] She'll see us when she comes back.
[AIKA] It's fine.
[AIKA] You're hard already.
[JIRO] No, that's...
[AIKA] She'll hear us if you make that sound!
[AIKA] Wow, it's so hard!
[AIKA] It's fine.
[AIKA] Feels good.
[AIKA] It'll be really bad if she comes back.
[JIRO] Then we should stop.
[AIKA] Not stopping~
[AIKA] You feel great.
[AIKA] Now this one.
[AIKA] I want to do it again.
[AIKA] Put it right here.
[JIRO] This is bad. This is really bad.
[AIKA] It's okay. She hasn't returned yet.
[AIKA] Feels good, huh.
[AIKA] It's all erect now.
[AIKA] Were you remembering about last night?
[AIKA] Ah, how about I use the boobs you love so much to give your dick a titjob?
[AIKA] See?
[AIKA] Does it feel good?
[AIKA] It's making a such a wet sound.
[AIKA] Wow, it's this hard.
[AIKA] How is it?
[JIRO] This is bad...
[AIKA] How about right here?
[AIKA] Does it feel good?
[AIKA] You can't hold it, right?
[AIKA] It's so hard.
[AIKA] It looks like you're feel pretty good.
[AIKA] Oh, how hard.
[AIKA] Why did you get this hard?
[AIKA] Oh, is it because you're going to cum soon?
[JIRO] No, uhh...
[AIKA] Won't it be bad if you cum right now?
[AIKA] Really bad, right?
[AIKA] Can you hold it in?
[JIRO] Ah, that's...
[AIKA] Can you hold it?
[JIRO] Oh no, I can't...
[AIKA] You cumming?
[AIKA] Ah, you came.
[AIKA] My boobs are covered with semen.
[AIKA] She'll find out if we don't clean this up.
[AIKA] Who was it?
[KANAKO] Community announcement.
[AIKA] Ah, I see.
[AIKA] Did you sign it?
[KANAKO] Yeah.
[KANAKO] Did you find the fork?
[AIKA] Yeah, got it.
[KANAKO] Oh, good.
[AIKA] What's wrong?
[JIRO] No. Let's eat.
[AIKA] Hey... heeey...!
[JIRO] Huh, what?
[KANAKO] You didn't shower yesterday, right?
[JIRO] No.
[KANAKO] Let's take a shower.
[KANAKO] Let's go shower. Here, this way.
[KANAKO] Come on already.
[JIRO] Uh, yeah.
[KANAKO] Bathing together kind of makes your heart race, right?
[KANAKO] Hey.
[JIRO] What is it?
[KANAKO] Take it off for me.
[KANAKO] Come on.
[KANAKO] And?
[KANAKO] Yay.
[JIRO] I'm taking it off.
[KANAKO] Hmm.
[JIRO] I was just thinking how beautiful your breasts are.
[KANAKO] R-really?
[JIRO] Yeah.
[KANAKO] I'm so happy. Really? Thank you.
[JIRO] Now the panties.
[KANAKO] It's so embarrassing.
[KANAKO] Then I'm going in first.
[JIRO] Okay.
[KANAKO] Quickly get in after me, okay?
[JIRO] Got it.
[JIRO] What in the... w-what are you doing?
[JIRO] Kanako's still in there.
[KANAKO] It's fine. She's taking a shower.
[JIRO] Ah, but... you can't... this is bad.
[AIKA] It's perfectly fine.
[AIKA] What?
[JIRO] We'll really be discovered.
[AIKA] Nope, we won't.
[AIKA] Shall we?
[JIRO] No...
[AIKA] Why?
[JIRO] But I...
[AIKA] It's all hard and ready go to though.
[KANAKO] Hey, Jiro-kun, you done yet?
[KANAKO] Hey!
[JIRO] Wait, I'm having a hard time taking this off. I'll come in soon. Wait for me.
[JIRO] I'm sor-
[KANAKO] Hurry up, okay?
[AIKA] See, she didn't find out.
[AIKA] You're this big already. Don't you want to cum soon?
[JIRO] What do I do?
[AIKA] Why are you getting this big before taking a shower?
[JIRO] No, that's...
[AIKA] It's because you saw Kanako's  breasts.
[AIKA] Right here.
[AIKA] Does it feel good?
[AIKA] Don't you like breasts?
[AIKA] Wanna see them?
[JIRO] No, I...
[AIKA] They're big.
[JIRO] No, but...
[JIRO] We'll definitely be discovered.
[AIKA] We won't. Not if we finish this fast.
[JIRO] Ah, but...
[AIKA] Wanna see them? You do, no?
[AIKA] It's okay to touch them.
[JIRO] She'll totally find out if you're this loud.
[AIKA] Aren't you over thinking it?
[JIRO] No, but...
[AIKA] She can't hear us anyway.
[AIKA] What a face you're making after seeing my breasts.
[AIKA] Does it feel good?
[AIKA] It got really hard.
[KANAKO] Hey, Jiro-kun, you done yet?
[JIRO] Sorry, I'm brushing my teeth right now, because I'll be giving you lots of kisses later.
[KANAKO] Hurry up, okay?
[AIKA] Oh, really?
[JIRO] No, no more. She'll really find out.
[AIKA] What are you talking about? Your breath still stinks.
[AIKA] Take it off. You'll going to take a shower anyway.
[JIRO] Ah, yes.
[AIKA] Come on.
[JIRO] Yes.
[AIKA] You still brushing your teeth?
[JIRO] Ah, sorry.
[AIKA] How cute.
[AIKA] Ah, right.
[JIRO] What are you doing?
[AIKA] Does this feel good?
[AIKA] It's throbbing.
[AIKA] I'll make you feel good with the breasts you love so much.
[AIKA] It's super hard.
[AIKA] Does it feel good?
[AIKA] I feel really good.
[AIKA] It's really hard.
[AIKA] So hard.
[AIKA] It can't get any harder.
[AIKA] Can you still hold it in?
[AIKA] It really is so hard.
[AIKA] Jiro, does this feel good?
[JIRO] No, I...
[AIKA] Does it feel good?
[AIKA] If you keep holding it in, we'll be discovered.
[AIKA] It's so hard.
[AIKA] How hard.
[JIRO] Ah, Onee-San, wait...
[AIKA] What is it?
[AIKA] Did you cum again?
[AIKA] Geez.
[AIKA] We'll continue this later, okay?
[AIKA] See ya!
[KANAKO] Come on...
[JIRO] Sorry, sorry.
[KANAKO] Done yet?
[JIRO] I'm all done. I'm going in.
[KANAKO] Come on in.
[AIKA] He got a pair.
[KANAKO] Then this one.
[AIKA] How was it? Still nothing?
[AIKA] Which one...
[AIKA] This one.
[AIKA] Got it.
[AIKA] How fun!
[AIKA] Is it mom?
[KANAKO] Hello?
[KANAKO] Huh? That was a while ago.
[KANAKO] Sorry, it's mom.
[AIKA] This is our chance.
[JIRO] No...
[JIRO] Wait, she'll find out.
[AIKA] It's fine. She's on the phone.
[JIRO] No, no, no...
[AIKA] It's okay.
[JIRO] This is too risky.
[AIKA] It's fine.
[AIKA] Your hands are in the way.
[AIKA] Why is it hard already?
[JIRO] No, that's...
[AIKA] Stick out your tongue.
[AIKA] Do you think she can hear this?
[AIKA] It's okay.
[JIRO] But...
[AIKA] You already saw them earlier.
[AIKA] Go ahead. Don't stop.
[AIKA] This feels good.
[AIKA] Hey...
[AIKA] All the way.
[JIRO] But...
[JIRO] Wait, wait, you can't take it off.
[AIKA] What are you worried about?
[AIKA] Get up.
[AIKA] Come on now.
[AIKA] Lick it.
[AIKA] Come on already.
[AIKA] This feels good.
[AIKA] Hey, touch my nipples.
[AIKA] Feels good...!
[AIKA] Feels really good.
[AIKA] Oh man.
[AIKA] Amazing.
[AIKA] I'm feel like cumming again.
[AIKA] This feels good.
[AIKA] I'm close.
[AIKA] I'm cumming!
[AIKA] That was the best.
[AIKA] Let me see your dick.
[AIKA] Doesn't It make your heart race when you don't know when she'll be tired of talking?
[AIKA] Yet you're still so erect here.
[AIKA] Now come rub your dick against my nipples.
[AIKA] Touch them.
[AIKA] I love how this feels.
[JIRO] Amazing.
[AIKA] Touch my pussy, too.
[AIKA] Hey, come touch it...
[AIKA] This feels great.
[AIKA] It feels good.
[AIKA] Gonna cum...
[AIKA] Cumming!
[AIKA] It feels good.
[AIKA] Want to put it in?
[AIKA] You want to do it raw, right?
[JIRO] This is... but...
[AIKA] Don't you?
[AIKA] You don't want to?
[JIRO] It's not that I don't want it...
[AIKA] How cute.
[AIKA] I feel like letting out my voice.
[AIKA] Why not?
[JIRO] No, that's...
[AIKA] Feels so good.
[AIKA] Feels good.
[AIKA] Come touch.
[AIKA] You feel great.
[AIKA] Wow, look how hard it is.
[AIKA] I love how this feels.
[AIKA] It feels good.
[AIKA] Oh dear, I can't hold in my voice anymore.
[AIKA] I can feel how hard you're getting.
[AIKA] You're face tells me you're feeling good.
[AIKA] Does my pussy feel good?
[AIKA] Doesn't doing it raw feel great?
[JIRO] Y-yes, it does.
[AIKA] Good.
[AIKA] You can't cum yet.
[AIKA] It's so stiff.
[AIKA] I don't want to go slow.
[AIKA] I want to cum as soon as possible.
[JIRO] No, you can't.
[AIKA] Why can't I make some noise?
[JIRO] We'll be discovered...
[AIKA] We'll be found out?
[AIKA] Tell me, what kind of sound would reveal us?
[JIRO] No, stop...
[AIKA] Like this?
[JIRO] Hey...
[AIKA] It's so hard.
[AIKA] So stiff.
[AIKA] But you still can't cum yet.
[AIKA] Feels good...!
[AIKA] That was the best.
[AIKA] She still hasn't found out, even with all the sounds we made.
[JIRO] Anymore than this...
[AIKA] Doesn't this feel good?
[AIKA] Even though you keep denying it.
[AIKA] This feels good.
[AIKA] It's hitting some amazing places.
[AIKA] Oh man...
[AIKA] Feels good...!
[AIKA] My voice...!
[AIKA] Not yet. Only when you absolutely can't hold it anymore.
[AIKA] Oh crap...
[AIKA] Gonna cum soon.
[AIKA] I'M CUMMING!
[AIKA] I let my voice out.
[AIKA] She's finally tired of talking.
[JIRO] This isn't how it looks!
[KANAKO] Big sis, what are you doing?
[AIKA] It's all because you never let him do you raw.
[AIKA] Hey, isn't that so?
[JIRO] No, ahhh...
[KANAKO] What ...!
[JIRO] This isn't...!
[AIKA] It's exactly how it looks. You were holding back for so long.
[JIRO] No...
[AIKA] Hurry, get up.
[AIKA] Let's show her how great raw sex feels.
[AIKA] Come on.
[AIKA] Hurry up.
[JIRO] This is bad. This is...
[AIKA] Just let it go and fuck me.
[JIRO] W-w-wait...
[AIKA] You can't get nervous after coming all this way.
[AIKA] It went in.
[AIKA] Raw sex feels great, right?
[AIKA] Still haven't taken off your shirt?
[AIKA] Whatever, just keep going.
[AIKA] It feels great, right?
[JIRO] Kanako, I'm sorry!
[AIKA] You're thrusting your dick with Kanako right here.
[AIKA] You haven't had enough at all.
[JIRO] No, that's...
[AIKA] After all, I know how to make you feel good.
[AIKA] This feels good.
[JIRO] Kanako, I'm sorry!
[AIKA] You'll cum soon, right?
[AIKA] You feel great.
[AIKA] Keep pounding my insides.
[AIKA] Right there! Amazing...
[AIKA] Kanako, I'm really sorry!
[JIRO] This is really...
[AIKA] This feels so good you can't hold in your voice, huh.
[AIKA] Hurry up and keep going.
[AIKA] Hurry up and finish this.
[AIKA] It feels good.
[AIKA] Ah, right there.
[AIKA] Feels so good.
[AIKA] Oh man.
[AIKA] I love how this feels.
[AIKA] Amazing...
[AIKA] That's the spot...
[AIKA] Oh man, oh man...
[AIKA] Amazing...
[AIKA] This could be really bad.
[AIKA] I'm cumming!
[AIKA] You can't stop yet.
[AIKA] Your face tells me you're feeling great.
[AIKA] Hey, Kanako, come see.
[AIKA] Turn your face.
[AIKA] You have to look at this face.
[AIKA] She doesn't want to look.
[AIKA] This feels really though.
[AIKA] Ah, I broke her.
[AIKA] Show me more of your faces expressions.
[AIKA] Do it from behind this time.
[AIKA] Kanako, are you taking a good look?
[AIKA] This feels great.
[AIKA] Amazing...
[AIKA] Grab me.
[AIKA] Amazing.
[AIKA] Going to cum again.
[AIKA] More! More! More...!
[AIKA] Cumming...!
[AIKA] You feel great.
[AIKA] Oh dear...
[AIKA] I'm cumming!
[AIKA] That felt great.
[AIKA] Lie down.
[AIKA] You can just stay there and watch.
[AIKA] This is what a cowgirl position look like.
[AIKA] Let's do it rougher.
[AIKA] I love how this feels.
[AIKA] Does it feel good?
[AIKA] As expected, you like this position more.
[AIKA] You found us out because I let out my voice using this position.
[AIKA] Are you sure you don't want to take a good look?
[AIKA] Feels so good.
[AIKA] Oh jeez...
[AIKA] Amazing...!
[AIKA] I'm cumming!
[AIKA] Are you about to cum?
[AIKA] Come on, show me more.
[AIKA] If you can't hold it anymore, you can just cum inside me.
[AIKA] Feels good...!
[AIKA] Reached your limit?
[AIKA] As expected, this feels so good.
[AIKA] It feels good.
[JIRO] Gonna cum...!
[AIKA] That's fine...
[JIRO] Cumming...!
[AIKA] Cumming!
[AIKA] Really amazing.
[AIKA] Let's see.
[AIKA] Is it dripping out?
[AIKA] Aww, it felt so good.
[AIKA] We have great sexual compatibility don't we?
(Translated by allenallenallen333)