PLEASE DO NOT REUPLOAD
JAV SUB BY (at)BONEKACE
FIND MORE SUB AT JAVSUBTITLES.COM
Seitou ni Jitaku wo Nottorareta Wakazuma Kyoushi.
Teacher Wife Beautiful Wife Hijacked Home To Students Turn Into Slave Pet
Moshi moshi, ant?
Hello, darling?
Ah, korekara Fukuoka nano?
Ah, you will depart to Fukuoka now?
Ah, sou nano. Korekara koujou dane.
Then you will go to the factory. I see.
Shucchou nanoni taihenne.
Looks like will be a hard business trip.
E, kocchi?
Me?
Sou nano, kore kara seitoutachi ga kuru no.
Yes, my students will come to study here.
Anata ni wa kansha shiteru yo.
It's very thankful to you.
Shucchou de no mikkakan...
Three days when you went off...
...ie de hoshuu jugyou sasete kureru koto yurushite kurete.
...you let me to do extra class over here.
Arigatou.
I'm very thankful.
Ii yo, minna ii kotachi bakkari dakara.
It's okay, they all good students.
Dakara watashi mo isshokenmei oshienakya ikenai to ne.
So I do have to teach them properly.
Daijoubu yo. Atashi mo kore demo sannenme dakara.
This is my third year being a teacher. It's okay.
Nande oretachi ga hoshuu jugyou nandana.
Why just three of us have to take extra class.
Sou dayo, benkyou dattara gakkou dake de iiyo.
Yeah, learning at school is enough for us.
Seiseki nanka doudemo iinda.
I don't care with my school grade.
Ah, mendoukuse.
Ah, what a troublesome.
Sore dattara sa...
If like that...
Kore wo Ookita ni tsukatte itazura shiyou ze.
Let's do some prank to Ookita using this.
Nani sore?
What's that?
Shiriai kara moratta kusuri nandakedo sa.
I got this medicine from my friend.
Kore wo tsukattara ippatsu de nagai rashii ze.
If using this, we can do sex for hours.
Maji ka? Sore ii jan.
Really? That's great.
Sugee omoshirosou jan.
Looks interesting.
Dakara kore tsukatte asobou kana tte omou sa.
Let's play with her after using this.
*both speaking*
Okita no yatsu sa, kyou danna shucchou rashii nanda.
I heard that Okita's husband is going for business trip today.
Dakara koitsu wo tsukatte...
That's why today we use this...
...ame mo kuidase.
...and do her.
Ore nanka tanoshiku natte kita.
I'm feels very excited.
Mou chanto yasai wo tabenai to.
You should eat some vegetables too.
Seitotachi ga mou kita mitai. Sorosoro kiru ne.
My students already came. I will hang up phone.
Oshigoto ganbatte ne.
Wish tons of lucks for your job.
Ja mata ne. Baibai.
See you. Bye bye.
Hai.
Yes.
Ah, irasshai. Douzo agatte.
Ah, welcome. Come in.
Ojamashimasu. / Hai.
Excuse me. / Yes.
Sensei, chotto kore wakannain desukedo.
Miss, I don't know this question.
"He is the man" tte koto wa "man" ga hito dakara kono ato wa daitai "Who?" ga kuru yo.
A word "man" from "He is the man" refers to a human, so the right question for it is "Who?".
Ah, "Who?".
Oh, "Who?".
"That" wo omo ni nacchaun dattara...
If you add "that" to this question...
Koko desu ka? / "Who?", sou sou.
Over here? / Yes, put after "Who?".
"Who is...?" sono ato ushiro ni tsukete.
You can add it after "Who is...?".
Sou sou sou. / "Who is that man?".
Yes yes. / "Who is that man?".
Sensei, kore wa desu ne...
Miss, how about this one...
Ah soko wa ne mazu nagareta...
Ah that's question, you have to look this question first...
*speaking english*
Sensei, dekimashita.
Miss, I'm done.
Huwa, Yoshida kun sugoi janai. Chanto benkyou shite kita mon ne.
Uwa, Yoshida you are very great. Look like you've studied at home.
Ah, kuwashii.
Ah you are vey detail.
Koko made dekirun dattara, ja tsugi wa mou chotto muzukashii no yatte mimashouka ne.
If you did it until here, how about try to do more difficult questions?
Ja tsugi wa sono mondai san wo yatte mite.
Try to do this part 3 questions.
*mumbling*
Ah, tsukareta.
Ah, I'm so tired.
Tsukareta.
I'm tired.
Nande eigo de benkyou shinakya ikenai na...
Why whe should learn English...
Hontou dayo.
That's right.
Sonna koto iwanaide yo. Mou sukoshi ganbarimashou.
Don't say that. Let;s do our best a lil bit more.
Demo sanzan tsukareta yo. Genaki. Kyuukei shiyou kyuukei.
But we are evry tired. It's limit. Let's take a break.
Wakarimashita. Ja kyuukei ni shimashou.
I understand. Let's take some break.
Yatta. / Hontou? Ya, te ga mou ugokenaku natte sa...
Yeay. / Really? I can't move my hands anymore...
*three boys speaking*
Ja minna no tame ni nomimono irete agemashou ka.
I will make some drinks for you all.
Yeay. Arigatou gozaimasu sensei.
Yeay. Thank you very much, Miss.
Ureshii. Tsukarechatta  yo na...
That's relief. I'm very tired...
Sensei dore gurai kyuukei shite ii no?
How long we can take break, Miss?
Juppun juugofun de. / Sonna ni?
Ten or fifteen minutes. / That much?
Yatta.
Yeay.
Ah, chotto...
Ah, wait...
*mumbling*
Ah sugee. / Kikun ka yo.
Ah, great. / Is that work?
Sensei.
Miss.
Okirou yo.
Wkae up.
Doushita no?
What happened?
Nani?
What?
Chotto.
Hey.
Nani kore. Hodokinasai yo kore.
What's this. Untie this, please.
Sensei.
Miss.
Oretachi ni...
Don't make joke to us...
...hoshuu nanka sasete jane zo.
...with this shit extra class.
Sou dayo.
Yeah.
Ii meiwaku nandayo kocchi ni yo.
That's very troublesome for us.
Eigo nante ore nanka kyoumi neendayo. / Chotto...chotto...
We don;t have any interest on English. / Wait...wait...
Chotto nani itteru no?
What did you said?
Chotto hayaku kore hodokinasai yo.
Untie this now. Hurry.
Danna san ga ie ni inakute...
Your husband is not at home...
...sabishiin janai ka? / Nani itteru no yo.
...doesn't you feels lonely? / What the hell you said?
Nani itteru no yo.
What the hell you said?
Okita san...
Miss Okita...
Oaite ni shimasu yo. / Chotto.
I will be your "husband". / Wait.
Yamenasai yo . Kore hazushinasai.
Stop itt. Take this shit off.
Chotto yamete yo.
Hey, stop this.
Yamenasai.
Stop it.
Yamenasai...
Stop it...
Oretachi ni hoshuu sasete batsu dayo.
You wrong for make  extra class for us.
Yamenasai.
Stop it.
Tashika ni omaera mo sawatteru sou.
Yeah both of you touch her too.
*both speaking* / Yamenasai.
*both speaking* / Stop it.
*three boys speaking*
Konna koto yamenasai yo.
Please stop this.
Chotto kore wo...
Wait, this is...
Yamete. Nani yatteru no? / Shashin totte iissuka?
Stop. What are you doing? / Can I take your picture?
Dame yo. Nani yatteru no. Yamete.
Don't do that. What are you doing. Stop.
Shashin tottocchau.
I will take your picture.
Jibuntachi mo. / Chotto yamete.
Take it with us. / Hey, wait.
Hazurerundattara saisho kara suru na.
You should not make that extra class at first.
Sugoi na. / Dame, chotto.
Oh, great. / No, stop it.
Yamenasai...yamete...
Stop...stop...
Ya...iya...
No...No...
Chotto...
Wait...
Kore toru yo.
I will take this too.
Dame, kora! Yamenasai.
No, Stop it bastard! Stop it.
Hontou ni yawarakai yo kore. / Ookii yo, sensei.
This one very soft. / It's big boobs, Miss.
Yamete.
Stop it.
Kyou wa daijoubu dakara ne, sensei.
Today it's okay to do it, right?
Mechakucha yawarakai na.
This is very soft.
Sore ja oppai mo torou ka?
Let's take this boobs pictures.
Ii ne. / Yamete yamete yamete.
Good. / Stop stop stop.
Hora, ii kao shite yo sensei.
Come on, make a good face Miss.
Sensei no oppai.
My teacher's boobs.
Minna ni okuttara dou naru no kana. / Yamete.
What will happen if I send this to all. / Don't do that.
Katakunacchau yo kore. / Ii kao misero yo.
Your nippels is getting hard. / Show us your good face, Miss.
Oh, sugee na.
Oh, this great.
*mumbling*
Chotto matte, osamari dekirun desu ne kore wa.
Wait a minute, I have to make this pone settled first.
Kirei dana kore.
This one is beautiful.
Zutto mae kara oopai sawaritakattan dayo.
I want to touch your booobs since before.
Yamete yamete...
Stop stop...
Chotto kocchi koi yo.
Move here.
Nanka sugee yo.
This great.
Okita sensei kocchi mite.
Miss Okita look at here.
Hora sensei kocchi mina yo.
Hey Miss, look at here.
Kocchi dayo. Kurosawatachi mo kurundayo.
Look at here. Kurosawa and friends will come too.
Nani itteno yo, yamete yo. / Nani? Namete hoshii no?
What did you said? / What? You want me lick it?
Yamete.
Stop.
Kissu shiro yo.
Kiss me.
Hai, tsugi ore ore.
Next is me.
Ah, suge suge.
Ah, this great.
Kocchi ni shite.
Take this one too.
Dame, dame, dame. / Hazukashigaranaide.
No...no...no. / Don't be shy.
Yamete.
Stop.
Mechakucha attameteru.
It's really warm here.
Yamete, iya.
No, don't.
Ii na. Chotto kore totte.
This good. Hey take this one too.
Ah, dame dame.
Ah, No no.
Chotto yamete.
Wait, stop.
Hora sensei.
Hey, Miss don't move.
Sugee.
Great.
Sugee na kore.
This one is great.
Ah, dame.
Ah, No.
Yamenasai yo.
Please stop it.
Motto misero yo sensei.
Show us more, Miss.
Chotto.
Don't.
Nanka nureteru yo, sensei. / Sensei no omanko konna ni nuretenno yo.
Your pussy is wet. / You pussy looks very wet, Miss.
Sugee na.
This is great.
Ah, yamete.
Ah, stop it.
Hora motto misero yo. / Hora hora...
Hey, show us more. / Hey...hey...
Ah sugee. / Dou natterun dayo, chotto.
Ah great. / Wait, what should we do.
Yamete.
Stop it.
Dame. / Dou dou?
Don't. / How how?
Sensei, namerareteru tokoro tottoku kara. / Oi, sensei.
I will take picture when he licked you. / Hey, Miss.
Dou desu ka sensei? Kou yatte nameteru no kimochi iin deshou?
How is it, Miss? Being licked like this, feels good, huh?
Ureshii? Ne?
You like it? Huh?
Sensei ureshii?
Are you like it, Miss?
Ah, dou nandayo. / Ie yo.
Ah, how is it? / Say it.
Oretachi ni namete moratte ureshiin darou?
You like it when we lick you like this, right?
Mou chotto mite kudasai, kocchi mite yo.
Hey, look at here, look.
Hirakasun dayo, see no.
Let's spreadi it, here we go.
Hirake.
Spread it.
Hirake. / Oh, sugee.
Spread it. / Oh, wow.
Yariyasui ne. / Iya.
It's more easy to lick it. / No.
Kao kakusun janee yo sensei.
Don't hide your face, Miss.
Kore wa ii ne.
This is great.
Kore okuttara minna yorokobu yo.
Everybody will be happy if we send this.
Ii ssu yo . / Chotto hiroge.
It's okay. / Spread it.
Oh, sugee na. / Konna natterunda.
Oh, this great. / It's look like this, huh.
Chotto kore de kinnen de sa, tetteiteki na shashin torou ze.
Let's take a thoroughgoing pictures as a memories.
Ah, kaeru ze kore de.
Ah, let's change pose.
Sensei, hora oide yo.
Come here, Miss.
Hora.
Come on.
Hai sensei oretachi omukai no hazukashii kakkou shite yaru yo.
Let's do pose "We are come to pick up you".
Sensei kocchi miro yo.
Look at here, Miss.
Hora hora hora.
Hey hey hey.
Pissu dero. Oh, ii ne.
Peace mark. Oh, great.
Ah sensei maji ne konna no.
This is great, right?
Kore gakkou no sensei toka okuttara dou naru no kana. / Dame yo.
How about we send this pictures to another teachers? / No, don't.
*mumbling*
Zettai kubi dayo.
They will fire you.
*both speaking*
*mumbling*
Motto sensei to naka yoku naritaindayo oretachi,.
We just want to be closer to you, Miss.
Yamete. / Hora hora kocchi muite.
Stop. / Hey hey, look at here.
Waratte waratte sensei.
Smile, Miss.
Waratte yo, hora.
Come one, smile.
Ah, sugee.
Ah, great.
Chotto manko sawatte manko sawatte.
Touch her pussy, touch it.
Ah, ochita yo./ Ah, dame datte.
Ah, it's dropped down. / Ah, I said don't.
Manko sawatte dame.
Don't touch it.
Sensei...
Miss...
Sugee haicchatta yo...
I got it into your pussy...
Matte matte hora, zenbu hairun dayo kore.
Wait...look this, it's all can entered in.
Sugee.
Great.
Konna sugee no kana.
I don't know it's great.
Yamete.
Stop it.
Oh, suge suge.
Oh, great.
Sugee.
Great.
Maji ka yo.
Seriously.
Chotto sa.
Take this.
Naka demo mireru yo.
You can see inside it.
Sensei no naka konna natterun da.
Inside your pussy is great.
Ippai irechaou ka.
Let's put it in more.
Irete hoshii na, sensei.
I want to fuck you.
Eigo no benkyou nanka kocchi no hou ga yaku ni tatsu yo ne.
It's more useful to learn this than English, right Miss?
Ne, sensei mo kimochi ii no?
You are feels it good, Miss?
Dou yana...
Dunno...
Sugoi shiru detenjan kore.
The precum came out so much.
Sensei manko shimittenno.
Your pussy really wet, Miss.
Sugee.
Great.
Sensei dou nandayo. / Nanka ie yo.
How is it, Miss? / Say something.
Nanka na, naka butsubutsu shiteru.
It's feels pimply inside here.
Sensei kimochi ii? Kimochi ii no?
Is it feels good, Miss? Do you feel it?
Saki to koe ga chigau nanka.
Your voice is different than before.
Motto motto yacchatte.
Do it more.
Chanto oshiete yo.
Tell us.
Yame yamete...
Stop...stop it...
Ah, yamete.
Ah, stop it.
Kore gurai haitte kitenne.
It just come inside this long.
Mite goran. / Sensei, sore nantte iu no?
Look. / What is that called, Miss?
Hora kore namero.
Hey, lick it.
Konna jiru ga deta sensei.
This precum is yours, Miss.
Ne, sensei.
Hey, Miss.
Oretachi no mo sa...
Lick our dick...
...kouiu fuu ni namete yo.
...like you lick this.
Yaracchatte iin desu yo, kou yatte.
Do it, like you lick this.
Ne oretachi mo shite yo, ne Sensei.
Hey, lick our dick too, Miss.
Kou iu juugyoumo oshiete yo.
You should teach us this kind of lecture.
Shite kure yo, sensei.
Do it. Lick our dick, Miss.
Hora, nigeru na yo sensei. Kanben shite yo.
Hey, don't run away. Do it properly.
Chanto tottiote ageru kara sa.
I will take picture when you do it.
Kocchi muite yo, hora.
Hey, look at here.
Kocchi muite yo.
Turn your face here.
Yoshi yoshi, sensei shagutte kurete.
Come on Miss, suck it.
Ne sensei, kore wo kuwaete.
Hey Miss, suck this.
Sensei, kuwaete nameru no tte docchi demo iissu yo.
You can suck it or lick it, Miss.
Dekinai no? / Chanto yatte yo sensei.
You can't do it? / Do it, Miss.
Ne yatte yo. / Shouganee na.
Hey, do it. / Ah, it can't be helped.
Nande dekinai no?
Why you can't do it?
Sensei yatte kurenainja mou, ima made no shame okuru shika nai na.
If you don't do it, I will send that pictures of you.
A, sou dana. Yatte kurenai mon na.
Ah, yeah right. She will not do it either.
Sou da. / Dakara yatte tte itten jan.
Yeah. / That's why I said do it, bitch.
Yatte kurenai no?
Still won't do it?
Yare  yo.
Do it.
Kuchi akete.
Open your mouth.
Aan mo dekinainda.
You can't just open your mouth?
Dekinai nara mou shouganai na.
If you not open it I will send this pictures then.
Yamete...dame, dame.
Stop...No, no.
Aitsu sasotta kara. / Maji ka yo. Aitsu dattara sugu kurunjanai no.
Ijust called him. / Really? He will come here anytime.
Ah, yamete. / Maji de mucha janai yo ima no.
Ah, stop it. / I'm not joking with that.
Sensei ga yatte kurenai nara mou dondon ninsuu fueru kara.
If you not do that Miss, I will call another one.
Yaru chanto.
Do it, properly.
Hora, yaru no? Dou nano?
Hey, will you do it? Or not?
Ii yo betsu ni yaranakutemo, dondon ninsuu ga fueru kara ne.
It's okay if you don't want to do it. But we will call another one to come.
Hora.
Come on.
Hai, zenin yonde. / Hai, hai zenin.
Okay, call them all. / Yeah call them.
O, ii ne.
O, good boy.
Ii ne.
You good.
Ii no, sensei? / Ah, sensei sugoi shagutteru yan.
Isn't that great,Miss? / Ah, you suck me good.
Sugee jan, sensei wa.
You are very good on this, Miss.
Kore chanto totte okan to.
I have to take this one.
Sugee shinjiranee.
I can't believe this.
Nande yo sensei. Kurasu no zenin yonda hou ga tanoshikute omoshiroi to omou kedo na.
Why we can't call another one on class, Miss? It will be fun.
Dame nano?
Can't we?
Sensei ga yonde hoshii tte yuu nara. / Yonde mo heiki ne.
If you loved to call them all too, we will call them. / We will call them.
Yonde hoshikunai no?
You don't want we call them all?
Chanto yannai to, hora. Chanto yatte goran.
Then you should do it properly. Do it, Miss.
Chanto yatte yo, hora.
Do it, come on.
Sou da. Ah, ii ne sensei.
Yeah like that. Ah, that's good.
Ah, dekinjan sensei.
Ah, you can do it, aren't you?
Ah, yaru nara dekinjan sensei.
You can do it at least if you try.
*mumbling*
Ureshisou na kao de yatte yo.
Make happy face when you do it.
Ah,ii kao janai.
Ah, good face.
Ah, mou gaman dekinai ore mo.
I can't resist it anymore.
Sensei, ore no mo onegai. / Sugee sokkuri dane.
Sensei, suck mine too. / Ah, it's look alike each other.
Ne, hora...hora.
Hey, come on...here.
Kuwaete miro.
Suck this.
Sensei, ah ii yo.
Oh my God.
Ah, sugee.
Ah, great.
Sensei...
Miss...
Ah, kimochi ii.
Ah, feels good.
Sensei, iu koto kiku chanto.
Listen everythings I say, Miss.
Kiku?
You will listen?
Oi, kao agete goran.
Hey, raise your head.
Iu koto kiku?
You will do what I say?
Hora.
Hey.
Iu koto kikanakattara...
If you not do what I say...
...hontou ni shashin okuru yo.
...I will send this whole pictures.
Baramau kara ne. Nigenaide yo.
Don't run away, I will expose everyhting we did.
Dondon ninsuu fuechau yo.
Then people in here will increase.
Kocchi de mo sawatte goran. / Sore ii kao ne, sensei.
Touch my dick too. / That's very good face, Miss.
Hora.
Come on.
Ah, gaman dekinai.
Ah, I can't resist it anymore.
Omae mo kuwaesasete yo.
Let her suck yours too.
Sensei yorokobu kara sa.
She will do it with pleasure.
Sensei kuwaitai tte.
She said she want to suck it.
Sou dane, Sensei.
It's right, Miss?
Chigau no?
No?
Sensei shame okutte, jiman shite ii yo.
I will send this pictures, and you can be proud on it.
Ne, ii deshou?
Hey, it's okay right?
Ja iu koto kiiten no?
Then you will do what I say?
Ii ne. / Sensei mo ureshii sshou?
Great. / You are happy tto, right?
Kuwaetotte yo.
Suck it.
Hora.
Come on.
Bacchiri.
Great.
Shashin tottoku ne.
I will take this scene too.
Ah, ii na sono me.
Ah, you close your eyes.
Ah sensei saikou dana. / Hora kocchi mo kocchi mo.
Ah you are great, Miss. / Hey suck this one too.
Sou.
Yeah.
Ah, sensei...
Ah, Miss...
Sensei...
Miss...
Hora ore no chinko mo ajiwatteru yo, hora.
Come one, suck and enjoy my dick too.
Ah,kimochi ii na. / Kimochi ii na.
Ah, feels very good. / Ah, feels good.
Ah, sensei...
Ah, Miss...
Sensei majime ni yaranai to hontou ni okuru kara ne.
If you don't do it seriously, I will send the pictures.
Ne, sensei.
Ok, Miss?
Sensei, kimochi ii.
It's feels great, Miss.
Sensei sugee eroi oto ga...
You made such erotic voice, Miss.
Kocchi mo...hora...
This one too...come on...
Aan shite sensei.
Open your mouth, Miss.
Sensei sugoi eroi.
Miss, you are very pervert.
Fudan anna ni majime ni juugyou shiteru noni.
Usually  you are looks very serious when teaching on class.
*mumbling*
Kocchi mo kuwaete yo hora.
Suck it more again.
Sensei o danna san ni konna eroi pero shitenno?
Miss, do you suck your husband dick like this too?
Hai, kuwaerun deshou.
Hey, suck it deeper.
Ne sensei dou nano? Shitsumon shitten dakedo.
Hey Miss, how is it? I'm asking you.
Sensei, shitsumon chanto kotaete yo.
Answer my question, Miss.
Chou sugee umain dayo.
She's very good.
Ah, sugoi sensei.
Ah, you are great, Miss.
Sensei, ii desu. Nanka  ikisou ni nacchatte.
Stop it, Miss. I'm feel like I will cum.
Sensei...
Miss...
Kikaseru oto shitenai ne.
You don't make any voices again.
*mumbling*
Sonna sugu owaru wake nai jan. / Dame dayo sensei.
It's not over yet. / Stop doing that, Miss.
Ah, yamete. Iya.
Ah, stop. No.
Sensei, hairu toko toru ne.
I will take when he fuck you, okay Miss?
Oh, ii ne ii ne.
Oh, this is good.
Hora.
Come on.
Oh, iine. / Nigenaide yo.
Oh, good. / Where will you go, Miss.
Oi nigenjanee tte itten darou.
I said don't run away, right?
Kocchi ni kao misete yo chanto.
Show your face here.
Yamete.
Stop it.
Ah, sugu yamete.
Ah, hurry stop it.
Dou? Dou? Kimochi ii? / Oh, kimochi ii ne.
How? How? Feels good? / Yeah, it is.
Yamete...yamete.
Stop...stop.
*mumbling*
Shita dashite yo.
Take out your tongue.
*whispering*
Yoku kisu shiteru na, hora.
You kissed good, hey.
Ne shita  iku yo. / Oh oriro oriro.
Let'sgo down. / Yeah, go down from sofa.
Kimochi ii ne.
It's feels very good.
Kurasu no yatsura mirerun janee no kou iu no.
All of classmate maybe can see us doing this if they want.
Tamannai yo maji de.
Feels really good here.
Sensei mo kimochi ii?
Do you feels good, Miss?
Sensei, dou nano?
How is it, Miss?
Ne.
Hey.
Kimochi ii no?
Is it feels good?
Yamete.
Stop it.
Sensei no oku made.
I will fuck you deep.
Sensei, yararenagara kuwaeteru tokoro totte yaru kara sa.
Hey Miss, I will take photo when you suck me while you be fucked.
Sensei, toreteru yo.
Miss, I will take it.
Yamete. / Hora.
Stop. / Come on.
Hora, ne tsugi yaru yo.
Come on, change pose.
Oh, sugee na.
Oh, this great.
Sensei omanko nure nure jan.
Hey Miss,your pussy is very wet.
Yamete.
Stop.
Oretachi mo shita kimochi ii yo.
Oh we are enjoy this very much.
Ne, kimochi ii?
Hey, you feels good?
Hora oretachi no iu koto kiite yo.
Hey, listen what will we said and do it.
Hora hora.
Hey hey.
Kocchi muite.
Turn your face here.
Iu koto kikanai to.
You have to do what we say.
Ah sensei.
Ah, Miss.
Hora oketsu dashite yo hora.
Come one, move your hips more.
Sensei eroi yo.
You are very pervert.
Sugee kimochi ii.
It's very great.
Ii yo sensei.
That's good, Miss.
Marumie dayo, hora.
Look, it's completely exposed.
Minna yorokubu yo kore uttara.
Our friends will happy if we send this kind of pictures.
Ah, Iya.
Ah, No.
Kao agero yo, hora.
Raise up your head.
Iya nano?
You hate it?
Chanto...
Suck it...
...kuwaerun da.
...properly.
Hora, sensei.
Come one, Miss.
Kimochi ii yo.
Feels good.
Ah, kimochi ii sensei.
Ah, feels good, Miss.
Suge kimochi ii.
Really feels good.
Kurasume no minna...
All of boys in the class will...
...sensei to shitagatteruna.
...wanna do this too with you.
Ah, yume mitai dashi.
Ah, this is like dream come true.
Hor.
Come on.
Ue no hou ga ii nano.
Come up on me.
Oh ii ne. / Oh, sugee.
Oh, this is great. / Oh, wow.
Kono kakkou saikou ne.
This one is really great.
*mumbling*
Te de yatte yaru yosensei.
Do blow job on mine.
Tsunagatteru toko bacchiri dawa.
It's looks great when his dick come inside you.
Danna san kou yatteru no, sensei?
Did your  husband do this to you, Miss?
Okiro yo hora, mae ni hora.
Get your body up to front.
Oh, ii ne. Oh iine.
Oh, this is great.
Oi sensei, kocchi mite.
Look at here, Miss.
Sousou.
Yeah, like that.
Sensei wakatten jan.
You know it well, Miss.
Sensei wa kimochi ii deshou?
You feels it good right, Miss?
*mumbling*
Sensei ureshii?
Are you happy?
Sensei dou nano?
How is it, Miss?
Ah, kimochi ii.
Ah, feels good.
Kou shiyou ne, hora.
Do it like this, come on.
Hora sensei oku made kuwaerun dayo.
Come on Miss, suck it deeper again.
Hora.
Come on.
Sensei kimochi ii no?
Do you feels good, Miss?
Hora.
Hey.
Chanto kuwaero yo, hora.
Come on, suck this too.
Hora.
Come on.
Ah yabai.
Oh damn.
Sugee kimochi ii.
It's really good.
Ah, ii yo sensei.
Ah, this is great Miss.
*mumbling*
Hora.
Come on.
Kimochi ii.
Feels good.
Yabai sensei...
Oh my God...
Ore icchaisou na yo.
I want to cum.
Yabai ne sensei, hora.
Oh, I wanna cum.
Maji de?
Really?
Motto tottoku kara ne.
I will take it when you cum.
Deru toko tottoite goran.
Take it when I cum on her, okay.
Suge kimochi ii yo ne.
Ah, really feels good.
Ah icchaisou. Yoroshii sensei? / Icchae yo.
Ah, I want to cum. May I, Miss? / Just cum now.
Ah, iku.
Ah, I cum.
Sensei kocchi mite.
Sensei look at here.
Kittanne... / Hora.
It's disgusting. / Look.
*mumbling*
Sensei kocchi mitara?
Sensei, look at here please.
Chantoyaru na, sensei hora.
wah, you did it great Miss.
*whispering*
Hora, hora.
Come on, Come on.
Oh, ii ne.
Oh great.
Marumie da yo, kore.
I can see her whole body like this.
Sensei, boushou ga nurechattenna.
Inside your pussy is really wet.
Te de shite,nigiru yo hora.
Grap it with your hand.
Ah sensei... / Nanka ie yo.
Ah, Miss... / Say something.
Ah kimochi ii. Ah, sensei ikisou.
Ah, feels good. Ah, I want to cum.
Icchae. / Sensei ah...
Cum. / Miss, ah...
Kocchi mite.
Look at here.
Ah, ii kao dayo sensei.
Ah, you make a good face, Miss.
Dasarechatta ne.
You made them cum.
Tottoku kara na.
I already take it.
Ah, kimochi yokatta.
Ah that was great.
Icchau, sensei.
I want to cum, Miss.
Ah, iku.
Ah, I want to cum.
Ore mo icchau.
I want to cum too.
Ah, iku...
Ah, I cum...
Ah, sensei ii kao natta ne.
You've made such great face, Miss.
Hontou hontou. Mae yori dekiru you ni natta jan. / Hakidasu na.
Yeah, yeah. You could do it if you want. / Don't spit it out.
Kirei ni surun darou?
You will clean it all, right?
AH, bacchiri tocchatta yo.
I already took pictures of all actions.
Sensei...
Miss...
Kore kara oretachi no iu koto kike yo.
From now on, you must do all things that we say.
Iu koto kikanakattara...
If you don't do it...
...kono kakkou gakkoujuu ni baremau kara ne.
...we will expose this pictures to whole school.
Sensei...
Miss...
Anta no danna ga inai toki no mikkakan...
Three days when your husband not in home...
Sensei ga sabishikunai you ni...
For make you not feels sad...
Oretachi de...
We will...
Tappuri kawaigatte yaru kara na.
I will treat you really good like this.
Motto yarou yo sensei. / Tanoshimou ze.
Let's do it more. / We will have fun.
Aitsu kita na. Itte koi yo.
He came. Pick him up here.
Kita na, aitsura. Hahahaha.
They already come. Hahahaha.
*boys speaking*
Kocchi ka. Hora sensei hainna yo.
Over here? Come on Miss, get in.
Kore wa sensei no shiminshitsu da.
So this is your bedroom, Miss.
Sensei no.
This is her bedroom.
Hora, sensei.
Come on, Miss.
Danna san to isshoni ichaicha suru toko.
The place when you make love with your husband.
Motto yaru kana. Ne sensei.
We will do it more. Right, Miss?
Yawarakai. / Yamete.
Oh, it's soft. / Stop it.
Konna koto shinaide.
Don't do this.
Yamete. Iyaa. / Hora sensei, otonashiku shiro yo.
Stop it. No / Come on Miss, just shut up.
Hontou hoshiin darou, sensei?
Actually you want it right, Miss?
Ah sensei rakki...
Ah you are luck, Miss...
Ashi akete.
Spread your legs, Miss.
Yamete.
Stop it.
Makoto yamete. / Teikou sunna yo. Otonashiku shiro yo.
Makoto, stop. / Don't resist it. Just be quiet.
Oi, sensei...
Hey, Miss...
Kore...mou wasurechatta no?
Did you forget this?
Otonashiku shiro yo.
Just be quiet and do it.
Sensei, kore namete ii ka? / Iya.
May I lick this? / No.
Yamete. Iya.
Stop. No.
Hora, chibire mo shichatta.
Look, it;s already wet.
Yamete. Kocchi wa chanto totte yaru kara sa.
Stop. / Iwill take pictures when you do it.
Ato de meeru de okuru kara sa. / Yamete.
I will send it by email. / Stop.
Sensei.
Miss.
Sensei sa...
You...
...danna san to itsumo kou yatteru na.
...always do this with husband right, Miss?
Dou nano kana...
I don't know either...
Ii chikubi shiteru ne, sensei.
Your nipples looks good from here.
Yada...
No...
Oh, kimochi ii yo.
Oh, really feels good.
Kimochi iin darou, sensei?
It's feels good right, Miss?
Sensei ureshii ne? / Yada...yada.
You looks very happy, Miss. / No...no.
Kakusanaide yo.
Don't hide your face.
Hora...
Come on...
Ookii no yureteru ne.
Your big boobs is shaking.
Koufun shite kita na.
I'm really horny now.
Chotto kawatte miyou ka. / Oh, ii ii.
You want tochange? / Oh, okay.
Yada...yada.
No...no.
Yamete.
Stop it.
Hora. Osaete yo. / Hora...hora...
Come on. Hold her. / Hey...hey...
Hoka no yatsu ni meeru suru yo.
I will send email to other one.
*mumbling*
Sensei, oppai chou eroine.
Miss, your boobs very erotic.
*mumbling*
Chotto choudai.
I will take this.
Aitsu mada yattenna.
He still fucking her?
Eh, sore chotto.
Hey, don't take that.
Nobi zeitaku dana.
Nobi looks very satisfied.
Aitsu miru dake jan.
And he just wandering around.
Sensei koko koko ni hairi kurikaeshite ne.
Miss, he is fucking you constantly on here.
Ore chotto mite miyou kana.
Oh, Let me take a look.
Maji haitteru? / Un, haitteru.
Are you sure he is digging in her? / Yes he is.
*both speaking*
Ah sugee. / Hontou sugee na.
Ah, great. / This is really great.
Sou da.
Oh yeah.
Sensei, mata shashin totte ageru ne.
I will take pictures of you again, Miss.
Hai, kocchi muite.
Hey, look at here.
Sensei pisu pisu.
Miss,make peace mark.
Ii kao shite. / Shite kurenai no?
Make good face. / You won't do it?
Nandayo.
What the heck.
Shouganai mou.
I can't do anything.
Mata dare ka yobou.
I will ask for someone come again.
Yada. / Ja,pisu shite yo chanto.
No. / Then make a peace mark.
Hai hai, oh ii ne.
Yeah yeah, oh good.
Oh ii ne, mou ichimai.
Oh good, once more.
Kondo ryoute ryoute.
Next do it both hands.
Waratte waratte.
Smile smile.
Hai, ii yo.
Yeah, good.
Ah, sensei.
Ah, miss.
Hora motto waratte yo, sensei.
Oh come on, smile Miss.
Sore tore yo.
Take that one.
Sou sou.
Yeah like that.
Hai, waratte waratte.
Okay, make your best smile.
Ah, ii ne.
Ah, good.
Ah nanka koufun shite kita.
Ah, I'm horny now.
Oh, sensei.
Oh, Miss.
Ore no  shagutte yo. / Omae binbin janee kayo.
Suck mine. / Why are you so hard like that?
dekee na omae no.
Wow, your dick is big.
Shagutte.
Suck it.
Sensei hontou ii oppai shiteru ne.
Your boobs very beautiful, Miss.
Ah kimochi ii. / Tsukamatte.
Ah, feels good. / Hold on him.
Hora.
Come on.
Sa ore shiyou kana.
I will lick this, then.
Sensei kocchi mite yo.
Miss, look at here.
Ah, sensei...
Ah, Miss...
Kimochi ii.
Feels good.
Hontou ni ii ne. / Ah, yabai.
This is great. / Oh, wow.
Ore mo ore mo.
Me want to join.
Ja boku wa kocchi ne.
I will take this side.
*both speaking*
Ore ni mo mata yare yo sensei.
Do it again to me, Miss.
Chotto matte.
Wait a minute.
Ah, sugoi yo.
Ah, this great.
Sensei...mada? Hara hette yo.
The meal not yet, Miss? I'm hungry.
Sensei...
Miss...
Hara hette,meshi mada?
I'm hungry, not did yet?
Senei...
Miss...
Asadachi shichatta yo.
I'm in the morning hardness.
Yarasete yo.
Let me fuck you.
Chotto,oi.
Hey, wait.
Ah, kimochi ii.
Ah, feels good.
Kimochi ii no?
Do you feels good?
Ah, kimochi ii.
Ah, feels good.
Aah, kimochi yokatta.
Ah, that was great.
Asa sekkusu sugee kimochi ii no.
Morning sex really great.
Maji ka yo?
Really?
Ore mo shiyou.
I will do it too.
*both speaking*
Ore ga katta ze.
I win.
Tsuyoi na.
You are strong, huh.
Ore make no?
Seriously I lost?
Tsugi wa makenai yo.
Next I will not loose.
Ah, kimochi ii.
Ah, feels good.
Mou yannai?
Don't want do it?
Oi Kenji...
Hey Kenji...
Keitai natteru hora. / Chotto matt. Mousugu hora.
Your phone is ringing. / Wait a minute. I will done this.
Hai...hai.
Yeah...yeah.
Moshi moshi. Oh, Yamada.
Hello. Oh, Yamada.
Un yatteru yo.
Uh, still doing it.
Ah, webbu mitanda.
Ah, you saw my web.
Oh hayaku koi yo. Tanoshiku yatten dakara.
Uh, come here hurry. We are enjoy doing it now.
Hai, ja nee, hai.
Okay, see you soon.
Ah kuso.
Oh, crap.
Sensei...
Miss...
Itsu made ushiro yattendayo.
You just do my back.
Mae mo yatte kure yo.
Do my front body too.
Sou janai deshou?
It's not like that, right?
Okuchi de surun deshou?
You must do it with your mouth.
Okuchi de aratte yo.
Clean it with your mouth.
Hayaku.
Hurry.
Sonna ja kirei ni nannai yo.
It will not clean if you not suck it properly.
Hai kore. Ah, kimochi ii.
Yes, like that. Ah, feels good.
Hora.
Come on.
Ah, kyuusuu no ga kimochi ii.
Ah, it's feels good when you suck it.
Sensei tomaccha dame dayo hora.
Hey, don't stop do it, Miss.
Kimochi ii.
Ah, great.
Araccha dame dayo.
Don't wash it with water.
Sugee kimochi ii na.
Really feels good.
Nani hakidashiteru no?
Why you spit it out?
Kirei ni.
Clean it.
Chou kimochi yokatta.
It was really great.
Sensei kondo yatte yo.
Next is me, Miss.
Hora kitanai kuchi dana.
Look that dirty mouth.
Arashite yaruyo.
I will clean it.
Sensei, chanto yatte yo.
Do it properly, Miss.
*mumbling*
Ah ikisou. Hora iku yo.
Ah, I want to cum. I will cum.
Ne sensei...koou yatte...
Ok Miss...already tied you...
Chotto yurui kana kore.
It's a little bit loosely.
*mumbling*
Kocchi mo misete yo.
Show me this one too.
Nani yatten dayo.
What are you doing?
*someone speaking*
Oh, Yamamoto tsuita yo. / Hai, haitte.
Oh, Yamamoto is arrived. ? Come on, get in.
Sensei jan. / Sugge kakkou shiten jan. Hontou dattanda.
It's our teacher. / This is for real, dude.
Sugee darou? / Sugee na.
Isn't it great? / This is great.
Maa maa suware yo suware.
Oh, both of you sit down.
Ore jikkuri yatte yaru yo. Sensei ga koufun shiteru kara sa.
I will do it slowly for you. She is on fire too.
*mumbling*
*both speaking*
Ah, sensei no oppai. Sugee na.
Oh, it's her boobs. Wow, looks great.
Sensei no oppai sawatte ii yo. / *both speaking*
You can touch her boobs if you want. / *both speaking*
Sugee na kore. / Chikubi tatten jan.
This is great. / Her nipples looks so hard.
Sawatte ii no? / *both speaking*
Can I touch it? / *both speaking*
I'm sorry, sensei.
Oppai sawatte ii kara na. / Sawatte miro yo.
You can touch her boobs. / You can touch it.
Nanka koufun shiten na.
She is getting horny.
Suki ni shite ii yo. Sukinshippu sensei.
You can do what you want. A skinship wit our teacher.
*mumbling*
*both speaking*
Kou yuu no wo tsukatte tsugi wa ikaseru yo sensei.
I will make you cum using this ting, Miss.
Sensei ii kao shite yo. / Iya yo mo iya yo mo suki ni utsutendakara.
You make such good face, Miss. You always said don't like it, but your face looks enjoy it.
Kimochi iinda sensei?
Is it feels good, Miss?
Hontou wa kocchi yowakatta kke, sensei?
Actually this is your sensitive point, right?
*four boys speaking*
Uwa, karada atsuku natte kita na.
Oh, her body getting warmed.
Dou da? / Iya.
How is it? / No.
Sugee n.
Oh, great.
*mumbling*
Ii koe natte kita yo.
Her voice getting nicer.
Hora.
See.
Motto kimochi ii toko ni attete ii no yo.
I will put this in your sensitive point.
Hora.
Look.
Ashi hirogenai to.
Spread your legs.
Sensei atete agerarenaiyo, akenai to.
If you not spread it, I can't put this ting on your sensitive spot.
*mumbling*
Tarinai? / Kimochi ii?
Not enough yet? / Feels good?
Ah, sugoi. / Sugoi na.
Ah, great. / Oh wow.
Hora omaera.
Hey you.
Mite miro, hora...sensei no omanko.
Hey look on that pussy, it's our teacher's one.
Hikuhiku shiten darou. / Ore sonna no mita koto nai.
It's twitching. / I never see pusyy like this.
Sanzan mite. / Kirei dana.
See it all. / Ah, beautiful.
Hontou kirei da.
Really, it's beautiful.
Kou iu no mo suki desu ne, sensei. / *mumbling*
You like this one too, right? / *mumbling*
*three boys speaking* / Tanoshikattara jibun de itte yo.
*three boys speaking* / If you enjoy it, say it.
Kimochi ii no sensei?
Is it feels good?
Katte ni irechaou.
Okay, I will put it in.
Aketa. / Oh, sugee.
I open it. / Oh, great.
Sugee na sensei.
This is great, Miss.
Hora , kekkou hairu yo hora.
Look, it cn get in deeper.
Hora.
Look.
Motto asobou yo.
Let's play with this.
Hora...
Look...
Hora, konna ni haitta. / *both speaking*
It's entered it this deep. / *both speaking*
Kimochi ii sensei?
Feels good, Miss?
Mou ikisou nanda.
Oh, she will cum.
Ah, sugee hikuhiku shitemasu yo.
Ah, your pussy is twitching.
Sensei omanko de asobu to sugoi kanjiru dana.
You are very sensitive when we play around your pussy.
Gohoubi.
Your reward.
Oh sugee kou natteru yo.
Oh wow, it's became like this.
*both speaking*
Ah, omaera sa sensei to yaru?
Ah both of you wanna fuck her?
Sou dana. Sore yarun dattara yaritai na.
Oh yeah. I want to do it.
Chotto oretachi sa, mou akita kara sa. Omaera suki ni yatte ii yo . Eh, ii no?
We are already enough with her. You can do what you want. / Seriously?
*both speaking*
Omaera ii no ka?
You are not join?
Suki ni yatte ii yo. / Sore ja ato de ne ato de.
You can do what you want. / See you again.
!@#$%^&*
Kore no tme ni yatte kitan deshou.
We came here for do it with you.
Kimochi ii narou yo sensei.
Let have fun with it, Miss.
Ah, sugee.
Ah, great.
Chotto kudasai yo sensei.
Give me kiss, Miss.
*both speaking*
Omae saki ni ii zo.
You can do it first.
Kimochi iin darou?
It;s feels good, right?
Ii yo, omae saki ni itte yo.
That's okay, you can do it first.
Oh, ohayou. / Ah, ohayou.
Oh, good morning. / Morning.
Sensei...
Miss...
Hitobanjuu butsukomarete...
You already trapped here for one night...
...chotto yaritakunacchatta ne.
...looks like you want to do it from yourself.
Ne...
Hey...
Sou deshou? Sonna ni?
Isn't that true? Really?
*whispering*
Ne sensei...
Miss...
Kono mono wa mou ii kara.
It's enough with this  machine.
Hora.
Come on.
Sensei...
Miss...
Ketsu agete yo.
Wake up.
Nuge.
Take it off.
Hora iku zo.
Okay, here I come.
Sensei...
Miss...
Chotto asadachi shiten jan.
He is on morning hard now.
Shagurina yo.
Suck it.
Hora sensei.
Come on, Miss.
Binbin jan.
It's hard.
Kuwaitai deshou?
You want suck it too, right?
Hora sono mama itte yo.
Come on, just suck it.
Kuwaetenasai yo.
Suck it.
Nani yatten dayo omae. / Omae binbin natten jan.
What the hell are you doing? / Your dick is hard.
Sugee na asa kara.
What are you doing in this early morning.
Sensei komoshi yoku shite kure yo.
Make me feels good, Miss.
Shikkari kuun dazo.
Suck it.
*mumbling*
Hora sensei kuchi akete matten dayo.
Hey she is open her mouth and waiting you.
Sensei shagutte kure yo, chanto.
Suck my dick properly, Miss.
Tanomu yo.
I'm asking you.
Uwa, dekee na omae.
Wow, your dick is big.
Oh, kimochi ii yo sensei.
Oh it's feels good, Miss.
Ah, kimochi ii yo sensei.
Ah, it's feels good, Miss.
Ah, sugoi.
Ah, great.
Nanka dechaisou na ore.
I'm about to cum now.
Sensei no kuchi de dashite ii yo na.
Can I cum inside your mouth, Miss?
Aah sensei deru.
Ah, I cum.
Sugoi na.
Oh wow.
Shagutte kure yo.
Suck it.
Kirei ni shite kurenai ka?
Can you mke it clean?
Sensei no kuchi ni tsuiteru.
My sperm in your mouth, Miss.
Mata ka yo. / Sugoi na omae.
Again? / You are very good in this game.
Zenzen kuria dekinee jan ore.
I almost can get clear even just once.
*playing games*
*mumbling*
Oi.
Hey.
Oi mite yo.
Hey look at her.
Ore no chinpo kuwaenagara jibun de kimochi yoku nattendayo.
She masturbating and enjoy it while sucking my dick.
Nandayo. / Maji ka?
What the hell. / Seriously?
Maji ka yo?
Seriously?
Sensei...
Miss...
Sonna gaman dekinainda.
You can't resist it anymore?
Sensei...
Hey Miss...
Sonna ni omanko sabishii no?
Your pussy missed our dicks?
Ochinpo irete kudasai.
Please put in your dick inside me.
Hora, sensei suki dayo.
Hey, she like our dick so much.
Kore de juubun darou, sensei?
I think you already enough with this?
Agenai yo.
I'm not giving you my dick again.
Hora.
Look.
Sore  wo motto...
I want more...
Ah, icchaou ka. / Ah, dame.
Ah, I will take this out. / Ah, don't.
Irete kudasai.
Please put it in.
Irecchau kara ne. / Dame.
I will put it in. / No.
Hora...hora.
Hey...look.
Ah dame...chinpo irete.
Ah, don't...put in your dick please.
Chinpo ga kono you ni haitte yaru yo.
I will put my dick in like this.
Ii darou kore gurai. / Ah dame dame.
It's enough with this, right. / Ah, no...no.
Ikisou nano.
I want to cum.
Chinpo de ikitai.
I want cum with your dick.
Chinpo de ikitai noni... / Urusai.
I want cum with your dick... / Shut up.
Kimochi ii yattenno.
Ah she looks so satisfied.
!@#$%^&*
Kore wa sugoi na...
This is so great...
Manzoku shitenno?
Are you satisfied?
Chinpo...chinpo kudasai.
Dick...give me your dick.
Chinpo wo kudasai.
Give me your dick.
Mita ka yo?
Did you see that?
Sensei suki dana...chinpo.
You like dick...very much, huh?
*mumbling*
Ore no hoshii no ka, sensei?
Do you want my dick too?
Mite miro yo.
Look at that.
Ochinpo.
Dick.
Ochinpo hoshii. / Dou shiyou kana. Nani ni shiyou kana.
I want that dick. / What should I do. What will I do.
Doko ni irete hoshii no?
Where you want me put it in?
Omanko de.
In my pussy.
Omanko de shite hoshii desu. / Ii yo yatte ageru.
I want you put it in my pussy. / Oh, that's okay, I will do as you wish.
Ochinpo...
Dick...
Dono chinpo?
What kind of dick?
Ochinpo...
Your dick...
Ochinpo...iyarashii ochinpo ga hoshii.
Dick...I want your nasty dick.
Soushitara sensei...
If like that...
Atashi no dosukebe na omanko ni...
Say, put all of your dick...
...ippai ochinpo wo uchikonde kudasai tte.
...in my nasty pussy please.
Ittara kangaete yru yo.
I will think to do it if you say that.
Atashi no...
Put your dick...
...dosukebe na omanko ni...
...inside my nasty pussy...
...ochinpo ippai uchikonde kudasai.
...put it all inside me please.
saisho kara sou ie yo.
You should said that since before.
Hora iku zo.
Here I come.
*mumbling*
Kimochi ii ka?
Feels good?
*mumbling*
Sensei kocchi muite yo.
Turn your face here, Miss.
Shita kimochi ii dayo sensei.
Your pussy really feels good.
Yamechaou ka sensei? / Dame, yamecha dame. Motto motto...
Should we stop? / Don't stop please. Do it more, more...
Ja motto onegai shite kudasai. / Motto yatte kudasai.
You should ask more for it then. / Please, do it more, please.
Motto... / Motto nani yo sensei?
More... / More what, Miss?
Sonna ni kuchi ni tsukete...
You suck it  perfectlly...
Yureteru na dekai chichi ga.
That big boos are shaking.
Ah, kimochi ii.
Ah, feels good.
Deru toko kuchi de ii ne, sensei?
I can cum inside your mouth, right?
Omanko kimochi ii...omanko...
My pussy feels very good...my pussy...
Ochinchin ga haittete kimochi ii no.
It's feels good when your dick is inside me.
*whispering*
Dou da, sensei? Boku ikasete yo.
How is it, Miss? Make cum please.
*mumbling*
Oretachi sugeekoufun shite kita yo. / Sou dayo.
We are getting horny too. / Yeah.
Sugee na sensei no naka ni.
It's feels good inside yours, Miss.
Sugee yo na. / Sou sou, sugee.
It's very great. / Yeah looks great.
Nee sensei, eroi ne. / Kore kimochi ii no?
Hey, Miss you are so nasty. / This is feels good?
Kimochi ii. / Nee sensei kimochi ii tte itten jan.
Feels good. / Hey Miss, at last you say it's good.
*mumbling*
Sensei iku toki sugee na. / Sensei ippai kawaigatte ageru yo.
You're so great when cumming. / We will fondled you.
Kocchi koi yo.
Come here.
Hora.
Come.
Suware  yo.
Sit here.
Hora.
Come on.
Sensei ore to kisu shiyou ze.
Kiss with me.
Sensei mou...
Oh my...
*four boys speaking*
Inran dakara sensei yo.
You are very easy, huh.
Ah sugee mou guchagucha natteru yan.
Oh, your already messed up here.
Sensei mou guchagucha jan.
You are already messed up here.
*mumbling*
Matte...
Wait...
Oh sugee...
Oh wow...
Kimochi ii...kimochi ii...
Oh feels good...oh...
Sensei oppai namesasete yaru yo.
I'll lick your nipples.
Dosukebe sensei.
Pervert teacher.
Iroiro makikomu yo sensei.
You just caught by me here.
Ippai ikasete yaru yo.
We will make you orgasm continuosly.
Kimochi ii sensei? Kimochi ii?
Is it feels good Miss?
Yamechaou kana sensei. / Yamecha dame. Motto...
Should we stop this? / Don't stop please. More...
*boys speaking*
Ore ni notte kure yo.
Ride on top, Miss.
Namesasete yaru yo. / Notte kure tte.
I will lick your pussy. / He said ride him.
Sou sou shiteru na.
Yeah do like that.
Kimochi ii?
Feels good?
Mou kimochi ii.
Yeah,feels good.
Mune sawatten jan.
I'm touching your boobs.
*moaning*
Kimochi ii...ah kimochi ii...sugoi kimochi ii.
Feels good...ah, it's feels good...yeah.
AH, haitta.
Ah, I got in.
Sensei sugoi dosukebe dayone.
You are very nasty, Miss.
Mata haitta ne. Ah sugoi sensei. / Sensei chotto chotto.
I got in. Ah, this great. / Miss, wait for minute.
Namete yo, hora.
Suck it, come on.
Sensei no inapuri yabee ne.
Your moveness really great.
Yatte yo sensei kocchi mo.
Do hand job on mine too.
Ah...sugee.
Ah...great.
Ippai tamatten na kore sensei.
Your boobs are really soft.
*mumbling*
Kore mo sawatte goran. / Sensei ja ippon de tarinai deshou.
Touch this one too. / You are not enough with one dick, right?
Sensei ippai no hou ga ii kana. / Sonna ureshisou na kao shite.
You like lots dick, right. / You looks very happy.
Omanko yo. / Ah, kimochi ii.
Your pussy... / Ah, feels great.
Sensei sugoi ne. / Sensei, te ugoki umai.
You are great, Miss. / Your hand job awesome.
Kimochi ii.
Feels good.
Ah, chanto shagutte na.
Yeah suck it.
Nihon no te to...
Grab this dick with two hands...
Ah, sugoi na.
Ah, this great.
Sugee kimochi ii.
Really feels good.
Ah sensei kimochi ii.
Ah it's feels good, Miss.
Ah...sugoi.
Ah...great.
Ah kimochi ii. / Sensei...
Ah feels good. / Miss...
*both speaking*
Kore zenbu...
Suck it all...
Ah sensei kawaii ne. Ore suki da kono juugyou.
Ah you are cute, Miss. I like this class.
Sensei hontou ni sugee na. / Hontou ni eroi desu ne.
You are very great, Miss. / Really nasty but.
Sensei kocchi mo.
This one too, Miss.
Hai, kocchi yo sensei.
Here, this one too.
Kore hontou ni suki na sensei.
You are very like this dick.
Sensei kore yabai yo.
Oh damn it...
Ah,sensei...
Ah, miss...
Kocchi mo shagutte yo.
Suck this one  too.
Nani shichaou kana.
What should we do next.
Sugoi na. Hora...hora...
Great. Come on...come on...
Hora.
Come on.
Sensei erosugi. / Chotto tsutsunde ii ne.
Very nasty. / Can I pinch this?
Kore dou kore wo? / Ah, kimochi ii.
How about this one? / Ah, feels good.
Sensei suki dane. / Kore mo kore mo.
You very like this dick. / This one too.
Kimochi ii oppai. / Tsurarete mo?
My boobs feels good. / Even I pinch it?
SUgee na.
It's great.
Sensei sugoi na.
You are great on this.
Sugee kimochi ii darou?
It's feels good, right?
Yabee yo sensei.
Oh this crap.
Oh kawarou ka.
Oh let's change.
Sensei...
Miss...
Kocchi mo aru yo.
Suck this dick too.
Kocchi muite yo.
Turn your face here.
Ah, sugee.
Ah, great.
Ah, kimochi ii.
Ah, feels good.
Ah sugoi sensei. / Ah sugoi. Soko kara namerareru no?
Ah it's awesome. / It's great. You can suck it from there.
Kore mo ii na sensei.
This one great too, Miss.
Ah, kimochi ii. / Sugee na sensei, kore.
Ah, feels good. / Ah, this is very good.
Sugoi na, dosukebe dana sensei.
Wow, you are very nasty  Miss.
Ah ore mo kimochi iindayo.
Ah I'm feels good too.
*two boys speaking*
Hora minna tsugi deshou.
You are next after me.
Ore wa saishou.
I do it first.
Koko ni te wo tsuite.
Put your hands over here.
Omanko sugoi wa.
Your  pussy really good.
Sugoi.
Wow.
Kocchi mo aru yo.
I have dick too, here.
Ah sensei, kuchi sugoi attakai yo.
Ah your mouth very warm and wet.
Marumie darou?
It's completely exposed, right?
Haittete dou nano? / Sugoi na, sensei.
How is it when he fuck you? / You are great Miss.
Sensei ore no chinpo oishii? / Oishii.
Is my dick taste good? / Yeah, it is.
Kocchi mo shagutte yo.
Suck mine too.
Kocchi hayaku suru yo.
I will do it faster.
Sensei haitteru toko sugoi mieru yo.
I can see it barely when he fuck you.
Ah, dame.
Ah, No.
Iku.
I'm cumming.
Sensei icchau no?
Are you cumming?
Mada mada dayo sensei.
Not yet, Miss.
*mumbling*
Hora minna wo tsukamatte...
Hold on your hands to another one...
Kocchi ikuyo ushiro kara.
I will come from behind you.
Hora...hora...
Hey...hey...
Kore mo tsukamaete kure yo.
Grab my dick too.
Sensei, kotai yo kotai.
Hey let's change, Miss.
Sensei dou da? / Kimochi ii. kimochi ii?
How is it, Miss? / Feels good, feels good?
Sensei, dou kimochi ii ssu yo.
How is it, Miss?
Sugee kimochi ii.
It's really great.
Ah koko mo sensei.
Ah this one too miss.
Ah, sugoi na.
Ah, this is great.
Sugoi.
Wow.
Dame kamo shirenai. Mou dechau kamo. / Maji ka?
I can't handle it anymore. I will cum. / Seriously?
Ah, kimochi ii.
Ah, feels good.
Nanda ikisou dayo sensei.
I'm about to cum.
Iinjanai desu ka kore?
This is great right?
Icchae icchae.
Just cum.
Icchatta ka omae?
Already cum?
Ah sugee, kore sugee na. / Naka de shotto.
Ah, great, this is great. / I cum inside.
Sugoi na kore. / Nanda yo omae, nureteru janee kayo.
This is great. / What the hell are you. It's wet isn't it.
Icchattanda. / Sugee nureteru jan kore.
I cum inside. / Oh it's really wet.
Kittanee na kittanee na kore. / Hora kitsukidase yo.
Ah this is disgusting, dirty. / Hey come upside down.
Omae dekee kara na,sugoi kutsuiteru yo.
Your dick is big, it's tick so hard inside.