Director Masaki Nao
I'm sorry, Yuuko
I'm sorry
Are you alright?
I am.. a bit late
It's fine.. Calm down
This man is Hiroshi.. He is very kind
I was hurt by my exhusband DV
He took care of my injured heart and has been always by my side.
I may be happy with this person
That's what I thought
The wife of a very Masochistic Family
Excuse me
Oh.. Yuuko?
I'm sorry
From now on.. This is your house
Yes
Today l will introduce you to my family
Come in
Yes
Thanks for helping me
Go ahead
Right here.
Excuse me
He is my father Hiroshi.. He is a teacher
Yuukosan, nice to meet you.
It is such a pleasure to meet a beautiful lady like you
It's me who should say that, I am happy to meet you too
Well.. Come inside
Please
This is my son, Satoshi
Nice to meet you
Quite a resemblance.
I am Yuuko.. Nice to meet you
Big brother! Introduce us too.
Ah, sorry sorry..
These two are my younger brothers
Hiroshi's younger brothers, Masashi&Takeshi
Nice to meet you, big sister
I am Yuuko.. Nice to meet you too
And then there is also my grandfather, but..
My grandfather is still sleeping.. I can introduce him later
But, I am quite happy,
That I can welcome Yuukosan into my family
Me too
I am happy being surrounded by such a splendid family
Hiroshisan
Thank you
No, likewise
From now on, please take care of us
I will
You're beautiful
Hiroshisan.
Huh?
Hey..
Let's have sex
I want to have a child
Besides that
Lately we have never done it at all
No, umm..
Wait a moment
Because life is long
Umm.. with.such matters,
Maybe we can...
...slow things a bit?
Right.
You're right
Somehow...
I am embarrassed now.. I'm sorry
Umm.. However
Umm
I wonder if
I can ask you
only one thing?
Yes
What?
Umm
I don't want you... to leave me because this, though.
Of course
Umm..
I wonder
if you could step over my thing?
Eh?
That..
Please
Step
On my face
F..face?
Step on?
Please step on me.
Umm..
Please step on my face !
Eh? Wait a second!
I'm begging you!
Wait, wait
Wait a sec
It's okay
Please step on me
l beg you.. Please step on me
Really?
Yes.
I want this so bad.
Is it okay?
Yes
Are you serious?
I'm serious
I understand.
Are you okay with this?
Yes
Please step on me with all your strength
Really?
It was strange and I was not disgusted about it
And this strange events continued since today
Ms.Yuuko
Yes, Mr.Takeshi?
Big brother is strange, right?
Is that so?
Maybe he is too kind
No.. That's not what I mean
It's about his sexual habits
Ah, about that..
I also have
A few unusual sexual habits
W..what are you doing?
With.. With that vacuum cleaner!!
Please hit my dick!
Wait!
I'm begging you!
Someone will come.
I beg you!
Hey.. Please wear your clothes
I beg you.. Please suck my dick with that!
So I beg you..I can't do that!
Hey.. Wear your clothes!
I'm really begging you!
That's why.. I beg you!.
Me too.
Please suck it with that
Takeshi
Calm down.. Calm down
I beg you!
I'm begging you by all means!
No, no.. Because it's impossmle. right?
I'm begging you!
I'm really begging you!
Because it's impossible.
I'm begging you! I beg you!
Someone will hear us.
I beg you!
I am begging you...
I'll be in trouble.
I am begging you
I am really begging you.
You really want it so much?
Yes.. I'm begging you...
With a vacuum cleaner?
Yes
Suck it?
Yes.
I beg you.
Suck my dick.
Is that enough?
I get it.
After that.. Will you,wear your clothes?
Yes
Understand.
Suck it.
With vacuum cleaner, right?
Yes.
Is it really okay?
Ahh..I beg you
Suck me with that.
It feels so good.
Do you want me to do it more?
Yes, more.
But isn't a person...
better than a vacuum cleaner?
Eh?
Rather than a vacuum cleaner machine.
It will really feel good.
Eh?
What is it?
Come on
You want to do it?
Yes
Ah, amazing!
Is it feels good?
Yes
Ah, amazing!
Here?
Yes
Is it feels good?
It feels good
Takeshi is so cute
Do you want me to suck this like that vacuum cleaner earlier?
Yes
Ah.. It feels good
want more
It feels good
Yes
Is it feels good?
It feels good
Shall I do on this side too?
Yes
Ahh.. Amazing!
With such facial expression
Please try stick out your tongue more
Awesome!
You are cute
Lick it
I will lick it
You like to suffer, right?
Amazing!
You can't..
I want to lick it.. I want to lick it
It's fine
More..
I want to lick it more
More?
Yes, more
I'll let you touch it more
Do it in this way
Stay like this, right?
Good?
Come on
Because I will do it too
It is standing like this
Do you feel it?
Feels good?
Ah.. Amazing
Well.. What should I do next?
More
Straddle on my face.. More
I want more, please
Please sit on me
I'll sit on you
Are you okay with that?
Feels good?
Is it feels good?
Lick it
I want you
to touch it directly
Directly?
Yes
Do you want me to suck it directly?
Ah.. This is getting so big
You want it so much, right?
Amazing!
It feels amazing
Oh no.. It feels good
Is it feels good?
I will lick it to the back
Yes
Please spread your legs wider
That's right
Like this?
It's delicious
It's so wide open
What happened?
Looks like the sperm will come out
You want to cum?
Please make me cum
I will cum!
Not yet
You still can't do it
Your dick want to cum, right?
That feels so good.
Feels good?
More.. If's really...
You want to cum?
I want to cum..
Do you want to cum?
Ah.. It will come out.
Takeshi-kun
Not yet
I can't hold it anymore.
Big sister won't forgive you
May I release it?
You can't.
Ah.. It feels so good.
Stop.. It feels good
Not yet
It feels too good
I can't endure it
I see
But.. You still can't do it
My dick..
You can't
Not yet
But..
Huh?
You can't endure it?
It feels good
You can't
Ah, it feels good
Feels good?
Yes
Not yet.
Ahh.. Amazing!
It feels good
This feels good
Feels good?
Yes
Ah,is dangerous
Not yet
Not yet!
It feels so good
Do you really want to cum?
Do you want to cum?
You want to cum by my hand pussy?
You want to cum by big sister's hand pussy?
Yes.. I want to cum
I'm gonna cum!
You will cum?
Yes
You can release it
Ah! I'm cumming!
Ah.. I'm cumming!
You came a lot, don't you?
You came a lot
Ah, that's bad
That?
Bad?
Is it good? Is it feels good?
Ah.. It will come out
Ah! It's out
Don't! It's enough!
Don'tl
No more!
Not yet?
Like this
Big brother.. That's unfair!
Masashi-kun?
I want to do it too
You too, Masashi?
Big sister
I want to do it too
What do you want me to do, Masashi?
Do it like this
I want you
To punish me with that body
Stick out your tongue more
It's delicious big sister.
Delicious?
Ah, big sister
Masashi-kun...
Deeper.
Here?
Amazing! More
Ah.. Big sister
Do you like to be licked, Masashi?
Yes
Ah.. You lick it so much, big sister .
Even though big sister just finished from doing it with old brother
You saw that
Big sister did it with Takeshi
I made him felt good
That's why
Big sister want to do it again
I want it
I will do my best
Big sister
You can touch it
I want it
Ah, big sister
You've been aroused since a while ago, right?
I was aroused
I am happy because I can drink big sister's juices
More
Please suck it more
I want to lick it until deeper
Yes..Be obedient
Do it more
Your cum is amazing! There is a lot
There is so much juice inside my mouth
Ah.. I'll release more of my juice
You're unbearable, big sister
Amazing!
It's still not enough
Masashi...
I'll lick it more
It is warm
Big sister's pussy juice
Big sister..
Give me more.
Ah, more.
Do you want more?
Do you want it?
That's right.
I gave you a reward.
Everything has came out, big sister?
It's such a waste! There is so much spilled here
Is it delicious?
Look at this.
Big sister..
You're a lewd boy
Big sister likes lewd boys, right?
But you wanted to release it, right?
Lewd boy
I wanted it
You wanted it?
Then, your reward
You got excited, didn't you?
I've got excited
Ah.. Right there
Ah, big sister..
Big sister's tongue feels amazing!
I'm extremely happy
Happy?
Big sister
Getting licked like this?
Ah.. It feels good
Ah.. It's soft, big sister
Big sister's tongue is dangerous!
Feels good
Good
Big sister
This tongue...
I make your tongue get dirty with my bad tongue
This is making me hard
I will forget that you are my older brother's wife
Please forget it now
Is it fine?
You want to forget it, right?
I want to forget it
You belong to me, aren't you?
You're only my thing
I will make you forget
I got aroused
Can I do this?
It feels good
Do you want me to tick it?
Is it okay?
It's warm
Ah.. It's incredibly soft!
Big sister's tongue is great
Ah, amazing!
Big sister
Not yet.
Not yet
Because I cannot
Lick something like that
But..
You did it with big brother earlier, right?
Is that a problem?
Until when you can endure this?
Big sister
Big sister wear those a while ago
Tight
Do you like this kind of thing?
You touch it with that warm socks
Ah.. it feels amgzing!
Big sister
Amazing!
There
Ah.. Big sister grasp my dick with that warm socks
Your hand
And your mouth is warm
Everything feels so good!
I will do it, Takeshi
I want you to watch carefully
Where do you feel good?
Big sister's hand and all about big sister feels good
Look at that
Don't cum
Ah.. It feels amazing
Big sister.. I can't hold anymore
You can't?
Inside big sister
I'm cumming inside bigsister's hand
I'm Summing!
This is bad
That was feels so good.
You felt good?
Big sister
It's all right now, big sister.
Is it alright?
No more big sister.
What?
Is that enough?
Because I already released it all.
Big sister, don't!
Wait! Big sister?
More?
Big sister..
Ah, don't!
I can't hold it!
Big sister? Ah!
It's leaking out.. Big sister!
Don't! No more!
No more! Big sister!
You can't do it anymore?
Big sister.
Do you want to cum again?
I can't.
You can
I really can't
I understand.
Let's end this here for today.
Thank you for make me cum a lot
Musashi
Big sister
I love it
Me too, big sister
Takeshi is..
Takeshi?
Let's do it together
Cute boys.
From today we're really family.
Yes
Honestly
It was quite a bit of fun to tease these men
Satoshi.. I'll come in
You study so hard
I know you're doing your best, but..
It would be good if you eat the meal for a moment
Thank you very much
Satoshi-kun, you study so diligently
Your father told me so..
Is that so?
Satoshi-kun
Do you have a girlfriend or a girl that you like?
No
About that...
Tell me...
I am a virgin
I never dated with any girls
Is that so?
I'm sorry
Umm..
Ms. Yuuko
No
There is something I want to ask you as my mother
Yes
This..
I want to use this
Please take my virginity by force
I want to be dominated by a woman
I'm begging you
Please lie down there
Yes
Satoshi
Yes?
Obey to everything I say
And get naked properly
Yes
Are you happy?
Then next...
Open your mouth wide
Do you want to have fun?
Does it feels good?
You feel it?
Yes
Ah.. It's great
Feels good?
Are you happy?
This is standing
Are you really happy?
I wonder what shall I do next?
Because you cannot see..
Do you wonder where is it?
Do you feel something?
It is standing like this
But.. Not yet
Are you happy with that?
Your eyes cannot see anything
Do you know this smell?
Come on
Amazing!
Satoshi you are skillful
You can do stuff like tnalt
Do you want me to do it so much?
Lick my dick
This dick?
Hey
You still not allowed to cum
But.. Shalll take it off?
Please take it off
Please spread your legs
You look shameful
Like this?
Yes.
Does it feel good?
Do you want to talk?
Open it
Do your best.
What do you say?
What?
It feels good.
It feels good
Feels good?
Are you okay with this?
Yes.. it feels good.
I want to do more
Do you want me to eat it more?
Yes, more
Please eat it
Don't
That
If you suck it like that.. It will come out fasf!
You still can't
Are you gonna cum?
I'm gonna cum.
Not allowed yet.
But you're so cute right now, Satoshikun
Do you want me to bully you more?
Yes.
Don't.. Don't!
Mom..
Don't
Mom got hot
Do you want to see ?
It's amazing!
Really?
Is it feels good?
It feels good
Mom is happy
I'll lick it more
Wait a minute.. It is a little embarrassing .
More, more
Shall ll lick it deeper?
Well then.. Can I lick your ass?
That is an embarrassing place
But it feels good, right?
It is embarrassing
It feels good
How?
Feels good?
Deep
Does it feel good?
Your dick is standing
That's so lewd
Is it embarrassing?
No
Is it feels good?
Feels good
Feels good?
Please try to raise your legs
Can you see mom licking it?
Yes
Ah, wait!
Don't too rough
Don't!
I am gonna cum!
Mom!
Is that so good?
No
I'm gonna cum!
Is it feels good?
Tell me what you want me to do?
Yes
Please try to say it
It seems I'm gonna cum!
You will cum?
I'm gonna cum! Don it!
I'm gonna cum already
Are you gonna cum?
Then I will lick it
Do you want to put it in?
I want to put it in
You want to get dominated?
Say "Please rape me".
Please say it
Please
Fuck me..
You wanna do it, right?
I'll fuck you.
Mom..
Mom will.
Fuck you with this pussy
Is it good?
Feels good..
I Feels good?
Ah.. Dangerous
Ah.. does it feel good?
Feels good
Mom also feels good
I'll move it
If you do it so violently...
I'm gonna cum
Ah, don't! it will come out
Is it feels good?
It feels good
Sateshi fucking Mom with your virgin cock
Satoshi's virgin dick is delicious
It's dangerous
It's fine
Ah.. You're moving it so fast
Mother's boobs
My nipples are all hard
Satoshi have to lick them
Come on.. Please lick it
More
Yes, more
Suck them all
Mom will start ride again from behind
So deep
Feels good
Feels good?
It's entering
Satoshi
Try put it in
It is your first time, right?
Yes, like that
That's right
Mom
It feels good..
Feels'good?
Moving it violently like this
Ah, yes
Yes, yes
Because Satoshi is diligent
That's amazing!
Good
It feels good
Satoshi
Ahh.. I'm cumming!
Mom did cum
Does it feels good?
How?
Your first dgggy style
It feels good
This is different, right?
It's my first time, Mom
My dick..
You can do Mom as much you like
Fuck me as you please
Ah yes!
It's good
Satoshi is skillful
I'm gonna cum!
You can't..
Not yet
Because there is still a lot of things you must learn
It's good
It feels good
Satoshi's dick feels good
Mom will cum!
Amazing!
Please put it inside Mom
well..
Do it deep
Yes
It's inside.
It's entering very deep
You're skillful
It feels good
Right
You can see it well?
I can see it well
Is it entering?
The thing entering
Inside Mom?
Say it
My dick is entering
Please say it properly
Whose dick is entering inside Mom's pussy?
My dick is entering
Inside Mom
Right..
Delicious
Does Mom feel delicious?
Say you want more?
More
Say you want to do it untilt deeper inside Mom's pussy
Yes
Like this?
Amazing!
It feels good
Thrust me harder
Ahh.. It will come out
May I release it?
It come out!
Wow! Mom..
Again?
Again..
You want again?
It feels so good.
Feels good..
I want Satoshi to make me cum again.
More..
More?
It feels good.
Amazing!
Are you happy Satoshi?
I am happy
I'm happy..
Next.. I will do it
It's embarrassing
But you want to got dominated, right?
I guess you like doing this Kind of thing
Ah.. It's embarrassing, but feels good
How?
It feels good
Feels good?
It feels amazing!
You like me to pumping it like this, right?
Let's do it more
Ah.. It's good
My pussy feels so good
Amazing
It's slipped out from Mom
Insert it
Is it feels good?
Feels good
I will cum!
A bit more
Do it more, Mom
Do you want to cum?
I can't hold it anymore
You can't endure it?
It feels good
It's bad!
I am gonna cum!
Ah! I will cum!
I'm gonna cum.
Are you gonna cum?
I'm gonna cum! It't bad!
Oh no! It's bad!
I want you to do it again.
Come here
Feels good
Feels good?
This is the last, right?
Maybe
Because you endure it a lot
You can cum so much
Satoshi
Oh no!
Ah, Satoshi!
I'm gonna cum!
It's fine.
A lot
You still cum.
Satoshi
It's okay
I can't
Don't
Don't?
It's okay.. Do it like this.
Coming.. Coming.
You give it to me
Satoshi...
That is your virgin dick
But..
This is the premiere of Satoshi's transformation
Mother is very satisfied
I can not suppress my urges any longer
It became so pleasuring to torture men
As if I found my real self...
It smells good.
Good evening... Is the food ready?
Father... Today I prepared Hiroshi's favorite curry
But I wonder if that will fit with Father's taste?
I am a bit worried
My mother was a great cook too
Curry rice.. So nostalgic!
Is that so? I understand
You..
You look quite similar with Hiroshi's mother
Umm..
You looks a bit similar like my previous wife
Ah.. Sorry! My mouth slipped
Is that so?
Because Hiroshi
Don't talk much about it
Father-in-law?
Should I grant...
Father's wishes?
N-no..
Father
You want to be bullied by a woman, don't you?
Like this?
I want more..
This pervert!
Please... more...
Do you want more?
Fwant it.. I beg you
Shall I spit on you?
Please do it
Are you happy?
I am happy
Then, one more time
Yes, yes
Cute
It was delicious
Please give me more
More?
Then.. Stand over there
Ah, yes
l know what do you want..
Yes
Do it more violently
More
How?
Please hit me and kick me repeatedly
Do you want me to hit and kick you repeatedly?
Yes.
I want it
Do you want me...
...to hit you more?
Where?
+ More..
Yes!
Punish my body
Does that feel good?
Yes
Feels so good.
Feel good?
Yes
Got treated like this
Makes you happy, right?
Yes, I'm happy
Perverted creep..
Imagining it everyday
I guess it gives you a huge boner, right?
Huh?
Yes
Is that so?
That's right
Ah..That's right
You've been aroused, right?
Yes,yes
Is this feels good too?
Yes.. It feels good
Do you want me to do it more?
Yes
Huh?
Please do it more
l want more..
You're obedient
Then.. What shall I do next?
You want to use it?
Yes
Does it feel good?
Yes yes
It feels good
I like it
Good boy
You're a good boy
Well then
I wonder what kind of reaction do you have?
It's standing
Yes
I am really sorry
Is it really standing?
I been bad
That makes you so excited, right?
This pervert
Pervert!
Pervert
Do you want to be told that you are pervert?
Please call me pervert again
Are you pervert?
Is that okay,pervert?
Is that okay..pervert ?
Yes..l am pervert
You wanted to be treated like this?
Yes
You always saw me with that kind of eyes!
That's right
It become so red like this.. Poor you
You better hurt than being licked?
Huh?
Yes.. I like being hurt
You like being bitten too?
Yes.. Please bite me
Please chew my belly
Cute
Next...
What shall we do? Please sit down
Come on!
Do you want to suffer so much?
So much?
More?
Yes.. Please give me your ass more
I wonder if it is not painful anymore?
It's bad! More
More? More?
Al it feels good
Is it feels good?
Feels good.
So it feels good..
It seems you feeL comfortable
But just once is not enough, right?
Not yet?
Ah, amazing!
Huh? Is it feels good?
It feels good
You are hard like this
You like this kind of abnormal thing because you"re a pervert
Right?
Do you want more of this?
More excitement?
This is exciting
Pull it harder, right?
Do you like being injured so much?
Yes.
Then.. I will press you with my breast
Do you imagined this?
Yes
I imagined it.
Then.. I will grant your hopes.
Ahh.. The best!
You cannot breathe
Ah.. It feels good
That thing feels good, right?
Yes.. If feels good
This pervert!
Already this hard
Let me have a look
Pervert
More more more..
More?
Grasp it more
I'll squeeze it
Please forgive me
It's getting harder and harder
This too
More
More?
Hit it more!
Slap that more
This pervert
Pervert!
Please slap it more
This..
It feels good
Then.. The same stuff
This is..
D..dick
Dick..
Please suck it
I haven't lick your dick yet
I'll lick this first before suck that
Feels good?
You cannot say anything
But you like being painful, right?
Do you like it?
It feels good
Then...
You must have been fantasized, right?
What kind of body did I have, right?
First is ass
Is your dick standing?
Is it feels good?
Not yet
I'll let you play with it
You want to play with it, right?
Try put it in
How is it?
You cannot see it because it's so close, right?
Try move it by yourself
Ah, yes
Keep moving it
Then..
Yes.. Lie down
Not yet
I will put it in
Come on
Is it painful?
It's entering in and out like this
Pervert!
Pervert !
Pervert
You felt good?
More..
You want me to make you feel comfortable, right?
Do you want to see more?
Yes
You like this kind of thing, right?
I like it
You wanted to be treated like this?
Yes
It feels good
It feels good there
Here?
Yes
More.. More
Please suck it more
More?
Clean it.
Amazing!
Ah.. Drooling
Do you feel it?
It feels good
Does it feel good?
Then.. I will make you feel better.
You want to feel good?
Yes.. I want.
Then..
Eh?
Do you want it?
More?
Yes
It feels good
More?
Please deeper
Deeper?
Yes.
It's entering.. it's entering.
Ah, it's deep.
More? Deeper
Ahh.. It has entered
Is this feel good?
Yes.. It feels better
You wanted this, right?
Yes
I wanted this
You waited, did not you?
Yes.. I waited
You wanted to do something like this with me, right?
Yes, yes.
Hey.. It's even harder, isn't it?
Right?
Did you wanted to be my servant so much?
T..that's right
Do you wanted to be my dog?
I will become your dog
I will become.. your dog
Father
From today onwards
You are my dog, right?
Yes
I am a dog.
Do you want to be?
Yes.. I want to be.
Do you want to be yourself?
Yes.. You're right,
Pervert!
Pervert father.
Yes...
Yes, l am..
Everyone here is also pervert
Because of Dad, right?
Is that dad's upbringing?
It is lovely perverted education.
It's fine
Because I love perverts.
I also love a pervert father
Pervert!
Do you get excited when I called you pervert?
Yes.. I am excited
Do you want me to say it more?
Please say it
Pervert!
Ah, more
Pervert father!
Pervert teacher!
Pervert!
Oh no! I'm gonna cum!
I will cum!
Pervert.
It came out a lot...
You are a cute pervert, right?
From now on, your are a dog.
Yes
I am a dog
How is it?
I am serious about this
Wtis incredibly tasty!
Right?
What's wrong with this?
I bought it from the wife next door
Eh? Oh my..
You don't eat it, Yuuko?
Because I aiready ate a while ago
You don't eat again?
It's okay.. Then I will feeding you
Here
Delicious.
I am glad
Umm..
I have...
...one request
But...
It's fine.
Eh?
Is it okay?
Yuuko?
I will tie your hands
Hands?
Relax
Do you like this kind of thing?
Yes
Yuuko
Do you always...
I
Wanted to do something like this?
It is not Yuuko, right?
It's Master Yuuko, right?
Master Yuuko
Good boy
Did you like doing this kind of thing?
You always wanted more than sex
umm..
More than sex
Right..
What did you want?
Then.. Bend over!
Come on
More!
Yes.
Being dominated...
Getting tortured.
I'll do something like this.
You want to be tortured?
While enjoying.
As I thought..
You were imagining such things?
Yes, Master Yuuko.
Yes... It's Master Yuuko now.
It's already standing up?
I'm sorry.
Pervert!
But I like it.
I like such a pervert like you.
It's standing like this
Hiroshi is a lewd person
Likes it even more than sex?
Huh?
Yes.
You want to get destroyed?
Is it feel good?
It.. it feels.
Huh?
It feels good
Say it louder.
It feels good.
You look weak like a woman.
It feels good!
Yes.
You forgot about being a man.
Thus.
Be louder.
Is it feels good?
Good.
Then I will make you feel it more.
I will grant your desires to be stepped on.
It's good.
You want to get stepped on?
Please say it.
Master Yuuko.
Please step on my dick.
I can't hear you!
Do you want to get stepped on?
Yes
Lovely.
My dear, Hitoshi
I am happy..
I will definitely grant your desires
It's only me
Let's make love more
Well..
Are you embarrassed?
It's embarrassing.
Is it more embarrassing inside of this?
Release it like this.
Please don't look
You're a bad child, right?
I have to punish you
Do you want it?
Punishment
Do it like this
Oh.. It came out
Is it so much?
Ah, don't look.
Don't look!
Was it came out?
Is it feel good?
It feels good
Come on.. It's so much
Don't look!
Please don't iook at that sidelines
Don't look the sidelines
You're a bad child, aren't you?
Ahh! Thankyou very much Master Yuuko.
I'm so glad about that
Ah.. I want more
Master Yuuko
You're really good
Your ass becoming like this.
Poor you
May I show you?
You want to see it, right?
I'll let you see
You wanted it?
I wanted it
You can chew it
Suck it a lot
Yes
It's delicious
Delicious?
Feels good?
Ah.. It feels good
Hiroshi's nipples are sensitive
Again?
It come out more?
Like this... Come on
Come on
I'm sorry
Did you felt it?
Forgive me.. I'm sorry
It's fine
It feels good, right?
You wanted to do this with me, right?
Yes
You always enduring it, right?
Yes.. Like you said
Your dick wants to be licked, right?
Right?
Then.. I will make you feel pain
You might like this too, right?
Come on!
You still can't get enough pleasure with such things, right?
Come on
You like it this way, right?
Come on..
It came out again
Yuuko
Yuuko ?
Umm..
Your pussy
It's Master Yuuko, isn't it?
Master Yuuko's pussy is hitting me
Where am I hitting it?
On my dick
No!
Ahh! Master Yuuko
Ah.. It feels good
Is it feel good?
Don't!
I'm gonna cum!
Feels good?
Ah.. It feels good, Master Yuuko
Oh no!
Well..
Dick play is over now
Well, today
I am not interested in that.
You are not interested?
Shall we have more fun?
More fun?
You like it, right?
What?
I guess I am the man today
Because you become a woman
Please spread your ass
Is it embarrassing?
Ah., Don't look!
Come on... more
Spread it wider
Spread it
Hiroshi
I'm sorry
This looks so shameful
May I lick your shameful places?
Love it, including your embarrassing places
Master Yuuko
Does it feel good?
It feels good
Then, shall we do it more?
Come on.. Do you know what is next?
I know
You're cute
Come on.. I can see it well
No!
I've become skillful, haven't I?
Right?
Ah, don't!
Ah! I will cum!
I will cum! I will cum!
You still can't..
You still can't
Ah, don't
My legs are cramping
Ahhh.. Don't!
Don't! I will cum!
I will cum! I will cum! I will cum!
You can't.
Why are you trying to cum as a man?
You are a woman today
The place that I licked is your ass, isn't it?
What?
No more.
You wish you were a girl?
Huh?
I am a girl
Yes.
You are a girl
I will lick your pussy
Ah.. You digging in
My pussy feels good.
Feels good?
Good
Oh my god!
I cum!
I said you can't do it, right?
You want that we...
make love each other with your boy-pussy, right?
Well.. The preparations are done
Then I will put it in
In this pussy.
You want me to put it inside, right?
I want Master Yuuko to put it inside.
I will hit you with my dick
Well.
That's right
It got inside
Feels good?
Ahh.. It feels good
You want to be more free, right?
Come on
Right..
This...
Ah, it feels good.
This?
I will thrust it deeper
Make your voice louder!
Come on!
It feels good, isn't it?
Is it feel good?
This
Come on
Is it feels good?
Huh?
Do not hold back.. Release your inner voice!
Release your voice.
Come on!
Feels good?
Does it feels good?
Then..
I will hit you from the front
It has entered
Until very deep?
Huh?
It's deep.
It has entered,
No!
Feels good?
Huh?
Is it feels good?
No way!
Master Yuuko
Feels good?
It feels good
Shall I make you feel better?
Because we are loving each other
Right?
Does it make you feel good?
More
Ah! Don't!
Feels good?
You want to be more tired?
Ah! I cum!
Good kid
Master Yuuko
It feels good, right?
Everything
It's very dirty.
I will accept anything.
It's fine
Release it all
Then, next..
Shall you do it with me as a man?
Do you want to cum?
I want to cum
You want to cum.
Standing hard like this
Here.. Is it good here?
Here
Ah.. Amazing!
Ah, don't!
Don't? Don't?
Ah don't!
I'm cumming!
Ah! I'm cumming!
It's still.. still coming out
It's still come out
No!
Hurry up, please release it.. Please release it!
Please release it all!
Come on
Don't!
Come on... Release it!
It's a lot.. It's still coming out, right?
It's still coming out!
Come on.. Release it more
More
It's not come out anymore.. You came a lot.
I am happy,Master Yuuko.
Are you happy?
Don't get close with my dirty body
What are you talking about?
Your body is not dirty.
Don't!
Come on
We are loving each other.
I'm sorry.
Look.. Look at my eyes
I'm sorry
Look at my eyes
Did we love each other?
Right?
Master Yuuko is lovely.
I will grant any of your desires
Grandfather?
Wake up.
Grandfather
I came to show you how your pervert grandchild looks like.
Because in the past... Grandfather was also the same.
Like this masochist man, right?
Right?
Even though with such appearance
Do you want me to do it?
What Grandfather?
Yuuko is so slender
Pretty
I want to get bullied
Is that what grandfather wishes?
Then..
Yuuko will make it come true
Hiroshi
Please sit over there
Yes
Watch properly, okay?
want to taste it?
Do you Klke this?
Your face is bright red.
Grandfather is actually the most...
masochist man in the family, right?
It all started with you, isn't it?
More?
Are you happy?
That is so good, right?
More?
Like this?
Trodden like this?
You like getting trampled, right?
Are you happy?
Did you get excited?
Do you want to do it too?
Not yet
Please get make me more excited
Watch properly!
Look properly and get excited
Grandfather
You're really pervert, right?
Do you like being called pervert"?
Pervert!
Please say it more
This pervert!
I am happy
Are you happy?
Please do it more
Well.. I wonder what shall I do?
What's going on?
More
More?
What about here, Grandfather?
It seems immediately standing, isn't it?
Ms.Yuuko
Huh?
Here?
A bit more
A bit more?
Is it standing up, Grandfather?
Grandfather
You're so pervert, aren't you?
Do you want it?
More..
More?
More.
Delicious?
I'm happy
Well
I'll try to make Grandfather...
Return to...
the days,you werg young.
Oh my..
Grandfather
You Wave such an excellent thing
Well..
In what way do you want me to do it?
Huh?
Please try tell me!
I want you to do it with your hand
How to make you feel good?
I want you to torment me.
Do you want me to torment,you?
You want me to torment you?
Grandpa likes to be hit, right?
Well..
How?
It's standing steadily
Grandfather is amazing!
Grandfather
Even though this is so stinky
It is standing gallantly
Hiroshi
Are you watching properly?
Come on...
You are Iosing to the grandfather
Did you got aroused?
Your grandfather is so great
Hiroshi is..
Maybe I want Grandfather's cock
Is it okay, Hiroshi?
Grandfather with such a big smile
Do you want my pussy?
Is it okay?
I wonder what shall I do?
First, I will show you
You have not seen a pretty girl in a long time, right?
Accept this
As a souvenir in heaven
Not yet!
You still can't touch it yet
Come on
Come on..
Thank God
I will give you a fellatio
You want to be licked, right?
You want to be licked rather than licking, right?
I like anything
So I am correct, right?
Lock properly, Hiroshi.
Grandfather has a very persistent heart.
So I will give you a fellatio.
Ms.Yuuko
Huh?
Lock at me while you're giving me a blowjob,
That's right
Feels good?
Please make me more sloppy
You are a pervert!
Come on, pervert!
Is it feels good?
Make me feel good again
Then, boobs..
Eh? Is it okay?
Boobs
Enfold it.
Yes.
That's right
Yes
Come on
Yes.. Please rub it more
Like this?
Is this good?
Grandfather
You are pervert,.right?
You are pervert, right?
I will praise you
Thanks to your pervert tendencies...
Everyone here became a pervert
This gift all started from you
And everyone became a deviant pervert
I won't let you cum still
I will eat your testicles more and more
Not yet
I'm gonna cum!
You wanna put it in so much?
This is my last request
I beg you
You want to go to heaven
Do you want to put it in?
Let me do this before I go to heaven
Then I will make you feels good
Like to go to heaven
I will give you a present for heaven
Can you see it properly?
You have to see it properly
I can see it
You can see it?
Yes
It's entering
Feels good?
Come on!
Come on
Feels good?
Yes
Come on
Come on..
Grandfather
Is it feels good?
It's standing so hard
like when you're young
Is it feel good?
Ah, it feels good
You move it like that
Do it like this
You cannot move it, Grandfather?
II start move it like this
There
Grandfather you are still strong
You are powerful!
Grandfather.. Ab, it's good
Hiroshi
Are you watching?
Are you got excited by watching this?
Ms.Yuuko
Don't do it, Grandfather
Are you gonna cum?
It feels too good.. I'm gonna cum!
It will come out
It come out!
I'll thrust you!
Grandfather
You made Yuuko came
More.. I want a lot more
You want more?
This is good
Ah.it's good
Yes.. There!
Ah! That's no good!
Oh no!
Hiroshi
Doing this kind of things...
I will also.
Make Grandfather look embarrassed
Come on
Look at that, Hiroshi
This is lewd
Come on..
It's drenched like this
Look at me, Hiroshi
Can you see it grandfather?
I cum.. I cum!
I cum!
You still cannot cum
Well..
Grandfather is amazing!
It's erecting so hard like this
It's entering deep inside Yuuko's pussy
This pervert !
You are pervert!
Grandfather is splendid
Then, this time..
Grandfather try to ride on me
Take off this clothes
Now you're naked
Shall I put it in?
Grandfather.
Grandfather's dick
We're not done yet grandfather
Your hip shake is still amazing!
Do you feel good, Grandfather?
You are the best !
Is it okay?
As you like, Grandfather
More
More.
I will cum!
Do it like this.. Come on, do it like this
Yes.. deeper
Oh no! If's pumping so hard
Delicious.. Tasty
Ahhh.. Grandfather
Your tongue using is skillful
Ahh.. This pervert!
It's good
I'm cumming!
Ah! Grandfather..
That's right
Do it like that
Grandfather
Yuuko will take grandfather to the heaven
You are the best
The best..
Grandfather is amazing!
This is my last request.. I will release it
It's fine
Grandfather
Do you want go to the heaven?
You want to ascend?
Shake your hips like you want to die
Eh?
Please shake your hips until you reach your limit!
Like this?
More, right?
More?
Your pervert style is not only that, right?
You're more perverted, right?
Are you a pervert?
You are a big pervert, aren't you?
You want to be called pervert, right?
So shake your waist !
Ahh! Yes, like that
Ah! Pervert!
You are pervert!
Pervert!
I cum!
You will make me cum!
Because you're fucking me
I can't hold it !
Pull out!
Pervert!
You came a lot, pervert
Coming!
Arrggh! Stop!
Hey, pervert! You are okay with this, right?
Pervert!
Grandfather?
Are you dead tired?
Hey, Hiroshi
You are a pervert
Hiroshi...
I am..
A good wife?... or a bad wife?
I am a good wife, right?
I felt I finally was myself again
After getting married here
Me and this family's life will begin again