- Caption production, distribution Kukdasu dot com -
Roommate NTR ~ The best friend who stayed in the house
together and the wind of his girlfriend Cum video ~
What?
Attention?
Yoo-chan, are you serious?
Can not I? Conomi-chan
What happened?
Explain it one more time.
okay
A friend of mine
I think I was kicked out of my house.
Until a moving house is decided
To stay in our house
I really... I was just adapted to living together...
Yeah
But I'm really in trouble.
Really, it's too nice to ride.
Yu Chan
That's a good thing about Yu-chan
Is he a person I do not know?
Who is it?
Do you want to see pictures?
-Huh
He's such a guy.
It's called Kohei.
He's the usual band.
I put the band too high
She said she was cut.
So I can not get my monthly rent.
I think I got kicked out.
I may be the type I hate most.
do not say that
He's pretty good.
It seems a little tough...
Still pretty
The band is working hard.
It looks light.
It's not already in appearance.
- Nevertheless, the band
I practice all together.
I often missed Alba
That's it.
It looks like it came.
What happened?
Wait a minute
Who came?
Yusuke
Take a moment.
Girlfriend?
I'm Kohei.
Please, please.
Thank you very much.
What was the consultation a while back?
Kohei, now I have no money
I do not think I have a place to stay.
sorry
How long do we have to stay with him?
I'll let you out until next month, Konomi's birthday.
please
Really
It's until my birthday.
Promise
All right.
It's a promise.
-Huh
Konomi
birthday
- Making and distributing subtitles Cukdas.com -
Hi, girlfriend
Good morning
What about Yusuke?
Yu-chan went to Alba.
I work hard.
Cleaning?
-Yeah
I'll help you.
It's okay
no
I clean up.
Give it to me.
The man is more powerful.
thank you
Look, you're clean.
Really.
From Yusuke
I can not clean it.
You should do this.
I wonder if he can do the right thing...
I do not know how many times you changed the shift.
There's no such thing as good.
Iknow, right
Really
Because I'm really sincere.
Yusuke
Do you know Alva Leader?
Ok?
I did not say.
I did not know
The manager liked it so much.
It's nice to not talk.
I've been there.
Come on
- Yusuke, come on.
I was learning guitar from Mr. Kohei now.
like that
-Huh
try
It's not.
- It's wrong.
You told me.
It's not.
It is difficult
On this day,
This day, this day
This day I went to school
On this day,
That's why you can not play at all.
Conomi-chan
What are you watching?
I'm looking at Yu-chan's alba shift.
I was not that busy before...
Yusuke, I work hard.
It's a busy time now.
I can not help it.
Look at it
Let's drink this together.
What is this?
alcohol
alcohol?
But
Yu-chan is working hard.
Is it okay to drink?
Do not bother with such details.
Yusuke is sad when I look sad.
Let's drink this and keep it cheerful.
still...
Let's sleep.
Yes, I do.
Thanks
What do you like?
Did you get something?
- Pretty much.
Do you like alcohol?
- Yeah, I like it.
I want to drink something sweet.
- What?
There's a sweet spot here.
Thanks
this
good
Do you like this?
-Huh
Can you drink this?
- Yeah. - Thanks.
listen
Yu-chan
When I lived together, I said that I would play a lot.
I just do not get any attention at all.
What do you think?
I can not help it.
Can not you help it?
- Alvar leader.
still
Alba
I'm lonely
I know it's lonely.
Konomi-chan, I really like Yusuke.
is it?
Feeling?
Of course not.
It's on the face.
is it?
Did you drink lightly?
Yes.
The face is red
It's hot.
Do not you drink with Yusuke?
I do not drink with Yu-chan at all.
I have never seen him.
It's just Alba.
I do not have time to spend together
I can not help being busy.
Konomi-chan, what if you get drunk?
I?
Huh
When you take
a little
Brighten
Is it a little bright?
Yes, a little
a little?
Huh
So if you drink a little more?
If you drink a little more?
-Huh
Because it's so hard.
delicious
His face was red.
is it?
I see that, Konomi-chan
Do you and Yusuke?
Huh?
I left it with
Is not it hard to make such a time?
Yep?
What are you talking about?
-sex
Do not talk about it.
It's original.
-I will not
I will not?
-Huh
You can not lie.
Let's talk about it.
Another story?
-Huh
I'm sorry I was worried.
I do not care.
How are you doing?
Huh?
If I'm Yusuke
I can not stand it.
Huh?
When I go to a convenience store?
Huh? What?
Do not hide.
What are you talking about?
Do not you have that desire?
Yes
Let's do it.
You can tell me.
Let's stop
His face is red.
drink
Which way?
what?
Have you ever been?
I will not
Why do you lie?
Everybody's doing it.
Conomi-chan
Do not
- My body is hot.
It's hot.
Close
Did you lighten up drinking?
-Huh
Do you feel strange?
Yeah, I do not.
Are you ticklish?
-Huh
Ticklish
My face is red.
hot
It's a real sweat.
what?
Do not
Yusuke, touch these places?
I do not feel like touching.
I do not think so.
Do not
- I like this reaction.
If the whole body is sensitive
Is not this a weak one?
It's so desperate.
That's it, I'm dating my girlfriend.
Then give me one chance.
Chance?
I'll give you a nipple.
Because the accuracy is low.
Huh
right?
- Wrong.
Really?
No
You do not know if it's a lie.
Show me the correct answer.
-No
It's a lot of sweat.
Just a little, just the right answer.
Lightly, lightly
Is not it true?
Not right.
It is so pretty.
Why are you covering
- That's it.
It's fine because it's so beautiful.
Show me more.
I can see it.
Show everything
Do not
These places are sweating too.
hot
Here?
no
You're a big reaction.
Why are you worried?
This is not an affair.
It's wind.
- It's not the wind.
Everybody
Yes?
-Huh
Be big
It is very soft.
Yusuke will be fine too.
But Yu-chan does not touch it like that.
lie
What is it? Conomi-chan
Here?
Let's stop
I do not like this.
You have not even started yet.
Do you really want to do it?
Already a store?
It's wind.
The wind?
-Huh
Everybody's doing it.
Do you feel it here?
I can not be nervous.
I hear that.
I see everything.
Do not look.
What are you doing
Do not
- Is it hot? Conomi-chan
It's hot
Your ass is so pretty.
Where
Hate
Do not
I can not kiss you.
You have an affair.
It's okay.
You can just blame it on liquor.
No
You can not wash your chest.
Do not
It's getting bigger.
Are you always so sensitive?
no...
Probably not.
You do not really like it?
Hate
Show me your ass, ass.
I really need your ass.
Do not you think so too?
not really
Yusuke does not praise you?
hip?
-Huh
I will not.
That's weird.
What about the back?
Not the back.
Even if I do not like it,
Do you want to do more?
no
Really
Do not
Why?
Do you want to take a shower?
Did you want to take a shower?
Lots of sweat...
I lost a lot of sweat.
- That's good.
Hate
Where are you touching?
Did you reach your hand?
- I got it.
Where did you reach?
On the boat
navel?
no
where?
You got your hands.
Where did your hand touch?
here
It's a place you should not touch.
You can not touch it.
Tell me where you can not go.
I was soaked in my panties.
You can not touch it.
Is your country spreading?
You can not tighten it.
Why?
Do not
Do you feel it too much?
How did it go?
pretty
I'm really sensitive.
Are you helping?
no
I want it to stop.
I'll just look.
It's beautiful.
I think it's bad for Yusuke.
Are you done?
There's a dot, here.
point
point?
where?
here
I did not know
-I did not know?
I'll take a closer look.
It's too close.
Do not
No
It's dirty.
Do not suck.
Do not
It's beautiful.
No
I did not shower...
What about
Hate
It's also Yusuke.
Conomy-chan, are you here?
You can not be here.
Yusuke, is this what you do?
No no
Who ever did this?
Good mood?
Konomi-chan, where do you feel?
It's narrow.
My finger went in.
You can not put your finger on it.
He's already in.
Two
Two !?
-Huh
That's not it.
If you do it intensely...
Something came up.
sorry
Does this always happen?
I've never been out.
-Really?
So will you let me get more?
I'll touch you more.
Open wide
Is this good?
No no
Sorry
Why apologize?
So wet?
It's so wet.
I'm excited.
Please take care of this too
Suck it
Wash it?
-Huh
What can I do?
You've done it before.
No, that's it.
Yu Chan
Then practice
Think of it as practice.
-Huh
practice...
It is very good
Good mood?
Could you get it done now?
uh
I'll stop.
Can you wash it deeper?
deep?
I can do it.
You're doing great.
I can not go anywhere. I feel good.
You can not wash straight.
I'm not keeping it.
Do you really want to do it?
Rinse together.
It's like this with Yusuke.
What
No no
Conomi-chan
I can not stand it.
Is it over now?
-Huh?
it's over?
What are you talking about?
What
Are you fine?
Conomi-chan, you piled up?
no no
Are you trying to put it?
No no
I can not.
It's really an affair.
I do not change, I just put it in.
Hate
I can not.
Only glans
Hate
I did not do condoms.
It's good.
I do not have it.
Do you have Yusuke?
-there is
Let's do it.
I do not know where he is.
I know.
I will bring it
Let's condom
- I do not like it.
no
I will not be inside.
- I'll come with a condom.
I will not
Lightly
I'm outta here
no no
The sun went down...
Feeling good?
No
Subtract
You're still there.
I'm having an affair...
I have a condom and I have a condom...
Yes?
-No
Sometimes the no cone is good.
No
You can not do this...
You can not put it so deep.
Do not put it deep.
No no
Do not be violent.
Have you ever done it?
Doing this?
Not much.
Come in deep
No
I want to see your pretty ass.
-hip?
Show me your ass.
OK?
-Huh
Do you want more?
This is not possible.
No
Please forgive
Go to bed?
Do not make it hard...
Cry?
Are you feeling good and crying?
Do not be too hard.
No
Conomi-chan
Are you jerking?
I will not
Did you go away?
OK?
here?
It's weak inside.
It feels so good.
what?
telephone
Yusuke is not it?
telephone?
That's it.
It's Yusuke.
You can not.
What?
-receive
Hello
Yusuke
sorry
Now, Conomi-chan, I can not get a phone call
For me
like that
Ah
Conomi-chan, I think I can get it.
I'll change it.
Hello
Yu Chan
There's a lot of trouble.
Huh?
now
I was learning...
That's right, so I breathe.
I'm not good at it.
OK...
That's right
All right.
Huh
Are you coming soon?
Coming in half an hour?
All right.
I do not need anything.
Carefully
come carefully
Bye Bye
I'll be right back.
If it's 30 minutes
He will come.
Not enough
Did you actually want to do it?
No no
Why did not you tell me to help you?
Tell me how...
Do you want to continue?
no
Stop it?
Would you like me to stick it in?
He will come.
Until then,
I told you to be honest.
No
It's dangerous.
I think I will.
Do you think you will?
You said you would not go inside.
Good mood
Do not
No
Do not be cheap
Is it really cheap?
It feels so good to see Konomi-chan
It's okay.
It's really cheap...
So absurd
OK
Now that it's Yu-chan
We have to take a shower.
quickly
You can slow it down.
Let's shower
We have to make it fast
- All right.
- Making and distributing subtitles Cukdas.com -
I've been there.
Anyone else?
Conomy-chan?
- Yoo-chan?
Huh
Come on
-Huh
Take a shower?
right
listen
... because I sweat
like that
Kohei went to a convenience store?
Yeah, I think I went to a convenience store.
like that
Okay, then I'll be over there.
Yeah, it's over.
-Yeah
Why do I keep putting my finger
No
You came here.
I wrapped it too deep...
It's dangerous if you do not pull it all out.
You're done.
It's still there.
It's all out.
It's okay, now.
It's been a while
more
I have to pull it out.
I can do it by myself.
I'll help you till the end.
I'm sticking my ass.
Yoo came back.
No, that's it.
If you do so violently...
Conomi-chan
Touch it.
That's it.
I'm touching Konomi-chan.
It's getting bigger.
I just got wrapped up...
Why are you so excited?
- Why?
I wanted to put it.
- That's it.
You have a good girl.
No
Do not get violent...
You can hear it.
No no
No
I can hear her...
I think I will.
Do you think you will?
No
Not now.
You can just take it out.
-no
You can take it out.
-No
Do not be cheap
No
Never.
It's also full of...
Yu Chan too
in
I have not been cheap...
Bound to that day
Kohei
More
I will touch my hand.
No
Do not
It's funny.
I can not stand now.
No
You're wet too.
Take it out.
Konomi-chan, it was soaked.
No
Initially
It was only when I did not have any.
Conomy-chan?
What is it?
Kohei?
Condomi-chan, have not you?
do not know
You were just there.
Yes, I did.
do not know?
Did not you go to the store?
Getting
Even when you have a good time
I tried to hold me without worrying
I took ten years.
You did not get caught?
OK
Are you a little excited?
Look at this.
I'll get it for the sound.
It's a lie.
That's great.
I think I will.
awesome
What, that
I want to put
I want to put it
-No
Why?
I can not take it anymore.
I'll get it soon.
I can not.
You can not.
It was wet.
It does not matter if you do not make a sound.
Sounds like...
Do not
No
I can not bear to groan.
I'll take her.
Conomi-chan
I think I will.
It looks like it's coming out.
No
You can not afford it.
I feel so good
You can not be inside.
No no
No
Never.
It's wrapped in...
what...
Yu-chan
there is
I wrapped it inside...
- Caption production, distribution Kukdasu dot com -
And
That day
I came here suddenly.
Yusuke
Thank you.
Well, Kohei is glad he got home soon.
Do not get kicked out this time.
Thanks to Conomi-chan, too.
then
See you later
Good bye
Something, than I thought.
I left the hook.
Even if it looks like that,
But now I can spend my life alone again.
Conomi-chan
Huh
Yeah
Kohei's gone.
I do not even know him.
still
Tomorrow is birthday
Yu-chan, what do you do?
It's Yoo-chan.
Hello
Hello, Mr. Connor?
Tomorrow's scheduled.
Huh
I will go to school tomorrow
It will come before nightfall.
Is not it?
-Huh
I'm telling you,
Tomorrow night
Something that should never be missed...
What!?
But can you come at night?
I think it will be late night alba, and I will not be able to come until morning.
It's my birthday, I'm so sorry.
I'll buy you a nice present.
Huh
All right.
Alba Gym...
Sorry
I do not really know.
Hello? Cohey?
Konomiya
I get along well?
Hey
Tomorrow night...
- Caption production, distribution Kukdasu dot com -
cold
I lied to Konomi-chan,
Would you be surprised if I suddenly pop out of the veranda?
I worked as a dying person
This ring
Would you be happy?
Why, Konomi
Good?
I told you it was good.
I like you too.
What's going on?
I want to do this.
You've done a lot before.
Still not enough?
- Yeah, it's a little short.
How much do you have to do?
What if he's Yusuke?
Huh? Yoo-chan is fine.
I told you until morning.
By morning?
I can not believe it.
right?
It's my birthday.
I'm lonely.
-Huh
Lonely
I'm glad you're with me.
Like that?
- Yeah, good.
I just liked the sex I just had.
In fact, I
-Really?
I do not think it's enough yet.
Huh
Sincerity?
I want to do more.
You want to do more?
-Huh
It feels good.
Do you mind?
Compared to Yusuke?
Tough
What do you think?
Good mood
It's easy to take off.
- Yes, I'm sorry.
Is it hot?
Could you peel it off?
-Huh
So me too
Thanks
Kohei-kun, it's sweet.
Is not it?
Me too, Yu-chan
I think he likes Kohei more.
What is that
Because if you had not met Kohei
I do not think sex would feel so good.
Yes?
-Huh
I'll break up with Yu-chan.
Come with me.
No?
Sorry about Yusuke.
Okay, Yoo-chan
with me
Be a friend after you break up with me.
I'm sorry.
I can not do that.
Why?
Date with me
I
I'll do anything.
For Kohei
I can do it.
Kohei
Lie on the couch.
It's hard.
sorry
You've done it a while ago.
I still do not have enough
Is not enough?
I stood up
It is very hard.
What about this one?
this way
this way?
Can I suck it?
Good mood?
All right
happy
Have not you done anything like this to Yusuke?
Huh
I'm not Kohei.
I'm sorry about that.
Huh?
Do the other side too.
Good mood?
I'm glad you feel Kohei.
you're good
Really?
-Huh
Can I suck here too?
It's awesome.
It's so big.
I just went to Love Hotel twice.
Good mood?
Kohei's cock is delicious
Tell me and tell me
So good
because
You build it a few times.
It's because Konomi is cute.
So will you come with me?
That's another story.
Why?
That's how you do it
Thanks
I sweat.
I am sweaty because I am fast
Look at me.
Looking at me
Kohei, do you like this?
right
I'm really done.
I can do anything for Kohei.
Is not it hard?
Yeah, it's hard.
I still want to feel it.
Good mood?
-Good mood
Deeper
Can you do it fast?
Quickly...
Too large
Also suck the balls.
this way?
Suck it
Do not weave?
delicious
delicious?
-Huh
What flavor?
I'm not squeezing.
Wear it?
Who better to build Yusuke?
What do you mean
Does not Yusuke do this?
I have not played Yu
Then do it.
this?
-right
I feel good there
Good mood?
-Huh
I'll suck you.
This is only for Kohei.
Really?
Will we meet?
right
I forgot
what?
I have a present.
Gift?
Give me the bag.
Now, gifts
Thanks
What?
what is this
It's a crazy toy.
I know?
Denmage?
-Huh
this
A gift?
-right
No, really.
How do you do this?
It's better than nothing.
No, I'm glad.
What did Yusuke do?
No, maybe Yu-chan did not prepare anything.
Let's write.
Huh
How do you write it?
I'll tell you
come here
sit down
-Yeah
Find a nice place.
Huh
I feel good
Good mood?
-Huh
It's not a normal massage.
Huh?
I feel good
-Good mood? -Huh
Look up your clothes.
this?
-Huh
Do you feel the depth?
- Yes, I'm trembling.
Is this your first time?
Huh
This is my first time writing this.
Yusuke does not do anything.
Is not it too much for the first time?
Yoo-chan does not give me any of this.
Is not it interesting?
Is that so?
I feel so good.
Let's face it.
Look up
This? -Huh
- You can take off.
Do you sweat a lot?
hot
You cool?
-Huh
It's cool.
Hold your arm.
like this?
-Huh
I'll find a nice place.
- I do not like the armpit.
I really do not like it.
It's tickling.
Good mood
Good mood?
-Huh
Can we do it here?
Comfortably
-Yeah
Where do you feel?
Near
there
Let me know.
Place it in the middle.
Good mood
kiss Me
I like you
DENMA?
no
Kohei
I think I'm going.
I'll make you feel better.
Really?
Hold it.
like this?
-Yes
I have a mark.
It's moving.
Near
I feel good there
Would you like another place elsewhere?
Give me your ass.
hip?
-Huh
Give me your ass.
I sweat in my ass again.
Sorry
I know everything.
Put it in a nice place
Waist shake
like this?
Rub in a nice place.
Do you like direct?
directly?
Use your hand to open it.
Easy to wait
like this?
Can you use both hands?
Give it to me?
Huh
I'll put you in the middle.
-Huh
I feel good there.
Good mood
Is not it just getting away?
I think I'm going.
I think I'm going...
Then by practice
Do you want to play it yourself?
I?
-Huh
I can take this off.
Look good
-Yeah
Sit over there
This way?
-Huh
Sounds familiar.
Can you do it well?
Make sure you're wearing it straight.
It's very wet.
Let me know when I'm going.
He's gone
I bought them
No
Was it good?
Conomy?
-Huh
Are you tired?
I felt good.
So will you go before Yusuke comes?
store?
Huh
You were satisfied.
Not yet...
Still not enough?
Let's have sex
I want to?
- Yes, I want to.
how will we do it
Okay, then
Do you want to do it one more time?
I thought so.
I want to do it again.
Good mood
Also
I like the feeling of Kohei's cock.
Good mood
Kohei Islands feel good?
I got a bunch of them.
what is this
It's the taste of Konomi.
Did I lose it?
-Right
Give me
needle
Spit it out.
I like you
It's the happiest sex I have with Kohei.
Good mood
Can you move?
Yusuke can not do this?
I'm scared, I'm scared.
Hold tight.
I'll fall.
It's good to be strong.
Good mood
It feels good.
more?
Give me more...
I will move.
Can you move?
I'll try.
Good mood
I'm in a good mood so I can not stop my back.
I like you
So good
Good mood
I feel good there
Good mood?
-Huh
I feel so good
It's awesome
I like you
Come with me.
So what about Yusuke?
do not say that
Good mood
What do you think?
Do more
Do you think it's rice?
Do you want to be cheap?
Inside me.
Will you fill it in?
It flows in...
It's full.
Happy
Suck it
-Yeah
Good mood
Good mood?
It felt so good, did not it?
Yeah
I still feel good
Could you do it one more time?
I want to?
You want to put it again?
Good mood
Good mood?
-Good mood
I'm glad
Show me what's inside.
Good mood
Good mood?
-Huh
I also
I think I'm going...
I think it's rice again.
It's filled in.
It's awesome.
It is packed twice.
It's because of Konomi.
Kohei is great.
I like the cock so much.
Let's have sex this morning.
Yusuke is coming.
Yoo-chan is now
done
Kohei, I really like it.
I like you
I like it a lot
Is it a dream?
Are you here yet?
Let's get taxed
Good mood
Suck more
Kohei
I really like it.
Who is it?
Yu-chan !?
There's more behind
- Caption production, distribution Kukdasu dot com -
Look at this.
Why are you taking
It's good.
-Do not
If you leave here
Masturbating while watching this
Look here.
Why?
What is it?
there is?
uh
Was not it Konomi-chan?
I do not know.
I was there.
do not know?
Did not you go to the store?
Go to the store?
- Uh, I thought there was something I wanted to buy.
Really?
I still have shoes.
Are you wearing sandals?
No way, it's so cold.
Well
I think it was a while ago.
Who are you talking to now?
no
What is the veranda?
It was not on the veranda.
Yes?
He went to see a store.
No, I think he's at home...
I do not have it.
Yes?
-uh
I can not concentrate on the bathroom.
-Why
There's no way out.
Have you used the bathroom so long?
Me, long time.
- Did not you come out soon?
it is not so
What are you doing?
I'm not doing it.
I will not
What, you
Konomi-chan, where are you going?
I can not concentrate.
Conomi-chan, are you out there?
is it?
I'll look for it.
It's strange...
- Caption production, distribution Kukdasu dot com -