Shigaku Dorm
- Good morning.+- Good morning.
- Breakfast! Breakfast!+- Let's have breakfast!
Breakfast! Breakfast!
- You are the first one as usual Kuroda.+- All you ever think about is food.
Oh! It's time to open.
Let's dig in!
I can see her today again..
Good morning.
Good morning. +Mr. Kuroda. you're always early.
- You... look tired... these days.+- Ma'am, give me a large portion!
- Give me double mackerel.+- Extra juice, please.
- Give me a large portion of rice.+- Double croquette. please.
I'll prepare your order now. Please wait a moment+- Quickly!
- Not yet? Can I have a large portion of miso soup?+-I see. Just a moment.
- Extra-large portion, please.+- Extra-large portion?
Yayoi..
-A large portion is good...+-Me too...
This is mine.
- We are late!+- Hurry up!
Oh, dang!
Yayoi..
Ahh, Yayoi..
Yayoi...
She is always so kind... her beautiful voice, her smile, the look in her eyes..
and her... plump body..
Please eat well.
Yayoi... Yayoi..
Ya, ya... Yayoi..
Yayoi...
Yayoi!
But..but but
You look... tired... these days...
The dorm mother has to be like a good wife...
and a good mother.
I've been trying to be that.
I'm so busy every day that I don't have many opportunities to meet guys.
Sweaty and stained..
Many guys...
Oh... I overslept and now...I'm late for school.
I couldn't.. control myself...
I'll go to school after... I use the toilet...
What am I doing ?
I'm proud of my job as a dorm mother, but
I'll comfort you.
-I'll take care of you, Yayoi. +- Mr. Kuroda, stop it!
Wait!  Stop!
- No!+ -Don't you like me?
Don't you?
No, no. wait!
I have to be a good sister and mother to you..
- I could be a good husband you.+- What?
Don't do that!
No, please stop sucking so strongly
It makes my nippies feel good.
it makes me... feel so good
You can't suck my nipples...
No... not too rough...
Yayoi's boobs...
So big and soft...+This is it...
-Yayoi's pussy...+-N-No... right now it's too sensitive so... ah!
I-it's throbbing... ah!
It's tasty..
Ah... amazing..
It's throbbing... it's throbbing a lot...
Ah... it's so good... ah...
Tsuji...
It's in me...  ah...
So wet...
What a strong scent...
This is real sperm smell.
Ah, Yayoi!
Yayoi, wait, you're sucking my dick.
You are hard.
Lay down...
Amazing... it's so hard
It's... rock hard...
How did you make it so hard?
Ah... your mouth... ah...
I can't hold back anymore... ah!
-Yeah... + Ah... It feels too good
If you keep going I'm gonna cum...
Ah... cumming...
Yayoi...
My body feels...
Feels so good.
And so hot
Stand up...
I'm tingling all over...+And my body feels so good.
I'll hold it with my tits.
How is it? Like it?
It feels good.
- It's too good. + - Feels good ?
Feels like inside my pussy.
Amazing... It's all the way in..
Your boobs... they're so big my cock's going all the way in...
It feels really good...
I want.. want this to last forever...
What an amazing cock
Ah... Kuroda?
I can't hold it back anymore...
Please fuck me..
I'm begging you...+Please fuck me.
- Is it okay? + - Yes...
Here... please put... your cock right here...
- Quickly... please... + -Yes...
- Then... + -Quickly... I can't wait anymore...
I am going in... + -Gently...  Yes...
It's so good...
So warm...
Kuroda... this feels... really good...
I'm making weird noises... + It feels too good... ah!
Ah... your cock is amazing...
Amazing... my body feels so good...
I can feel it chrusting in and out of me...
Ah... so good...
My body, ah... it feels... ah...
Yayoi... you're soaking wet...
Ah... so good...
-Grab me.... touch me... + -Yes...
Ah... it feels good...
Your cock...
It feels good... I feel I'm gonna go crazy...
So good...
Amazing... it's so deep inside me...
It's going all the way in...
Yayoi...
What am I gonna do... you're getting tired...
Since Kuroda's been doing all the work...
My blood type is O.
Our bodies becoming one.
It makes me feel really happy...
- Really? Does my cock really feel that good? + - Ah... I can feel it in me...
I'm close... I'm gonna cum...
I'm gonna cum
It's so good, I'm gonna cum
More, do more... I want more...
Your cock feels so good.
Good. I'm cumming... ah!
Ah I'm cumming... ah
Feels good...
-Ah... Yayoi... + - It's gotten sensitive so...
I can feel each thrust... ah...
Cumming inside me...
Ah... I'm gonna... I'm cumming again... ah!
Cumming!
Hey, kuroda, fuck me from behind... + Please.
fuck me from behind...
- Fuck my pussy... fuck it... + Yayoi...
Ah... amazing...
Doing this from behind...
It's going all the way in...
I can feel it... brushing my flesh from tip to base...
Ah... Yayoi..
Ah... I'm gonna cum... I'm cumming... + Cumming... ah!
Ah... your boobs... they're so big... + They feel so good...
Awesome, Kuroda.
Ah, I can't hold back anymore..
No... ah...
I can't control myself...
I'm cumming... I'm gonna cum again... ah!
Ah, cumming... ah!
I want it... I want more... more...
I'm pushing it in...
Ah.. it's inside
Amazing... my hips won't stop moving...
Oh no... It feels too good.
Do it more... Bone me harder.
Oh no... I can't stop anymore... + It feels too good..
Ah.. so good... ah!
Amazing...
My pussy.. my pussy's soaking wet..
It's the first time this has happened...
My pussy's throbbing from inside...
I'm gonna cum, I'm cumming...
So good
Don't stop, keep thrusting, keep moving...
Ah, no
I'm goona cum again
Me too, me too, I'm close... + Ah, not...
More, do it harder.
-More... + -Ah... ah I'm cumming...
Feels good... feels too good!
Amazing...
It's coming out.
Aoyanagi!  Done!
I'm gonna pee my pants... I'm gonna pee my pants... I made it!
- So, I saw Kuroda during breakfast, but he didn't come to school.
It's rare he didn't come. His only merit is his diligence.
Maybe he's in his room masturbating.
For sure! He must be a virgin since he's not popular with the girls.
Poor guy.
- Let's go have dinner. + - I'm hungry.
- Are... we... ok... Yayoi? + -Yes.
It has... to be you...
Please... fuck me again...
I'm so happy. We'll have such a lovely life in the dorm from now on...
Come here... quickly
It's been one year since I started coming to this library.
This is the perfect place to study for my examination...
But above all..
my secret crush, Mayumi Sato, works here
It's almost one year since I've been in love with her
She takes good care of the books and works hard...
Excuse me.
I'd like to return this book... To which shelf... should I return it?
- Well, this book... goes over there. + -OK.
Over there?
Ok, thank you very much.
She's shy when she talks to men.
I really like how she blushes when she does.
But... I can't concentrate on anything... since I fell in love with her.
I'll fail the examination.
It's time to confess my feelings for her...
She'll turn me down... but then... I'll be able to concentrate again.
Excuse me.
Yes?
Excuse me... Mmmh...
Where is the... biology section?
It's... over there.
Thank you very much.
I dio it... But I failed...
Excuse me, Mr. Arai.
Eh, you know my name?
I'm sorry, I saw your name in the library card.
You remember my name!
This is a list of useful books in this library for the entrance examination.
Please use it if you like.
- Eh? Is this for me?
I'm sorry if I appear to care too much... Do your best!
I'm sorry to disturb you.
- Oh! + - Watch out!
Are you ok?
So soft... warm... and nice-smelling...
Excuse me, Mr. Arai?!
I'm sorry.
Her tongue feels so good.
I'm getting so horny.
Hey!
What the hell am I doing?!
Doing this kind of thing...
I know I'm not gonna get away with this so easily but still...
Satou's mouth is...
So warm, so wet
Feels good.
This is really bad...
I have to stop... I have to!
If someone sees us... ah!
Um... Arai...
Right now...
There aren't a lot of library staff around...
And this certain corner...
Isn't easily found by others so...
Huh?
People don't come here much.
Then...
That means...
Feels good...
Ah... It feels so good...
Getting head from Satou like this...
It's like a dream.
So, how is it?
Am I hitting the spot?
It's my first time.
Then...
Does it mean that for Satou.
I'm your first... ?
Yes.
I'm touched...
Satou...
I've...
I've been dreaming of doing this ever since.
Satou!
Ah... whoa...
Satou...
I'm embarrassed..
Wow
They're huge...
Awesome lingerie...
Satou
So you really are lewd, huh?
T-That's not true...
It's just that..
I wanted to try being a little aggressive...
You're this wet...
No...
Please don't put it in...
If you're this wet...
Other people will hear us...
Ah... so good.
I'm so embarrassed... no...
If you get too loud, someone will hear us...
I feel... weird somehow.
You're feeling weird, huh?
It's weird... it feels good... ah...
I'm cumming..
Cumming
Cumming!
Satou...
I can't hold back anymore...
No, not there...
No...
You can't put it there...
It's going in...
Not there...
No...
It hurts...
Ah... wait... wait...
I won't wait, Satou...
You're so hot...
And wet inside...
So deep... It's too deep.
Deep...
Your pussy's engulfing me.
Satou...
Deep... it's going in so deep...
I'm coming.
It hurts... ah!
You're so warm...
Having sex with Satou like this...
makes me really happy...
It's really painful.
But...
the more we do it...
the more it feels different.
Since I became a teen...
I've always been eyed by guys...
everyday...
I've been fantasizing...
about something like this happening...
That's why..
I'm also...
very happy...
Satou...
You're so tight..
Satou's...
pussy...
is so wet and easy to fuck.
Satou...
does it feel good?
It's so good.
Satou.
Where does it feel good?
I'm embarrassed.
Satou... please say it..
Where does it feel good?
Where?
My pussy.
Feels good
I feel even more motivated...
More... please say it more...
M-My pussy...
Your pussy...?
My pussy...
My pussy feels so good...
Ah... so good... I'm cumming... + Feels good...
Cumming... ah!
Then...
Now, let's do it from behind.
Come here....
I'm coming.
Feels good.
It's going all the way in...
Ah, cumming...
It's going all the way in... ah!
It's hitting so deep in my...
Ah... my uterus...
It's hitting my uterus...
It's hitting your uterus, huh?
Ah no... it's too deep...
Ah.. I'm cumming... ah
Cumming... cumming...
My hips can't stop moving...
Ah, cumming... cumming.
I'm being so loud...
Feels good...
I think I'm close.
I'm cumming...
After that, I went to the library every day and... + I did well on my examination..
Because... after studying...
I always had... a good time... at the library.
While my parents are traveling, + my brother and his wife are visiting me.
My sister-in-law  Miki, is my secret crush.
- Miki... here's your towel. + - Thanks.
I like the countryside because the air and the water are so fresh.
- I'm jealous, Satoshi. + - Are you... ?
This are my sister-in-law Miki's...
What am I doing? But it smells so good. I can't stop it!
I took a bath first. Thank you very much. It was a nice hot bath.
We already started eating.
Satoshi, now it's your turn. The water was good.
Satoshi, you're always very quiet.
I'll take a bath now.
Miki, I'm going to drink a lot. Serve me some drinks.
I can't resist it... I can't resist it...
Miki...
Satoshi?
Stop it!
Hiroshi is sleeping just next to me.
You know how my family are heavy sleepers once they're drunk.
No, no...
I can't control myself... - Satoshi, Satoshi.
I can't control myself...
It feels good.
You are so wet...
I haven't had sex in a long time.
You mean, my brother... ?
He doesn't sees me as a woman anymore.
Even though you're so fine?
Your dick is so hard.
So hard..
So hard.
He's making you feel so lonely.
I love you Miki, that's why I've been doing this...
Then we can't stop..
I'm about to come.
Amazing... it's standing right up...
W-Wait... what are you doing?
So tasty...
That's it...
Whoa...
You're this big, huh..
That's it.. whoa... you're so lewd.
Some pre-cum came out...
Ah... shit...
It's so yummy. Satoshi...
So delicious...
Does it feel good?
Ah.. fuck...
Here...?
Ah... shit...
Are you coming?
Ah... it's coming out...
Shit... I can't hold back anymore.
No, you can't do it like that...
If you do..
I think I'll go crazy..
But...
I'll feel really good too..
And that makes me happy.
Then...
That's why...
Let's do it like this..
It feels so good.
This is amazing..
Satoshi's..
hard dick is rubbing me. It feels good.
Ah... feels good.
You're rubbing my clitoris.
Amazing... it feels so good.
You're rubbing me so hard
W-Wait...
You get what I'm doing, right?
Can you feel it when I do this... ?
Sliding my pussy against Satoshi's cock feels really good...
Amazing... so good...
-So good... + - Fuck, so good.
I think I'm gonna cum.
Ah... it feels too good.. + I think I'm gonna cum soon...
So good... ah.
So hard..
I'll make you feel even better...
I wanna lick you... can you go on your knees?
- My knees? + - Yes...
- Like this? + - Yes...
- Are you embarrassed? + - Yeah, I'm so embarrassed.
- Does it feel good? + - It feels really good...
I'm gonna lay down under you, okay?
Just stay in that position..
Lower..
Feels good...
Wow... it's yummy...
I'm also coming.
So tasty...
- Does it feel good? + - It feels good..
Feels good?
So wet...
It feels good.
So good.
- It feels so good... + -Really...? I feel really good too...
So good...
Feels good...
- It's close... your cock is...
Yeah... that's it...
Is this good?
That's really good.
- What is? + -I think I'm gonna cum...
You're cumming?
Do you like what I'm doing?
Is it good?
-More... + - More... ?
More... more...
That's good... I'm gonna cum... ah!
Amazing
This much...
It's been a while, huh..
Amazing... I'll clean you up, okay?
Satoshi...
Miki...
Miki... I love you!
Saying things like that...
it makes me,
like this cock even more...
Hiroshi
I'm sorry...
Anytime soon...
This delicious cock...
I don't want to let it go...
Miki, hurry up!
The bus is coming...
Miki!
Satoshi!
What's she doing in Satoshi's room? Miki...
Hurry up!
Hey!
Satoshi, I don't want to leave.
I don't want you to leave.
- Will you visit me? + - Yes. I'll be visiting you soon.
It looks hard and tasty.
I want to eat it.
So tasty..
So good..
It's really good.
And so hard..
It's tasty.
Amazing... it's so hard...
I want your cock... please give it to me..
Yumeno... I also can't hold back anymore...
Please, give it to me..
Quickly...give it to me..
Faster.. put it in while it's hard...
Put it in me...
Huge...
- That's it...right there. + - Then...
- Put it in there... + - I won't hold back...
Put it in...
Ah, it's so big...
Ah... amazing...
Ah... it's so hard.
So big... ah... it feels good.
Ah, amazing... it feels good. + More, more
Big... a big cock... feels really good...
It feels really good...
Push it in... all tlue way in..
- I'II do like you say. + - Ah... amazing, so good, ah!
You're soaking wet and looking really lewd right now...
Ah, cumming... cumming, ah!
Ah... cumming
My pussy, feels so good.
Your pussy feels good
Your pussy feels really good.
Amazing... It feels really good..
Y-Yumeno
Not good, I think I'm close...
I'm cumming... I'm goona cum...
So hot... I feel so hot, I think I'm cumming...
I goona cum
Ah... amazing... ah
Ah... cumming, I'm cumming...
You gave me lot of hot cum...
Let me lick it...
Does it feel good?
Your cum is so tasty, Hajime.
I did it again...
I touched her... even though she's my guest.
But... it felt so good.
Mr.Imaizumi.
Good morning.
Ms. Yoneyama.
This guest house is really good.
- It's small but has a homelike atmosphere and good food. + - Thank you very much.
In addition...
this part... is also nice.
I was so depressed after I lost my husband.
But now, I think I must move on...
So I'm happy I came here.
I see...
So tonight...again...ok?
My pleasure
Good morning!
- She also lost her husband. + - What?
We met on the Internet because we are both going through the same situation.
We have to try to stay positive.
So we took this trip together.
But she told me it would be difficult for her to recover...
That is... horrible.
Miki!
Dinner will be ready soon.
Is...it?
Look! It looks tasty, isn't it?
We want to eat seasonal food, don't we?
Look... such a big eggplant.
- What's the matter with you? + - Nothing.
Look at this carrot. It's nice, isn't it?
This cucumber is very fresh and tasty. + Want to have it?
If I continue moping around...
will I waste my youth?
This is fine too, right?
It's my first time experiencing this...
I'm getting excited..
Someone please help me...
Very well, I'll take good care of you.
Touch me.
Ah... more...
Touch them harder.
One more time...
Don't tease me.
I'm so horny... since this is my first time doing this...
Is that so?
More... more... ah!
Ah... so good.
Good girl..
More...harder...
Touch my nipples too...
Amazing...
Feels so good...
More... do it harder...
Oh, no...
- My nipples too... my nipples... + - You like this, huh?
Lick it, lick it more... please...
Please don't torture me anymore... + Just lick it already...
Feels good?
More, more please...
Wow..
Wow.
Is it good? More... suck it more...
Feels good...
How's this...?
Even if it's just my nipples, I'm really turned on right now...
Ah... it feels so good.
It's so good.
Getting sucked like this feels really good.
Lick them well, please.
- Do you like my tits? + - I love your tits...
Amazing... ah
So good... I'm so turned on right now... + So turned on...
I'm going crazy...
I'm-going crazy...
I'm gonna make you even crazier...
I'm getting crazier already...
Your cock .
Usugi's... big cock...
That feels good...
I'm gonna make you feel even better...
Ah... come here and look at me.
What do you want?
I want a big dick.
I want a hard dick.
Please touch my pussy...
Ah.. it's so big..
Amazing... ah.
What a strong scent...
Looks nice.
I won't give it to you yet.
So huge... huge...
Hot.. your cock is so hot...
It's hot... ah, no... I'm going mad...
Ah, it's my first time doing something like this...
You want more... ?
- You want more? + - More... I want more...
I want to do it rougher...
- You wanna go crazier? + - I want my whole body go crazy.
You can't stand it anymore.
Your cock... ah...
Your cock... poke my tits with it... + Poke my nipples too...
It's so good... I think I'm cumming. + I'm cumming already...
So crazy... ah.
- Are you tired? + - No..
It felt really good...
Ah... amazing...
Your cock's gotten hotter
Like this...
Your cock against my...
More, fondle my huge tits some more...
Really...
I want it
I want your cock.
Your cock...
Please make yourself feel good.
Your dick...
Want more?
I want it
How are you feeling now?
How about here?
Please... touch me...
Like this...?
Hey... please... touch me...
Please... ah
Awesome...
Ah... amazing...
Amazing...
Ah... so good.
Amazing... so good..
Don't stop... touch me more...
- It feels good. + - Look at me.
Ah... can't take it anymore...
It feels so good.
Amazing...
Please touch me... + - Want me to use my tongue?
So warm...
It feels good.
Amazing... it's so good.. + Didn't know it could be this good...
Amazing...
I'm gonna cum... ah!
Ah...cumming...
That's awesome
After cumming so much
you got even more beautiful.
Then, let's do your ass next.
My ass?
Ah... that feels good... oh no.
Such a strong scent..
I'm so embarrassed... please don't lick it..
How about here?
Ah no... that's no good...
Your cock.
I want it... I want it so much. + Please give it to me...
Don't pull out.
Now...
Over here...
Your finger... finger... I'm feeling tingly all over..
Feels so good..
My pussy... no
You don't like it?
It's so hot inside.
It's inside my pussy
Ah... amazing...
I'm cumming... cumming... cumming...
Ah... good...
One more time.
That's it...
One more time...
No more, it's still sensitive... ah! + - Can you feel it? My finger?
No... l'm gonna cum again...
I can't stand it anymore... please
your cock...
give it all to me...
Such a big one
More... I want it deep in me...
Do you want me to slide it...like this?
I want to feel even more good... more...
It's going in... it's going deep inside me...
My pussy feels so good... + I think I'm going crazy...
Your pussy... is awesome.
It feels so good... so good...
Your cock is amazing... it feels so good..
It's so good... I'm going crazy...
I'm gonna cum... I'm cumming.
I'm cumming...
Ah... no...
Cumming, ah
No... no
- Ah... amazing... + - Are you enjoying it?
So good... it's hitting so deep in me. + Feels so good
I'm gonna cum again.
Ah, no...  I'm  gonna cum...
Cumming... I'm cumming...
Cumming...
Cumming... gonna cum...
What the hell are they doing?
They're doing it again.
Do you want more... ?
Ah...amazing
I'm gonna cum again
Ah... so good
-Amazing... it's hitting so deep inside me... + - Ah... so good.
Ah... cumming... I'm cumming...
Ah... does it feel good? + -Ah... I think I'm going crazy
Ah... I'm so embarrassed.
Ah, I'm gonna cum again. + I'm cumming.
I'm so... embarrassed
- You're embarrassed? + - Yes.
I'm embarrassed..
I'm gonna do even more embarrassing things to you.
It's amazing.
I can see your pussy clearly. Miss.
I'm so embarrassed.
Like this, and then...
Ah... it feels weird... it's hitting me so deep inside..
It's so good...
Because it's going all the way in...
You're so hot inside...
Ah... amazing
- Amazing... I can really feel you inside me... + Hey, you feel really good.
It's warm.
Whatever you do to me is embarrassing...
I'm going crazy... I think I'm going crazy...
Good... good.
Awesome... more...
So good
I'm gonna cum, gonna cum, l'm cumming.
I'm gonna cum too... + - I'm cumming... cumming, cumming
Ah... cumming...
Ah... cumming... no...I'm cumming
Ah... amazing... raw dick... Raw dick is amazing...
Ah, it's tight
It's tight... ah.
Ah, amazing... I'm tightening up inside.
How is this...?
Ah, it's so good... + It's all the way in...
Does it feel good?
I'm going crazy... I'm going crazy...
No... no good
I'm goona cum, I'm cumming again.
I'm gonna cum again, cumming...
Ah, cumming...
cumming... your cock... so hot.
cumming... cumming... cumming
- Ah... cumming... + - Cum inside me...
I'm cumming too...
Cumming... ah!
Cumming...
Ah... I'm gonna cum too...
I also...
must move on...
I'm gonna cum, I'm goona cum...
I'm coming!
I can't stop it...
It's too much for me to bear...
I can't satisfy myself...
Mr. Imaizumi... I want...
Where... ? Where is he?
Mr.Imaizumi, where are you?
Why is he not here?
Will I ever... be happy again?
I shouldn't... have come here.
Oh! Ms.Kira, are feeling ok?
Wait! Wait! What?
What's wrong with you?
Wait! Stop!
Calm down...
-I want you. + - What?
It smells so good.
I have to have it again.
It's throbbing.
Amazing... it got this big.
So good... my mind's going blank...
Kiara... what's gotten into you?
She said she wanted to look ahead and move on.
That's why she went on this trip with you.
So that's why...
I understand now...
If you're okay with me,
then please let me do you.
Amazing... you're this wet...
It's so wet.
Amazing... this is awesome...
I'm going in...
So hard..
Ah... amazing, amazing...
Feels good...
Awesome...
Ah... amazing.
-Ah amazing... inside it's...ah,ah. + -Ah... so hot..
So hot...
My uterus, it's hitting my uterus...
It's going so deep, it's hitting my uterus.
I'm going crazy
Ah... it's so amazing... amazing...
It's hitting me... it's hitting my uterus.
Somehow... it's... it's too good...
Amazing... it's so amazing... + It's going right in my pussy...
Even though it's so big, + it slides in so easily..
I'm gonna melt... I think I'm melting... ah!
I'm going crazy... ah!
A-Amazing...
You're so wet inside...
This is too amazing...
Ah... I'm going crazy...
It's amazing... so amazing...
- My pussy... it's so wet and messy... + - Was l... was I able to help you?
I forgot how much.
keeping your nipples warm is important.
Oh no... I'm going crazy... + Going crazy... going crazy...
I'm gonna cum... I'm cumming... + Cumming... ah!
- Ah... it was so good. + - Come here...
Come here, come here... + On your knees...
Amazing... ah
Fuck me... please fuck me.
It's pushing inside me...
In my pussy...
- It's so hot... you're so hot inside... + - Ah... amazing.
I feel like my insides... are melting...
I'm going crazy..
Ah... awesome...
-Do you feel good? + - I feel good...
Fuck me...fuck me some more... Fuck me harder...
How is this? How's my cock?
More... touch me more...
What amazing nipples!
Yes... that's it...
Ah... amazing...ah...ah
Ah... it's hitting my uterus... ah
Ah... I'm cumming, cumming... + Your cock, it's driving me crazy.
I'm gonna cum... I'm cumming... + Cumming... cumming!
- Aoshi... kiss me... + - Kiss you...? Ah...
Cumming... cumming... cumming
Amazing...amazing...ah
It's so good... ah, I'm gonna cum..
Cumming
Awesome.
Ah, awesome...+ - Now it's my turn...
I'm gonna put this in my pussy
Amazing... it's so deep..
Amazing... so amazing... your cock..
Amazing... amazing... it's going inside my pussy...
It's going all the way inside my pussy...
I'm gonna cum again... I'm cumming again... + Cumming...
I'll pinch them.
I'm going crazy... crazy... my pussy is... ah...
Your cock in my pussy...
I'm cumming...
Oh, no... ah...
Ah, I'm cumming again... cumming...
Your cock... your cock feels so good..
So hot.
So hard... this cock... feels so amazing...
Ah cumming...
Me too... I'll cum so hard in you
Ah, amazing, amazing
Ah, cumming... I'm cumming
- So good, my pussy... your cock... so good... + -Ah... good... so good
It's so hot I'll get burnt.
Ah...no... I'm gonna cum again
Kiara, come here.
It's so good, so good, it feels really good
- My pussy... pussy... + - Me too...
My pussy... feels so good... so good
Ah so good... so good
- Amazing... so good... I'm gonna cum again... + - Feels good?
FeeIs good... it's so good... It's too damn good
Can I cum in you?
- Give it to me... cum inside me... please. + - I'm gonna cum...
- Cum inside me... cum a lot... + - I'm cumming... I'm cumming... ah.
Amazing... I came deep inside your pussy...
It's thick...
My pussy...
It tastes good...
Until the end... Let's continue until the end.
The rumors were true...
This place heals women's bodies and hearts.
What, an Internet rumor... ? Now I understand.
That's why so many female guests want my body these days.
But I want to heal even more.
So I'll extend my stay!
It's not fair... Let me join you.
My pleasure!